Naruto
火影忍者
Oh my God a good morning good evening guys.
哦，我的上帝，早上好，晚上好，伙計們。
So yeah I want to talk about a little thing
所以，是的，我想談談一些小事
My friend made for me
我的朋友為我做的
You might have noticed already it's like it's right there
你可能已經註意到它就在那裡
But it looks really cool I like it Ash it's on but I think it's pretty it's going to be
但它看起來真的很酷我喜歡它灰它在但我認為它很漂亮它將成為
And nothing for the all the games that we can be playing today probably be playing later
我們今天可以玩的所有遊戲都沒有可能在以後玩
But
但
I thought about and love it by Kimani everybody hey
我想過並喜歡 Kimani 的每個人，嘿
The only good day so far or good evening if you just got home from work or from school or whatever
如果您剛下班或放學或其他任何事情回家，那麼到目前為止唯一的美好一天或晚安
What's up guys what's up
怎麼了伙計們怎麼了
Yeah I know right it looks really cool doesn't it
是的，我知道它看起來真的很酷不是嗎
So it's for a
所以這是一個
For when we eventually to play
當我們最終要玩的時候
Closing shift ends you know
下班結束你知道
I think it's going to be
我認為這將是
I heard yet so I can make drinks like your Starbucks employee or something I don't know also
我聽說了，所以我可以像你的星巴克員工那樣製作飲料或我也不知道的東西
I
一世
On it said turn on the the dog years for today because you guys
上面說今天開啟狗年，因為你們
How's like
怎麼樣
Help us reach pretty big goal we hit 200k
幫助我們達到相當大的目標，我們達到了 200k
On-switch today
今天換機
Yeah we hit 200k on Twitch we hit 200k on YouTube because 200k overdue underground sweater everything
是的，我們在 Twitch 上達到了 200k 我們在 YouTube 上達到了 200k 因為 200k 過期的地下毛衣一切
Right now so I just want to say thank you guys so much for
現在所以我只想說非常感謝你們
You know supporting me on everything inside
你知道在裡面支持我
Reaching those amazing Milestones her pogging jogging
達到那些驚人的里程碑，她慢跑
Let's go
我們走吧
It's really really awesome so like you know hit those those goals in the see those numbers
這真的很棒，所以就像你知道在看到這些數字時達到那些目標一樣
Billy Gunther cell
比利岡瑟細胞
Thank you guys so much.
非常感謝你們。
I'm embarrassed involved because like
我很尷尬因為喜歡
I guess in.
估計進去了
Oh yeah besides all the shame that's happening tonight we're going to be streaming in a
哦，是的，除了今晚發生的所有恥辱，我們將在
About
關於
12 hours from now to since we're playing until dawn in like 12 hours
12 小時從現在到我們在 12 小時內玩到黎明
Today was I hope you have fun today
今天是我希望你今天玩得開心
Thank you I keep forgetting to turn text-to-speech off all my goodness but
謝謝，我一直忘記關閉文字轉語音功能，但是
Donation in Logan luck on your test
洛根捐款在您的測試中運氣好
Am I going to be okay of course I'm going to be okay I'm always I'm parking right now I took a nap earlier to
我會好起來嗎當然會好起來我總是我現在正在停車我早點打盹
So I think I should be fine but if you want to know who did the you know that I set for me
所以我想我應該沒問題，但如果你想知道誰做了你知道我為我設置的
I'm for my hands it's a Jack or a parasitic fun he has no I'm he did the same thing for my ears and for the tail
我是為了我的手這是一個傑克或一個寄生的樂趣他沒有我是他為我的耳朵和尾巴做了同樣的事情
So y'all can give them some love to if I let you know because only support the people that are making
所以如果我讓你知道，你們都可以給他們一些愛，因為只支持正在製作的人
Also hold on wait there's a lot of people donating stuff oh yeah right I hope you die
也等一下，有很多人捐贈的東西哦，是的，我希望你死
You guys enjoy the mystical of yesterday
你們享受昨天的神秘
It was really f****** fun and so I really am really glad I got to play with him and we are definitely planning to
這真的很有趣，所以我真的很高興能和他一起玩，我們肯定打算
Play something more in the future I don't think we're more buddyman that because we molded the f***
以後玩更多的東西
Out of our minds from that game but it was still really fun but just
在那場比賽中我們沒有想到，但它仍然很有趣，但只是
I think there's only so much a super Bunny man we can both tolerate you know
我認為只有這麼多一個超級兔子人我們都可以容忍你知道
So we're going to try and look for something else so later yeah
所以我們會嘗試尋找其他東西，所以稍後是的
Don't know what'll it be I don't know if that has missed the plate away out already I think he might have right
不知道會是什麼我不知道那是否已經錯過了盤子我認為他可能是對的
I feel like know I should play a way out with Vox because I'll be replaying it takes to sew
我覺得我知道我應該和 Vox 一起玩出路，因為我會重播縫紉的過程
I think about that
我想那個
Oh yeah and the again thank you so much for the 200k on
哦，是的，再次感謝您提供的 200k
Suction YouTube something really embarrassing look like
吸YouTube的東西真的很尷尬的樣子
I'm so sorry it's all my normal viewers I know I do have Normy viewers out here too and they're just like
很抱歉，這都是我的普通觀眾，我知道我這裡也有 Normy 觀眾，他們就像
I don't know I feel like she always what the f*** whenever I die do some type of off
我不知道我覺得她總是在我死的時候做些什麼
Making a noise like that self and my apologies but thank you for supporting me still regardless of all of my
發出這樣的聲音，我很抱歉，但謝謝你仍然支持我，不管我的一切
Cringe but free activities
畏縮但免費的活動
Okay
好的
Also I thank you for all the results today thank you so much guys and welcome back to the guild all the all the guild East
另外，我感謝你們今天的所有結果，非常感謝你們，歡迎所有東公會回到公會
Dumb
啞的
Pray thank you for the $6.90 suffocating for the 1000 B
為 1000 B 的令人窒息的 6.90 美元祈禱感謝
Resolve any further affect your lungs. Gummy bear I think you for the 1001 that he owes for the local 502
解決任何進一步影響您的肺部的問題。小熊軟糖我想你是為了他欠當地 502 的 1001
Baba baba blah ignores thank you for 10000 video
Baba baba blah 忽略了謝謝你的 10000 個視頻
Wow
哇
Holy s*** Bro also I think I saw some washing but Mighty. Thank you for the also for 10,000 b as well
神聖的 s*** 兄弟，我想我看到了一些洗滌但強大的東西。謝謝你也為 10,000 b 以及
I guess say thank you for that from yesterday but thank you so much again
我想從昨天開始感謝你，但再次感謝你
Phoenix thank you for the $6.90 in cup of beans thank you for the tendon tear on gifts as well
Phoenix 感謝您提供價值 6.90 美元的一杯豆子，也感謝您提供禮物上的肌腱撕裂
Is really good Subs guys and forgive him some love back to the community it means a lot
真的是很好的替補隊員，原諒他對社區的一些愛，這意味著很多
A nipple
一個乳頭
Guess I'll just
想我就
Also saw someone that you really are
還看到了一個真正的你
5 tons of steel
5噸鋼
We got the only dislikes guys what the f***
我們得到了唯一不喜歡的傢伙什麼他媽的
Thought ya
以為你
Those are just so you know because I want to say thank you for it one more time because those are real
這些只是為了讓你知道，因為我想再說一次謝謝你，因為那些是真實的
You know big big that's a lot of Gil these we have a lot of deal these now and I hope you guys
你知道很大很大，這是很多吉爾這些我們現在有很多交易，我希望你們
Guys are enjoying your time at the guild whether you're just you know chilling out and lurkin or off your participating in the chat
伙計們正在享受你在公會的時光，無論你只是知道放鬆和潛伏還是不參與聊天
For all you know you're fussing at this Corridor your Clipper Channel or you liked it song
據你所知，你在這條走廊上大驚小怪你的 Clipper 頻道，或者你喜歡這首歌
Anything at all that just seeing Alden someway just helps me and I'm security
以某種方式看到奧爾登的任何事情都對我有幫助，而且我很安全
Means a lot and I see you guys so I really do appreciate it and I hope you guys enjoy the stream tonight
意義重大，我看到你們，所以我真的很感激，我希望你們喜歡今晚的直播
Really wanted to play this game for a while since I saw and development holding shift
真的很想玩這個遊戲，因為我看到和發展保持轉變
Because I know it's the
因為我知道這是
I just really like Sheila's are games a lot I love indie horror so much and
我真的很喜歡 Sheila 的遊戲 我非常喜歡獨立恐怖遊戲
M3
M3
Thank you for that $13 also.
也謝謝你那 13 美元。
It is why I feel like I should turn the text to Joe sometimes because I like I feel bad when I'm talking over it or like one
這就是為什麼有時我覺得我應該把文本轉給喬，因為我喜歡在談論它或喜歡一個時我感覺很糟糕
Sometimes
有時
I don't know when's the right time to have Text-to-Speech on honestly I got figured out some time for myself
我不知道什麼時候是開啟文字轉語音的合適時機 老實說，我已經為自己找到了一些時間
I did like I know I don't confuse my my brain
我確實喜歡我知道我不會混淆我的大腦
I really I love him before is a lot and thought anytime I play indie horror
我真的很愛他
Games it just makes me like go back to really comfortable space and saw
遊戲只是讓我喜歡回到真正舒適的空間並看到
It's like you know when you're playing a game that you're usually feel like you're at home with right
就像你知道當你在玩一個遊戲時，你通常會覺得自己在家一樣有權利
Realization review games are home with like some people you know sit back and chill and play Dark Souls and or Elden ring
實現評論遊戲就像您認識的一些人一樣，坐下來放鬆一下，玩黑暗之魂和/或Elden戒指
And stuff like that right and they feel super comfortable or they play retro games or Mario games are Nintendo games are Pokemon games
像這樣的東西，他們感覺超級舒服，或者他們玩復古遊戲或馬里奧遊戲是任天堂遊戲是口袋妖怪遊戲
For me it's always indie horror in the I don't know why that is it just like there's something beautiful about it
對我來說，這總是獨立的恐怖，我不知道為什麼會這樣，就像它有一些美麗的東西一樣
And jogging to play more this
和慢跑玩更多這個
Just saw and share it with you guys make me really happy so I'm excited
剛剛看到並與你們分享讓我真的很開心所以我很興奮
I don't
我不
How do you get comfortable horror games I don't it's hard to just drive it's like I'm I love horror games
你如何獲得舒適的恐怖遊戲我並不難駕駛它就像我喜歡恐怖遊戲一樣
A lot I guess and I've been playing it for so long and Whores a consonant
很多我猜，我已經玩了很長時間了，妓女是一個輔音
Genre video games I've always been consuming since I was a young Rogue since I was a young boy
我從小流氓時代就一直在消費的類型電子遊戲
I've always been interested in horror
我一直對恐怖感興趣
So
所以
Can you die Stout elyx
你能死嗎 粗壯的 elyx
Oh my God
我的天啊
I'm about to spill your drink on the on your lap if you keep doing that I swear
如果你繼續這樣做我發誓我會把你的飲料灑在你的腿上
You only do that right
你只做對了
I'm your I'm your bastard send that a barista I'm going to f****** throw your drink
我是你的
Acura on your lap
謳歌在你的腿上
And say oops did I do that
並說哎呀我這樣做了
Are spitting your drink spit in your drink
吐你的飲料 吐在你的飲料裡
Yeah
是的
I'm just getting onto that I get fired on day one though my God if I did if I did that
我才剛剛開始，我在第一天就被解雇了，但我的上帝如果我這樣做了
I also need thank you for the 51 gift Subs bro thank you thank you
我還需要謝謝你的 51 禮物 Subs bro 謝謝謝謝
I'm just kidding I would never do that I feel like I could not bring myself if I were to ever be enough
我只是在開玩笑，我永遠不會那樣做
I'm not going to come in the drink if I were to ever be you know in customer service and stuff like that I would never
如果我在客戶服務和類似的事情上成為你所知道的，我不會進來喝酒的
You know the file somebody else's to I feel like that's just like a low blow and it just feels gross like I wouldn't want that so
你知道別人給我的文件我覺得這就像一個低級打擊，感覺就像我不想要那樣
Lights off
關燈
Never would do that to anybody else
永遠不會對任何人那樣做
Also suffer I'll send you for the 12:45 Gasol's bro
也受苦了我會送你12:45加索爾的兄弟
Thank you so much and I'll concession bro what's up
非常感謝你，我會讓步兄弟怎麼了
Haven't heard the pufferfish in a while
好久沒聽到河豚的聲音了
Alright
好的
But I hope you guys are excited for this soft drinks tonight I am I'm super duper excited
但我希望你們今晚對這款軟飲料感到興奮 我是超級興奮
Clemente thank you for the $20 install Glock of work
Clemente 感謝您安裝 Glock 的 20 美元工作
I'll be in trouble while you're watching all right
在你沒事的時候我會遇到麻煩
Only tell you not to watch but good luck
只告訴你不要看但祝你好運
Alright so let's see
好吧，讓我們看看
The triangle for the game right now since I want to get right into it
現在遊戲的三角形，因為我想直接進入它
I hope everybody's having a good morning so far
我希望到目前為止每個人都過得愉快
A good evening
一個美好的夜晚
Hands are good afternoon wherever you are in the world are you watching from the f****** love you guys
手是下午好無論你在世界上的任何地方你都在看著 f****** 愛你們
I had a nightmare earlier today
我今天早些時候做了一個噩夢
When I woke up and thought I was going to Spooky but then I saw like at whenever I like have a
當我醒來並以為我要去 Spooky 時，但後來我看到就像我喜歡的時候有一個
Strathmore I'm stressed out usually I do like looking through my Monday I'd like to do is like look through Twitter
Strathmore 我通常壓力很大 我確實喜歡瀏覽我的星期一 我想做的就像瀏覽 Twitter
And look at my art sag
看看我的藝術凹陷
And I'm just see like all the cute stuff you guys like doodle like I I remember I was like
我只是看到你們喜歡塗鴉的所有可愛的東西我記得我就像
I really wanted a hug or like to cuddle we cuz like I don't know
我真的很想要一個擁抱或喜歡擁抱我們因為我不知道
Whenever I'm working a little anxious hugging my pillow that makes me feel a little bit better
每當我工作時有點焦慮，抱著枕頭讓我感覺好一點
But all I saw someone drew like this fan are over
但是我看到有人像這個粉絲一樣畫的都結束了
Me hugging or Vox hugging me and that made me feel a lot better
我擁抱或 Vox 擁抱我，這讓我感覺好多了
I forgot who they invite you know who you're talking about you know who I'm talking about every tweeted it I think
我忘了他們邀請誰知道你在說誰你知道我在說誰我認為每條推文
So thank you for that is really our
所以謝謝你這真的是我們的
Really healthy
真的很健康
Let me look
讓我看看
4 MI
4 英里
The game
遊戲
Missing children
失踪兒童
Here it is
這裡是
It sounds so bass boosted reduce the volume a little bit
聽起來如此低音增強了一點點降低音量
It's time for spooky boys hold on I'm going to
是時候讓恐怖男孩堅持住了，我要
Quickly go over and
快速過去並
Get your make your drink so give me a second all right I'll be right back
把你的飲料拿來，給我一秒鐘，好吧，我馬上回來
Do not
不要
Do not perceive prefer like a quick second thank you thank you
不要覺得喜歡一秒鐘謝謝謝謝
All right there we go
好吧，我們去
Now look for the game they already are
現在尋找他們已經是的遊戲
So I also have yet this heart rate monitor
所以我也有這個心率監測器
At this point I feel like I should have a heart rate monitor for area spooky stream these days I think I just appropriate right
在這一點上，我覺得這些天我應該有一個區域幽靈流的心率監測器，我認為我恰到好處
Play a lot of these Sands School adds another layer of a fun when you got
多玩這些 Sands School 會增加另一層樂趣
I can see my heart rate when you play games like these sometimes
有時候玩這樣的遊戲我可以看到我的心率
Okay I guess I'm keeping the dog ears on for the stream like sometime
好吧，我想我會像某個時候一樣為溪流留著狗耳朵
Times I feel like some people don't like the dog you actually can I get a pole like what you guys want to
有時我覺得有些人不喜歡狗，你實際上可以我得到一根桿子，就像你們想要的那樣
Dog years on Earth all gears off for the stream until I didn't really ask about
地球上的狗年一切都在為流而準備，直到我沒有真正詢問
Well. I think it'd be a good idea to check and see how you prefer I know a lot of people are going to say yes
好吧。我認為檢查一下你的喜好是個好主意 我知道很多人會說是的
Don't even know why I'm asking invited. Might as well you could be surprised
甚至不知道我為什麼要邀請。或許你會感到驚訝
I want to so much mancillas sodalicious again that's why I always
我想要這麼多的 mancillas 再次社交這就是為什麼我總是
Shocking Wanna Miss the said like oh I don't like the actually like, the f*** what the hell
令人震驚的想念說喜歡哦我不喜歡實際上喜歡，他媽的什麼鬼
Galaxy bro a shocking absolutely shocking
Galaxy bro 令人震驚 絕對令人震驚
I've never heard of a British person that said they didn't like see you but I guess there's a first for everything right it's like
我從來沒有聽說過一個英國人說他們不喜歡見到你，但我想每件事都有第一個，就像
It's like having a Whatsit having an Asian person say oh I don't like using chops
這就像有一個亞洲人說我不喜歡用排骨的 Whatsit
Or like and I'll large saying hearing like a Canadian person say all I hate
或者喜歡，我會說聽到像加拿大人一樣說我討厭的一切
Maple syrup Idaho something like that I guess it just like it's like gas wow that's crazy
楓糖漿愛達荷州之類的東西我猜它就像煤氣一樣哇，這太瘋狂了
You know you don't like see either but he's so good I love tea
你知道你也不喜歡看，但他很好，我喜歡茶
I'm drinking black tea right now since. It was Maya go to sell decaffeinated
從那以後我就在喝紅茶。這是瑪雅去賣不含咖啡因的
And has a little bit of honey in it
裡面還有一點蜂蜜
I'll hold on let me get closer to
我會堅持讓我靠近
My microphone hello
我的麥克風你好
I thought it's been awhile okay long time
我以為已經有一段時間了
Yep that's my name I heard you became a boy Detective
是的，這就是我的名字我聽說你變成了男孩偵探
I can understand your decision especially after that incident
我能理解你的決定，尤其是在那次事件之後
I feel for you
我對你有感覺
That's why I want to talk to you about this I believe you can help us out this time because of
這就是為什麼我想和你談談這件事我相信這次你可以幫助我們，因為
What's a bully detective again I'll explain the details in person
又是什麼惡霸偵探我會親自解釋細節
I'll be waiting at nekamo may see you there a boy Detective
我會在 nekamo 等你 可能會在那裡見到你 一個男孩 偵探
What
什麼
Is it like
是不是像
I believe this is a like all the bad cop
我相信這是一個像所有壞警察一樣
Is it sounds like a bad cop you know the ones that you know
聽起來像個壞警察嗎？你認識你認識的那些
Or like maybe a vigilancia detect I don't know
或者像我不知道的警戒檢測
Doesn't make sense to me
對我沒有意義
Looks like everything is okay so far
到目前為止一切都還好
Fellowship I love you I love you too bro good morning
團契我愛你我也愛你兄弟早安
Responses getting your nervous excited for what will happen I'm excited to
讓你緊張興奮的反應將要發生的事情我很興奮
I'm really excited to get I'm always happy to play games like these
我真的很高興得到我總是很高興玩這樣的遊戲
A lot of fun
多好玩
Hello
你好
He look like that
他長這樣
York high
約克高
Thanks for coming saddle
謝謝你來馬鞍
So
所以
To put it simply
簡而言之
Three Junior High School students went missing
三名初中生失踪
But
但
We're suspecting. It's not a case of kidnapping
我們在懷疑。這不是綁架案
One of the kids parents overheard their conversation of meeting up on the TV went missing
一位孩子的父母無意中聽到他們在電視上見面的談話失踪了
Awesomeness you should be able to help you out
真棒，你應該能夠幫助你
Be quiet to badmouth
對壞話保持安靜
Don't be too harsh on him
不要對他太苛刻
Should be taking a break at the back there
應該在後面休息一下
Oh and one more thing
還有件事兒
I want to save come talk to me anytime
我要保存隨時來找我
I love it when the
我喜歡它的時候
You know
你懂的
Characters break the fourth wall like that is like if you need to save your game just come talk to me
角色打破第四面牆就像如果你需要保存你的遊戲就來找我談談
Oh
哦
Oh wait this bannable
哦，等等這個禁令
This is like twitch TOS I don't know weight has armpits
這就像抽搐TOS我不知道體重有腋窩
Look at that while you actually look really pretty is looking at the ceiling
看看那個，當你看起來真的很漂亮的時候正在看著天花板
I'm so tiny
我是如此渺小
Wait why my showtime for
等等為什麼我的放映時間
I want to save
我想保存
Yeah
是的
Why are you looking at the ceiling look down at me I'm so short bro why the f*** am I so short
你為什麼看著天花板低頭看著我我這麼矮兄弟為什麼我他媽的這麼矮
Why are why don't like that
為什麼不喜歡
You look he looks creepy to
你看起來他看起來令人毛骨悚然
It's just a model
這只是一個模型
Oh
哦
Don't talk to me so abruptly
不要這麼突然地跟我說話
I thought my heart's going to stop
我以為我的心會停止
So your detective yamaka sound talked about what I'm looking at his chest can I can't move my
所以你的偵探 yamaka 聲音談到了我在看他的胸口我不能移動我的
My face to look at is
我要看的臉是
Forget his face
忘記他的臉
Not really a detective I mostly just help out struggling kids in schools
不是真正的偵探，我主要只是幫助學校裡苦苦掙扎的孩子
And people start calling you a boy Detective
人們開始稱你為男孩偵探
Whatever it is I find it very hard to trust a woman who looks so
不管是什麼，我發現很難相信一個看起來如此的女人
Real take on a mission like this Q
真正承擔這樣的任務 Q
Anyhow
無論如何
Amazon sold me
亞馬遜賣給我
You know a lot more about these kinds of things than us officers
你比我們這些官員更了解這些事情
How many Clues
多少線索
Hotsy
辣妹
Occurrence of the missing kids friend
失踪兒童朋友的發生
Is all the girls communicating via private online chat
所有女孩都通過私人在線聊天進行交流嗎
Natural is music key
自然是音樂的關鍵
Let's go to her house first
我們先去她家
If you're really like to help us out that is
如果你真的想幫助我們，那就是
Okay thank you for letting me look at your chest and sorry time it's not that impressive honestly
好的，謝謝你讓我看看你的胸，對不起，真的沒那麼令人印象深刻
I feel so short guys on my God
我覺得我的上帝太矮了
Sorry yeah TV this is Otis about the word
對不起，是的，電視，這是奧蒂斯這個詞
The people use to say shorty
人們常說矮個子
Cuz I got TV
因為我有電視
Funny enough
夠有趣的
Alright
好的
This kind of makes me want to go to all I don't know if you guys saw those like videos of like the
這種讓我想去所有我不知道你們是否看過那些喜歡的視頻
Those are Japanese vending machines but I really want to go and check those out sometime
那些是日本的自動售貨機，但我真的很想找個時間去看看
I'm in the future like I know there's like dedicated restaurants in areas for like those vending machines still
我在未來，就像我知道在那些自動售貨機之類的地區還有專門的餐廳
Where you going music is house
你要去的地方 音樂就是房子
Hello there
你好呀
Where would you like to go I'll knowing this the crack you're actually
你想去哪裡我會知道這就是你實際上的裂縫
I'm not sure it's only mean
我不確定這只是意味著
I'm 5-9 we talked about this
我 5 到 9 歲，我們討論過這個
Oh
哦
Hey there
嘿
Are you
你是
Who are you
你是誰
What do you want from me
你想從我這裡得到什麼
You're here for music you she's not here there's no point of coming inside
你來這裡是為了音樂你她不在這裡沒有必要進來
Whiskey's gone I can't be bothered right now
威士忌沒了，我現在無暇顧及
You please go away
你請走開
You're not even the police
你連警察都不是
You Think You Are
你認為你是
Well rude ass lady I didn't even get a chance to talk
粗魯的屁股女士，我什至沒有機會說話
Grandma she doesn't really look like a grandma she looks like an ODS
奶奶 她看起來不像奶奶 她看起來像 ODS
Karen snow I feel like she gives me more of like a you know it's like the ship
凱倫雪，我覺得她給了我更多的感覺，你知道這就像船
R-on-t
R-on-t
You know
你懂的
Like all those on seas that are just like assholes to the family voices
就像所有在海上的人一樣，就像家庭聲音的混蛋一樣
Doggo
狗狗
Hey doggo hey doggle
嘿狗哥嘿狗哥
Still breathing
還在呼吸
I guess he's just old is Sissy just sold
我猜他只是老是娘娘腔剛賣掉
Can I can I pet him
我可以撫摸他嗎
Can I communicate
我可以交流嗎
I hope he's okay
我希望他沒事
Okay at 8 breaking bad happen to the dog
好的 8 點壞事發生在狗身上
Doesn't look so good
看起來不太好
Is it like it's not just me right you just doesn't look so good
是不是只有我是對的，你只是看起來不太好
Not sure why
不知道為什麼
There's nothing back here
這裡什麼都沒有
Is Dad no say that no he's not dead he's just taking a nap you know like
爸爸是不是說不，他沒有死，他只是在打盹，你知道嗎？
Dogs get older they have less energy and they just want to sit around and be lazy right
狗變老了，他們的精力越來越少，他們只想坐在那裡偷懶。
Is a child or an old man with a child with the
是小孩還是老人帶著小孩
Old man mask
老人面具
Is one multiple as weird no matter how I swing it in the returns
無論我如何在回報中搖擺它，一個倍數是否很奇怪
This isn't so fun
這不是那麼有趣
What sucks to suck you back in my day I used to play with a Game Boy advanced than
在我曾經和一個遊戲男孩一起玩的時候，把你吸回來是什麼糟糕的事
Play all Pokemon FireRed and LeafGreen and I also had a what else I have
玩所有 Pokemon FireRed 和 LeafGreen，我還有一個我有的
Transformers
變形金剛
And you got to Windmill. Kind of sucks
你到了風車。有點爛
It's about bow-bow thank you for the odd since you're 12 Subs bro also
這是關於鞠躬謝謝你的奇怪，因為你也是 12 Subs 兄弟
Don't know what to do here
不知道在這裡做什麼
Is that it
是這樣嗎
And I could talk to you mr. officer
我可以和你談談先生。官
Guy and see what's up
伙計，看看發生了什麼
Demon Slayer Demon Slayer mask
惡魔殺手惡魔殺手面具
Where do you like to go
你想要去哪裡
Could you come with me
你能跟我來嗎
Well I
那麼我
I'm not good at this kind of thing
我不擅長這種事情
Please
請
Don't suck unless it's police
除非是警察，否則不要爛
Fine
美好的
Understand
理解
Believe me if anything happens
相信我，如果有什麼事發生
Wow
哇
He like walked into me
他喜歡走進我
So you just came inside of me what
所以你剛剛進入我的內心是什麼
I checked it over cuz how the how the model looks
我檢查了它，因為模型看起來如何
Getting some more water
多喝點水
Or I Morty rather also thank you for the donation
或者我莫蒂也很感謝你的捐贈
Thank you
謝謝
Oh
哦
Looks like you brought an actual officer this time what kind of what is this discrimination bro why is it Matt
看起來你這次帶了一個真正的軍官這是什麼歧視兄弟為什麼是馬特
Water from the officer or not
官員的水與否
Still there's no way I'd let you win
仍然沒有辦法讓你贏
Too bad we can't help it
太糟糕了，我們無能為力
The time being let's go to akiko's
暫時去秋子家吧
Raw why is everybody like
raw 為什麼大家都喜歡
She's hiding something
她在隱瞞什麼
Yeah she's definitely hiding something you officer let's go
是的，她肯定在隱瞞什麼，你的軍官讓我們走吧
Would you like to go Akiko Salas
你想去Akiko Salas嗎
Cop is so lame he doesn't even know he's not even assertive or anything like that
警察太蹩腳了，他甚至不知道他甚至沒有自信或類似的東西
How much you be useful help us out
你對我們有多大幫助
Interrogate the suspects Elmo she's a suspect but
審問嫌疑人 Elmo 她是嫌疑人，但
I'm trying to look we're trying to look for the kids right so
我正在努力尋找我們正在努力尋找正確的孩子所以
Guys stop calling me short song not sure I'm 59
伙計們不要再叫我短歌了，不確定我是 59
I'm pretty sure I'm sorry than the lot of you I started talked about this so much I'm not sure
我很確定我比你們中的很多人感到抱歉 我開始談論這個太多了我不確定
Newspaper article 1 could be domestic abuse
報紙文章 1 可能是家庭虐待
It's also the middle schooler in town on September 14th takumi softball 12 years old was found dead in the toilet
也是9月14日鎮上的中學生壘球匠12歲被發現死在廁所
IC prefecture
集成電路縣
With numerous wounds on his body police suspect his parents a single mother might be up in the culprit
他身上有多處傷口，警方懷疑他的父母可能是單親媽媽的罪魁禍首
His mother might have been the culprit
他的母親可能是罪魁禍首
59 that's like 175 cm
59 等於 175 厘米
Deadpool yeah let's get a pull start something I want to see how tall a buddy is I'm 59
Deadpool 是的，讓我們開始吧，我想看看朋友有多高，我 59 歲
I'm pretty sure there's a quite a quite a lot of you that are underneath 59
我很確定你們中有相當多的人在 59 歲以下
Alright
好的
Don't lie all right don't lie because if you lie then you look like a dick
不要撒謊，不要撒謊，因為如果你撒謊，那麼你看起來就像個雞巴
And you're just all you just look make yourself look like an idiot to
而你只是你看起來讓自己看起來像個白痴
Those people have no right calling me
那些人沒有權利叫我
Commercial boy
商業男孩
Not case cuz I'm not a boy
不是因為我不是男孩
No one's answering
沒有人回答
Maybe there's someone around
也許身邊有人
Oh yeah if you're taller than 6 ft than you are a children
哦，是的，如果你比孩子高 6 英尺
Sorry Titan bro I don't know
對不起泰坦兄弟我不知道
You look so
你看起來如此
Frail
脆弱
I mean I guess this is the grandma look right
我的意思是我想這就是奶奶的樣子
Cheese don't scare me like that
奶酪不要那樣嚇我
I thought I was going to straighten my back
我以為我要挺直我的背
What are you looking for I don't know if I should do a gram Voice or not
你在找什麼我不知道我是否應該做一個克語音
I apologize for interrupting
我為打擾而道歉
My name is softball
我叫壘球
I've heard Alcatraz gone missing I'm trying to gather evidence
我聽說惡魔島失踪了 我正在收集證據
I have a look inside the house
我看看房子裡面
Oh
哦
Is Akiko okay
秋子好嗎
Who's acting very strange lately
誰最近表現得很奇怪
I'm anxious now
我現在很著急
Please find Akiko
請找秋子
I believe in you
我相信你
And of course of course
當然當然
Take a look inside the house as much as you'd like
盡可能多地看看房子內部
Okay Grandma
好的奶奶
Kind of voices that I don't know I was trying to think of like frail old lady and just didn't end up
一種我不知道的聲音
Y'all look it up 80% of you guys or are shorter than 5 ft 9 what's
你們 80% 的人都查一下，或者身高低於 5 英尺 9 是什麼
Projecting much
投射很多
Excuse me
打擾一下
It's locked
它是鎖著
Grandma's being weird as well everybody in this area I think everybody in general
奶奶在這個領域的每個人也很奇怪，我認為每個人都
Being weird
怪怪的
Okay we'll fly
好的，我們會飛
Says it's luxville go in Ono way it's not locked
說是luxville go in Ono 沒有上鎖
I thought your permission first
我以為你的許可首先
That's always going on
這總是在發生
It's locked
它是鎖著
Lady Grandma knows something
外婆知道一些事
Washer noise coming from inside sale you guys hear that
內部銷售的洗衣機噪音你們聽到了嗎
Hello
你好
Who's moving self
誰在移動自己
Tell Grandma
告訴奶奶
You live like this
你這樣生活
Cup noodles everyday that's not really good that's a lot of us sodium in your system if you're getting up noodles
每天喝杯麵不是很好，如果你起床的話，我們體內的鈉含量很高
All the time and it's not very nutritious
一直在吃，而且不是很有營養
Let me make you a meal I'll make you a
讓我給你做一頓飯 我給你做一頓
Make you something delicious
給你做點好吃的
A lot of vegetables vegetables are delicious guys you should eat your veggies more they can be so good
很多蔬菜蔬菜都很好吃，你應該多吃蔬菜，它們會很好吃
I just feel like a lot of people don't know
只是感覺很多人不知道
You know
你懂的
Parrot or like to know how to prepare properly
鸚鵡或想知道如何正確準備
I thought the Vox about this so many times but I'm just surprised at the amount of YouTubers
我曾多次想過 Vox，但我只是對 YouTube 用戶的數量感到驚訝
That hate vegetables
討厭蔬菜
Like you're so good
就像你那麼好
You can make it taste so good
你可以讓它嘗起來很好吃
Has are missing out
錯過了
Eat your veggies
吃你的蔬菜
My my vegetable propaganda
我的蔬菜宣傳
No don't go in I'll talk to her
不，不要進去，我會和她談談
I guess we should just go talk to Grandma again
我想我們應該再去和奶奶談談
The Boston the Boston
波士頓波士頓
Knology, Boston
Knology, 波士頓
Opossum
負鼠
Please don't scare me like that. I was going to string my back
請不要那樣嚇我。我打算把我的背
I just met you earlier
我剛認識你
What's that song
那是什麼歌
I think it's because you have a face that is hard to remember
我想是因為你有一張很難記住的臉
By the way I could use room was locked
順便說一句，我可以使用房間被鎖定
That's offensive I mean she's a grandma so I guess it's hard for an old lady to
這很冒犯我的意思是她是奶奶所以我想一個老太太很難
Number
數字
Do you know where the key is
你知道鑰匙在哪裡嗎
Okay God I know I called the guy called the carrot a fruit by accident yesterday
好吧，上帝，我知道我昨天不小心把那個叫胡蘿蔔的人稱為水果
You guys are mean look like it was an I was being but I was flustered there was a lot happening Mr
你們很卑鄙，看起來就像是我，但我很慌亂，發生了很多事情，先生
That was giving me like a shitshow of a time I couldn't think straight and
這給了我一個我無法思考的時間的狗屎秀
Is inoa care is a vegetable I just called it a fruit by accident all right I know it's not actually a fruit
inoa care 是一種蔬菜嗎 我只是偶然稱它為水果 好吧 我知道它實際上不是水果
Okay sometimes you just your brain
好吧有時你只是你的大腦
Brakes about it
剎車
You know where the key is
你知道鑰匙在哪裡
How would I know
我怎麼會知道
Let's see
讓我們來看看
I think I saw something about it looks like a key around here
我想我看到了一些關於它的東西，看起來像是這裡的鑰匙
I can't quite remember where they'll
我不太記得他們會去哪裡
Okay so we have to look around for the key
好的，所以我們必須四處尋找鑰匙
Probably on the ground somewhere
大概在地上的某個地方
Most likely right
最有可能是對的
Is asset
是資產
Wow
哇
Hey I found the key grandma
嘿，我找到了鑰匙奶奶
Okay almost felt like I was getting a lot longer to be honest
好吧，老實說，我幾乎覺得我變得更長了
OSHA Tokay police officer spooked me for a second I thought that was a monster
OSHA Tokay 警察嚇到我一秒鐘我以為那是怪物
If you would like waiting down the hill I didn't think you would come up the hill with us
如果你想在山下等著我沒想到你會和我們一起上山
Tell you what it tomato is a tomato is a fruit
告訴你番茄是什麼番茄是水果
Yeah right tomatoes are fruits yeah
是的，西紅柿是水果是的
I think
我想
Fun
樂趣
Hello
你好
I found another key
我找到了另一把鑰匙
Don't know what's $4 for storage their terrible graffiti
不知道 4 美元用於存儲他們可怕的塗鴉
On the bag. Are they
包上。他們是
Grandma
奶奶
Grandma are you dying out there
奶奶你在外面死了嗎
Stop dying
別死了
Yeah the Arts really pretty though
是的，雖然藝術真的很漂亮
Really cute outfits
真的很可愛的裝扮
Scripture the noise came from this room right
聖經噪音是從這個房間傳來的
Don't answer the phone
不接電話
I think I will
我想我會
Hello
你好
May I ask who's calling
請問你哪位
Other thing I can hear someone singing
其他事情我能聽到有人唱歌
What happened to the lights
燈怎麼了
F*** that no I'm not coming outside
去他媽的，不，我不會出去的
Are you crazy
你瘋了嗎
I'm sitting back here
我坐在後面
Be a man you mean be a man I'm a manly man
做個男人，你的意思是做個男人，我是個有男子氣概的男人
Check it
檢查
Since you want to f*** around with demons
既然你想和惡魔混在一起
Ghost
鬼
Hello
你好
What's that
那是什麼
Nothing
沒有
Hello
你好
Right weight is it are you Akiko
合適的重量是你Akiko
Agency that
代理機構
What's wrong
怎麼了
Do you know where your mother and father are
你知道你的父母在哪裡嗎
A child
一個孩子
Right
正確的
They
他們
Is there not
有沒有
Will they come back
他們會回來嗎
Stop talking much as she
別再像她一樣說話了
On your hand
在你手上
.
.
Dog
狗
What dog food
什麼狗糧
Why do you have that
為什麼你有那個
Hey want to come down
嘿想下來
She doesn't want to talk to me anymore
她不想再和我說話了
But she isn't too scared
但她並不太害怕
Just kind of lifeless
只是有點死氣沉沉
I wonder why she's lifeless guys I know she has dog food don't make the shut up shut up shut up
我想知道為什麼她是死氣沉沉的傢伙 我知道她有狗糧 不要讓閉嘴 閉嘴 閉嘴
I want to hear it I don't hear it don't
我想听我不聽不聽
Okay
好的
Wow
哇
That's
那是
Weird
詭異的
Don't think she should be eating dog food
不要認為她應該吃狗糧
Or maybe she's just having a she wants to feed a dog
或者也許她只是想餵狗
This is the storage key
這是存儲密鑰
This is the storage
這是存儲
I don't know I just picked up what is this called again
我不知道我剛剛又拿起了這個叫什麼
It's like one of those are
就像其中之一是
All those charms right
所有這些魅力都對
It's like a sachet
就像一個香囊
Or off
或關閉
A lucky charm it is it's a lucky charm
幸運符 它是幸運符
A talisman
護身符
The Galaxy Gill g a little bit more I don't know what to do with this music use I'm amore
The Galaxy Gill ga little bit more I don't know what to do with this music use I am amore
Also, Maury
還有，莫里
Phenom amore
現象級愛情
I'll talk to Grandma
我會和奶奶談談
Omamori omamori
禦守禦守
Grandma
奶奶
Great grandma
偉大的奶奶
Opossum
負鼠
Where'd you go
你去哪兒了
Was she even a real I don't think she was real she's probably dead everybody here is probably f****** dead
她是不是真的我不認為她是真的她可能已經死了這裡的每個人都可能死了
Okay
好的
Go to music he's house
去他家聽音樂
Maybe if I show the the charm
也許如果我展示魅力
Siwa
西瓦
Set her right
設置她的權利
Where did you find this
你在哪裡找到這個
This is Miss Keys precious charm
這就是凱斯小姐的珍貴魅力
See
看
I guess I have no choice
我想我別無選擇
If it's from musically
如果是從音樂上
Or we can go inside now wow
或者我們現在可以進去哇
Did I love how we can't even communicate with the auntie
我喜歡我們甚至無法與阿姨交流嗎
You know you don't even say anything she's just very one you know sided conversation
你知道你甚至什麼都不說 她只是一個你知道的側面談話
You're not looking so good
你看起來不太好
Misiki
三木
She looks scary till
她看起來很嚇人
Alright
好的
This is her room
這是她的房間
The music starts yeah there's no music in here
音樂開始了，是的，這裡沒有音樂
All the cat mug
所有的貓杯
Oh my God account Motel
Oh my God account 汽車旅館
It looks like music he had a boyfriend
貌似音樂他有男朋友
Look very happy
看起來很開心
Her boyfriend's name is safety at all
她男朋友的名字是安全的
What was that
那是什麼
Toys R Us
玩具反斗城
If you are such a dick
如果你是這樣的傢伙
Oh my God I'm going to I'm going to spank you slap you
哦，我的上帝，我要去，我要打你一巴掌
U of my
我的你
But my tail dumbass don't do that
但我的尾巴笨蛋不會那樣做
I'm looking at passwords access it
我正在查看密碼訪問它
Okay well I don't have a password so f****** I guess and I guess again axis it I think
好吧好吧我沒有密碼所以f******我猜我又猜我想軸它
Yeah
是的
IHeartRadio
心臟電台
I love how reflective d
我喜歡反光的d
Boys are like do you guys ever see wooden floors this reflective
男孩們就像你們見過這樣反光的木地板
They must be really shiny or like really clean I don't know
它們一定很閃亮或者很乾淨我不知道
I don't see those guns for as much
我看不到那些槍
Box of masks
一盒口罩
Okay
好的
Is this
這是
Please break up with me
請和我分手
I regret sitting seats you do come
我後悔坐你來的座位
It's embarrassing to tell everyone say to dokkan doesn't have the money or the brain
跟大家說dokkan沒錢沒腦子好尷尬
McKenzie sports right
麥肯齊運動權
I don't need you in my life
我的生命中不需要你
Mom says she should break
媽媽說她應該分手
Up with you
和你一起
Musiqi
穆斯奇
Huh
呵呵
You lady
你這個女士
Oh my God
我的天啊
Guys
伙計們
I can't do this
我不能這樣做
There's so much designer bulshit this spooky Miguel it's so quiet in this goddamn house
有這麼多設計師胡說八道這個怪異的米格爾在這該死的房子裡很安靜
Okay
好的
Why are you in my room
你為什麼在我房間
Play also she wrote the letter
還玩她寫的信
Did I tell you can go into my room
我告訴過你可以進我的房間嗎
Whatever
任何
Come to think of it
想想看
Music he's been meeting up with her friends recently
他最近和她的朋友見面的音樂
Last time she went out
上次她出去
What is what can I use house
我可以用什麼房子
Why don't you go there instead
你為什麼不去那裡呢
Senpai
前輩
Do I have the letter now or know she probably took the letter f***
我現在有這封信還是知道她可能拿了這封信 f***
Okay
好的
Wait I want to read the letter again because like I want to make sure like
等一下，我想再次閱讀這封信，因為我想確定喜歡
It was cheese on that forged it was what do you guys think that she right or is that actually I'm pretty sure
這是偽造的奶酪，你們認為她是對的，或者實際上我很確定
The mom wrote the letter so like a f*** with the piano
媽媽寫這封信就像鋼琴一樣
That's weird
這很奇怪
Really weird
真奇怪
Alright well we have a box of masks maybe the kid with the masks would like it right because
好吧，我們有一盒口罩，也許戴口罩的孩子會喜歡它，因為
He seems.
他似乎。
There's an elected office and if not then damn I have no f****** idea maybe the kid maybe the other kid with the dog food
有一個民選辦公室，如果沒有，那該死的，我不知道也許那個孩子可能是另一個吃狗糧的孩子
Would trade it masks for the dog food I don't know
會用口罩換我不知道的狗糧
Yeah I don't like it when parents are very
是的，我不喜歡父母很
I don't like it when parents I govern your relationships like that like
我不喜歡父母我這樣管理你們的關係
You know like they don't want you to hang out with certain people and stuff like that like I remember my mom didn't want me to hang out
你知道他們不想讓你和某些人一起出去玩，就像我記得我媽媽不想讓我出去玩一樣
I was like two people I still talk to stay from for my college right because they
我就像兩個我仍然在談論我的大學的人，因為他們
She was like there going to be a bad influence since they Gon Party so much or whatever like that but they are some of the smartest wise
她覺得會有不好的影響，因為他們會參加這麼多或類似的派對，但他們是一些最聰明的人
People I've met in my entire life inside it's like you can't really judge somebody by like money or
我一生中遇到的人就像你不能用金錢或金錢來判斷一個人
Or like a Luxor to all that Cyprus up there answer so I don't know I think it's traditional
或者像盧克索一樣回答所有塞浦路斯人，所以我不知道我認為這是傳統的
Like that it's super annoying but you guys get what I mean by you know those
就像那樣，這很煩人，但你們明白我的意思，你知道那些
To judge a person so quickly like that
這麼快就判斷一個人
It's just so artificial I don't like that
太人工了，我不喜歡
Thanks
謝謝
My family can live in peace
我的家人可以安居樂業
Oh yeah
哦耶
Don't get what's so good about the StoryBots
不要了解 StoryBots 的優點
Here you go
幹得好
Okay bye thanks for the pinwheel nerd
好的，謝謝你的風車書呆子
Yeah there's a family of Demon Slayer is my kind of people
是的，有一個惡魔殺手的家庭是我的那種人
Where'd you like to go yourselves that you're a bad influence trust me I feel like I was also
你自己想去哪裡你是個壞影響相信我我覺得我也是
One of those kids that parents moved in like don't hang out with shell tall he's a bad influence he curses
父母搬進來的那些孩子中的一個不喜歡高高在上的孩子，他詛咒他是一個壞影響
So much he he's off now you like stuck in trouble and all that stuff I like
這麼多他他現在離開了你喜歡陷入困境和所有我喜歡的東西
Y'all f*** you you would want to but you know I just think their moms are jealous because they can't be my friend
你們都f ***你會想要，但你知道我只是覺得他們的媽媽嫉妒，因為他們不能成為我的朋友
That's why I told myself when I was younger
這就是為什麼我在年輕的時候告訴自己
Connie's house okay
康妮家還行
I'm about to okay I was kind of a Rowdy boy when I was younger like I didn't have much self-control
我會好起來的 我年輕的時候有點像一個吵鬧的男孩，好像我沒有太多的自製力
I remember in kindergarten and saw first grade I was I had like a lot of
我記得在幼兒園的時候，看到一年級的時候我有很多
Write-ups on my calendar so how it works is that up
寫在我的日曆上，所以它的工作原理就是這樣
Pause real quick
暫停真快
She know I don't need to pause
她知道我不需要停頓
Docking kindergarten I used to have a this calendar or my teachers would write sound like notes
對接幼兒園我曾經有這個日曆，否則我的老師會寫出像筆記一樣的聲音
For the day if I was like a good if I was like a behaved well right it would put a sticker on the day that I
如果我表現得很好，如果我表現得很好，那一天我會在那天貼上貼紙
Did really well and then other days they would have like a a red mark that I did really badly right
做得非常好，然後其他日子他們會喜歡一個紅色標記，我做得非常糟糕
And then most of the time I had a lot of red marks because I haven't had a problem with self-control I was really like rowdy
然後大部分時間我有很多紅色標記因為我沒有自製力問題我真的很喜歡吵鬧
I like to cause trouble I like seeing you know
我喜歡惹麻煩我喜歡看到你知道
Pick fights I guess they're like you know I don't know
選擇打架我猜他們就像你知道我不知道
Misbehave I was I was a big mistake Dave
行為不端，我是一個大錯誤戴夫
Favor
青睞
I recall it
我記得
I think I've mellowed out after middle school though
不過我想我中學畢業後就變得成熟了
Bad boy I used to be a fat boy
壞男孩 我曾經是個胖男孩
Sometimes I still am
有時候我還是
Hey how's it going
嘿 怎麼樣
I just pulling weeds
我只是拔草
This place looks like a mess
這個地方看起來很亂
I agree
我同意
This isn't even my place
這甚至不是我的地方
Then who are you
那你是誰
I'm just a random guy hired by the guy who lives here
我只是一個被住在這裡的人僱傭的隨機人
I keep getting complaints though
我不斷收到投訴
I were to slowly say
我要慢慢說
Why don't you just not Nazi what then
你為什麼不只是不納粹呢？
They pay me well
他們付給我錢
How much
多少錢
100-yen an hour
100日元一小時
They pay me while 100-yen an hour
他們付給我一小時 100 日元
White
白色的
Old man not all Gees on your getting ripped off
老頭子，不是所有的人都對你被扯掉了
That's not that's not
那不是 那不是
Good pay is it I'm not crazy maybe there's a translation there's no way
好薪是不是我沒瘋也許有翻譯沒辦法
Ausar 100-yen an hour
Ausar 100 日元一小時
Damn girl
該死的女孩
That's like below minimum wage right
這就像低於最低工資的權利
Okay
好的
Well anyway
不管怎樣
I want to get my job done fast
我想快速完成我的工作
I have something for you if you bring me something that can make my life easier
如果你給我帶來一些可以讓我的生活更輕鬆的東西，我有東西要給你
Something that can make your life easier
可以讓你的生活更輕鬆的東西
Chipotle sweets out
Chipotle糖果出來
Was he doing out there in the night I don't know that's also back for his back isn't it
他晚上在外面做嗎？我不知道那也是為了他的背，不是嗎
Wrong house wrong house what
錯誤的房子錯誤的房子是什麼
Whose house is this then
那這是誰的房子
Wait isn't this Connors house doors, is house
等等，這不是康納斯家的門，是家
Over here
這邊
He's probably dead you mean the old man I won't be surprised either has also the wrong house
他可能已經死了你的意思是那個老人我也不會感到驚訝也有錯誤的房子
Bro
兄弟
He's probably desperate for money yeah I feel like a lot of places do you have an issue of like you know the
他可能急需錢，是的，我覺得很多地方都有問題，就像你知道的那樣
Old people population in like
老年人口
Dumb
啞的
Making money in
在裡面賺錢
Being homeless and stuff and I feel feels bad
無家可歸之類的，我感覺很糟糕
I know it's an issue in Korea right
我知道這是韓國的問題
Kind of reminds me of that
有點讓我想起了
Like people are now desperate for money and they got to make a deal with what they can
就像人們現在迫切需要錢，他們必須盡其所能達成交易
That's how my parents are used to be
這就是我父母的習慣
You like that I don't want to be I don't want to be
你喜歡我不想成為 我不想成為
You know
你懂的
Or see anybody in my family that saw saw freeze like that it'll just make me sad
或者看到我家裡的任何人看到這樣的凍結只會讓我難過
I think that's one of my fears actually in life I think a lot of people have that fear just being like a you know living on the streets
我認為這實際上是我生活中的恐懼之一
Being cold without a bed
沒有床就冷
I know like home-cooked meals that's really sad
我知道像家常飯菜那樣真的很難過
No one's home
沒人在家
Are my parents from my parents actually moved over to the United States
我的父母是否真的從我父母搬到了美國
From from Vietnam
來自越南
So they they drew up with very little and Zoe and I worked really hard 200
所以他們草擬了很少的東西，佐伊和我真的很努力 200
Yeah I saw me going out with my parents is really rough it wasn't easy
是的，我看到我和父母出去真的很艱難，不容易
Ansel
安塞爾
It was really really a sucky
這真的很糟糕
Early on in life by. Hey I feel like we're doing a lot better now
早年靠。嘿，我覺得我們現在做得好多了
I think
我想
You guys want
你們想要
Nice convincing
好有說服力
Do you happen to know anything about it
你碰巧知道什麼嗎
So troubled by it
為之煩惱
No idea
不知道
Play my fun something in the house
在家裡玩我有趣的東西
Please come pick a lock
請來開鎖
Dude look like he was going to lawnmower me into the crown okay
伙計看起來他要把我割草到皇冠上好嗎
Sure I'll follow you old man
我當然會跟著你老頭
Can I speak that I know I can't really
我能說我知道我不能說嗎
I'm like one of those children that didn't really learn the their native language of all-time like
我就像那些沒有真正學習過他們的母語的孩子之一
Not very Americanized bro
不是很美國化的兄弟
I'm sure I'm trying to learn like there's so many other languages I want to learn bro you just phased into the door like it was
我確定我正在努力學習，就像我想學習很多其他語言一樣，兄弟，你只是像以前一樣步入大門
Nothing your radical as hell
沒有什麼是你的激進分子
Holyshit can I do that
我能做到嗎
So yeah
嗯是的
I really there's a lot languages I want to learn because like I said like I said before I love learning languages
我真的有很多我想學習的語言，因為就像我之前說過的那樣，我喜歡學習語言
Annoys
煩人
I want to learn make sure learning Vietnamese and then make sure they're not Japanese Chinese Korean
我想學習確保學習越南語，然後確保他們不是日本人中國人韓國人
There's also think the learning
還有想學
More Spanish should be fun series since I've already like taking some classes on that now when I was younger and the
更多西班牙語應該是有趣的系列，因為我現在已經喜歡上一些關於這方面的課程，當時我還年輕，
And I'll be able to communicate more people is like a very beautiful thing right
而且我能和更多的人交流就像是一件很美好的事情對吧
Because not everybody knows English like not everybody understands me and I'm pretty sure there's a lot of people watching me that's on
因為不是每個人都懂英語，就像不是每個人都懂我一樣，我很確定有很多人在看我
Understand what I'm saying right now but they still watch me but thank you guys for watching me
明白我現在在說什麼，但他們仍然看著我，但謝謝你們看著我
Might it be really wonderful for me to properly communicate with people like that in the future so you know
以後能和這樣的人好好交流，對我來說真的很棒嗎？所以你知道嗎？
I don't leave anyone out there like you know I can be
我不會像你知道的那樣把任何人留在外面
Not
不是
Monolingual f*****
單語f*****
Who are you
你是誰
2005 you look really hot
2005 你看起來真熱
Hotboii
火鍋
The chicken
雞
Slot
投幣口
This milk
這奶
The sock on his room or just saw the dad's room
他房間裡的襪子或剛剛看到爸爸的房間
Yeah he's a fine but yeah this looks like a character I would a shrimp over
是的，他很好，但是是的，這看起來像是一個我會喜歡的角色
Pretty sure
很確定
Remind me of YouTuber honestly
老實說，讓我想起 YouTuber
Anytime I see her
每次見到她
Hey
嘿
Chinese Destroyer won't open
中國驅逐艦打不開
Do you have the key for it
你有它的鑰匙嗎
No I don't
不，我沒有
Well I remember, I would always hiding behind some furniture when she was little
嗯，我記得，她小的時候我總是躲在一些家具後面
But that was when she was when she was a child
但那是她小時候
Thanks for the snack stork
謝謝你的點心鸛
Cancer on the TV
電視上的癌症
I got Snackeez
我有 Snackeez
I'll newspaper article number to write
我會報文號寫
Is only read the the first one it was a suicide the single mother agrees a police investigation
只看過第一個是自殺單親媽媽同意警方調查
The curse all the cause of death of pacu me Supple soldiers old found in the Oil City it prefecture on
詛咒所有pacu me的死因，在它縣的油城發現的老兵
September 14th was infected suicide a mother who has been working hard as single mother
9月14日被感染自殺 一位一直在努力做單親媽媽的媽媽
What's in Sears
西爾斯有什麼
Is that my daughter
那是我女兒嗎
This is talking about my daughter right
這是在說我女兒吧
Because I'm also stoppel
因為我也是stoppel
I think
我想
We don't doing
我們不做
Her name is subtle or is like llamado softball right or something
她的名字很微妙，或者就像美洲駝壘球一樣
Or maybe I'm thinking of it incorrectly
或者我想錯了
One of these days you guys are going to you guys are going to regret doing that
有一天你們要去你們會後悔這樣做
Fordham Galaxy a f*** out of here
福特漢姆銀河f***離開這裡
But I I like I said before
但是我就像我之前說的
Growing up was not easy for my parents and we have to be frugal with everything that's why I like these days there
長大對我的父母來說並不容易，我們必須節儉一切，這就是我喜歡這些日子的原因
Are very all my parents are you guys
我的父母都是你們嗎
Okay but like I said I'm going up there
好的，但就像我說的我要去那裡
Spendless
花費少一點
Enzo Sav-Mor mentality finish everything on your plate you know
Enzo Sav-Mor 的心態完成你所知道的一切
Did just how it is when you grow up like with not much yeah those those habits
當你長大的時候是怎樣的，是的，那些習慣不多
Answer Preserve
答案保留
As much as he can and not waste money
盡量不浪費錢
Police officer
警官
Hello
你好
Why were the police officer go
警察怎麼跑了
Guys
伙計們
Play why people sing yeah yeah
播放為什麼人們唱歌是啊是啊
Hours all the police or the police officer
小時所有警察或警察
You Blended in with the grass
你與草融為一體
Would you like to go
你想去嗎
I think we should go to music he's house
我想我們應該去他家聽音樂
Again because
又是因為
Was it there's a dog there right
那裡有隻狗嗎
Oh no
不好了
You should bring the snacks to
你應該把零食帶到
Police station
警察局
Hey you want some snacks
嘿，你想吃點零食
Are you okay
你還好嗎
Not really
並不真地
What happened
發生了什麼
I don't know I just very tired
我不知道我只是很累
I'm so tired I don't even want to look at you
累到不想看你
Thing is
事情是
Ground bison booze
地面野牛酒
Stores around here close early
附近的商店早早關門
So if you and your police friends want me to go away
所以如果你和你的警察朋友想讓我離開
Please bring me a cold one
請給我來一份冷的
Thanks
謝謝
I mean why would we want you to go away sir
我的意思是我們為什麼要你離開先生
You're very happy
你很開心
For some reason
因為某些原因
Very very happy
很高興
That's really want to scare me off the dicks
這真的是想把我嚇跑
What's happening on Save y'all
Save y'all 上發生了什麼
I guess he doesn't want to snack he's are you sure you don't want the Snackeez
我猜他不想吃零食他是你確定你不想要Snackeez
Yeah he wants beer alright so you don't want snacks
是的，他想要啤酒，所以你不想要零食
Maybe the child with a dog food right
也許孩子吃狗糧吧
Yeah maybe I'll we give actual food to the child's
是的，也許我會給孩子真正的食物
Instead they don't eat dog food. Don't eat that that's not fair that's not for young girls
相反，他們不吃狗糧。不要吃 那不公平 不適合年輕女孩
Is supposed to eat healthy and snot cup noodles
應該吃健康的鼻涕杯麵
Ambler giving her snacks like isn't any much better
安布勒給她的零食也好不到哪裡去
Need to talk to your holding
需要與您的控股公司交談
If you'd like
如果你願意
You changed for these snacks
你換了這些零食
Okay
好的
Thank you
謝謝
Hey
嘿
By the way
順便一提
How's your grandma around
你奶奶在附近怎麼樣
In or she won
在或她贏了
We
我們
We don't have a grandma
我們沒有奶奶
Wait who's that lady outside
等等，外面那個女人是誰
Beautiful puzzle lady outside
外面美麗的拼圖女士
Okay
好的
Hello
你好
What's that
那是什麼
I'm about I'm this close I'm disgusted fist-fighting my chart
我是關於我離我這麼近我很反感我的圖表
You guys already ice think I'm so easy to scare
你們都已經冰了 覺得我很容易被嚇到
You think I'm so f****** easy to scare
你以為我f******很容易被嚇到
Cuz you're right I have
因為你是對的我有
Okay well enjoy your snacks I guess don't
好吧，好好享受你的零食吧，我猜不
Tie up your parents come home don't talk to any old ladies outside if you see any
把你父母綁起來回家不要和外面的老太太說話，如果你看到任何
AUC old lady around here
AUC老太太在這
No okay
不可以
I'm pretty sure I also saw its 1 here to help your old man yeah this thing
我很確定我在這裡也看到了它的 1 來幫助你的老人，是的，這個東西
Gary Cal you have a safe
加里卡爾你有一個保險箱
Or is this called was it called again I cashier
或者這叫它又叫我收銀員
Something siwak pick up the grass with right a sickle yeah that's what it's called a sickle
有東西 siwak 用鐮刀撿草
That's a pretty cool name
這是一個很酷的名字
Alright let's go to all
好吧，讓我們去所有
Whose house again, his house
又是誰的房子，他的房子
No school music is house first
沒有學校音樂是房子第一
And then we can
然後我們可以
Give the dog food give the dog food to the dog and then we'll see what the dog
給狗糧把狗糧給狗，然後我們看看狗吃什麼
Maybe he'll be our friend
也許他會成為我們的朋友
I happen to know he's going to give us something something
我碰巧知道他會給我們一些東西
What a dog doing it all go
什麼狗做這一切去
Poggers
波格斯
Where you going bro
兄弟你要去哪裡
Wait where are we going I'm confused now
等等我們要去哪裡我現在很困惑
Is very excited it's a big dog
很興奮這是一條大狗
Okay okay no do bad
好吧好吧不做壞事
Bad shot you guys are bad alright
打得不好你們都不好
Oh thanks for the food
哦，謝謝你的食物
Wait
等待
Who's that
那是誰
That wasn't a dog
那不是狗
I was not a dog
我不是狗
Thanks for the food and he just runs off
謝謝你的食物，他就跑了
I can open it without a key of course we don't have the keys to open it and f***
我可以不用鑰匙打開它當然我們沒有鑰匙可以打開它，f ***
We got your data by an old man no
我們從一個老人那裡得到了你的數據
Wow alright okay
哇好的好的
I kind of sucks well
我有點爛
I haven't been down here yet I'm go check what's down here yeah
我還沒來過這裡我要去看看這裡有什麼是的
Say who's the neighborhood for
說出誰是鄰居
Huh how's the scariest thing yet the I mean I mean I will be free fries out
嗯，最可怕的事情是什麼？我的意思是我的意思是我會免費薯條
If father dog turned into a human right and then like an old man and just like waddled off
如果父親狗變成了人權然後像個老人一樣蹣跚而行
The dog food I don't know
我不知道的狗糧
Okay I was going to Connie's house
好吧，我要去康妮家
Oh yeah we can give the sickle to the old man right
哦，是的，我們可以把鐮刀給老人吧
And he'll give us something probably
他可能會給我們一些東西
That was weird
那很奇怪
House of really weird that's okay
房子真的很奇怪沒關係
Yes
是的
Hey Straw Hat bro
嘿草帽哥
Please don't take 100-yen an hour that's proof that's not very pog
請不要一小時拿 100 日元，這證明這不是很糟糕
Thanks
謝謝
Now I can live
現在我可以生活了
I don't have any money but
我沒有錢但是
Just swipe down on the ground
只需在地面上向下滑動
Should come in handy
應該派上用場
Trust me
相信我
But now I can live what does that mean
But now I can live it 是什麼意思
And what does that mean
那是什麼意思
Zalika
扎莉卡
Are you also that I feel like he's not real either something something about this
你是不是也覺得他不是真的
Seems like
似乎
Hey dude is off
嘿哥們下班了
Pretty
漂亮
Riyadh not he's not all there either
利雅得不是他也不在那裡
Okay now what
好的，現在什麼
How do I get the key in the drawer
怎麼拿到抽屜裡的鑰匙
You said alright the dad said that there was
你說好吧，爸爸說有
There is a Mackie hidden behind like some furniture maybe I look behind furniture
有一個 Mackie 像一些家具一樣藏在後面，也許我在家具後面看
Upstairs
樓上
Donation
捐款
Good evening for a good morning guys again
晚上好，再次祝大家早安
Good day
再會
Vanilla sauce what's wrong with the windmill it's going to come in handy they said
香草醬風車有什麼問題他們說會派上用場的
I don't know what your name is vital you look really called you have a mole under your eye wow you look
我不知道你的名字很重要你看起來真的叫你眼睛下面有痣哇你看起來
Just became like
剛變得像
20 times hotter
熱20倍
Crazy dial
瘋狂撥號
Alright
好的
Maybe there is a Bonafide Rover here
也許這裡有一輛真正的流浪者
You know if you need anything
你知道如果你需要什麼
Why can't I go inside this area
為什麼我不能進入這個區域
Door is locked
門被鎖上了
I think here
我覺得這裡
Fine Furniture
精美家具
Guys
伙計們
Or is he I don't know where to find the
還是他我不知道在哪裡可以找到
Chucky
查基
Money
錢
They just watch me as I walk around yeah I don't know where to find the the f****** the f****** key
他們只是看著我走來走去，是的，我不知道在哪裡可以找到 f****** f****** 鍵
Okay
好的
Huh
呵呵
Where do I go it's all I have in my inventory Cy
我要去哪裡，這就是我的庫存中的全部 Cy
Now I don't I just have my windows
現在我不只是有我的窗戶
Maybe it's outside
也許它在外面
Maybe it's outside I'll take a look outside
也許在外面，我去外面看看
If it's in her room
如果在她的房間裡
Find a house yet
還沒找到房子
You might have just I've just saw giving us the clue
你可能只是我剛剛看到給我們提供了線索
Needed
需要
And no there's nothing back here
不，這裡什麼都沒有
Is there a second floor there's a second floor
有二樓嗎 有二樓
I don't think
我不認為
Guys
伙計們
Okay you guys have the green lights a backseat for this game by the way I'm a I'm not sure what to do now
好吧，你們已經為這場比賽開了綠燈，順便說一句，我不知道現在該怎麼辦
I can't give it to the kid I don't think that's where I'm supposed to do
我不能把它給孩子 我不認為那是我應該做的
Jessica Bassman
傑西卡·巴斯曼
Yeah let me go upstairs I think.
是的，讓我上樓吧，我想。
My are my help
我是我的幫助
Look in the room a little bit more
多看看房間
Nope
沒有
That's not it
不是這個
Look at the poster again for inspiration lochia
再看海報靈感惡露
A key icon has house that's invisible
一個鑰匙圖標有一個不可見的房子
At the key that's invisible lights
關鍵是看不見的燈
There's an invisible key
有一把看不見的鑰匙
How am I supposed to find an invisible key
我應該如何找到看不見的鑰匙
What's what do you mean
你是什麼意思
Why are you talkin about
你為什麼在談論
That is start clicking everything
那就是開始點擊一切
Table
桌子
Drawers
抽屜
TV is off of the TV
電視已關閉
No
不
Oh
哦
Wow
哇
That's that's f******
這就是f******
Dad
爸爸
Where did Dad go
爸爸去哪兒了
Dude everybody's dead
哥們都死了
Dad
爸爸
Sorry
對不起
Where the f*** is that girl
那個女孩在哪裡
Oh
哦
Hey
嘿
What is he saying
他在說什麼
What did that say can somebody Translate.
有人能翻譯那句話是什麼意思。
Yahoo always at say
雅虎總是在說
Somebody
某人
Give me a give me an answer I'm very confused
給我一個答案 我很困惑
They missed translated
他們錯過了翻譯
They mistranslated he's possessed
他們誤譯了他被附身了
Is possess
是擁有
What
什麼
I don't get it either
我也不明白
There is no meeting
沒有會議
Although there is no meaning it's just gibberish
雖然沒有意義，但只是胡言亂語
It's just random all I think he's just like it's just gone
這只是隨機的，我認為他就像它剛剛消失一樣
Bunch of gargle okay
一堆漱口水還行
Alright done
好的完成
Well you have fun being possessed.
好吧，你有樂趣被附身。
I guess also thank you for the hype-train again guys thanks for the donation
我想也感謝你們的炒作，再次感謝你們的捐贈
They were fighting again
他們又吵架了
Are yelling at each other and I can't sleep
互相大喊大叫，我睡不著
That was mad about what Mommy for dinner
媽媽對晚餐吃什麼很生氣
Statistical
統計
Again
再次
I'm also getting tired
我也越來越累
That was upset about Mom buying a back online
媽媽在網上買回來讓我很不高興
Why can't you reward herself once in awhile
為什麼不能偶爾獎勵一下自己
See this is what I'm talking about my my parents are upset when I like like to treat myself sometimes right
看到這就是我在說的我的父母很不高興當我喜歡善待自己有時是對的
I like sometimes I'm like I spend $10 on the on the snack or like maybe by myself a
我喜歡有時我喜歡在零食上花 10 美元，或者喜歡自己一個人吃
And my mom is like
我媽媽就像
Shelter stop spending so much money on this job I'm like but I made it myself
庇護所 不要在我喜歡的工作上花這麼多錢，但我自己做的
Venza
文扎
I thought I want to treat myself mom
我以為我想善待自己 媽媽
You know
你懂的
I don't get it I just it's very stupid it's okay to treat yourself guys alright
我不明白我只是這很愚蠢，請善待自己沒關係，伙計們
Remember
記住
Never says anything otherwise you should remember it just do even more
永遠不要說什麼，否則你應該記住它只是做得更多
Even more is an Asian thing yeah I guess it is an Asian thing
甚至更多是亞洲的東西，是的，我想這是亞洲的東西
Or an ethnic thing
或者民族的東西
Okay
好的
Mom has allowed on this time around
媽媽允許這次
I've been drinking Riesling is wasting money for god-knows-what
我一直在喝雷司令是在浪費錢天知道什麼
Inside me some excuse about how it's not fun coming back home and Health Center space
在我內心深處，有一些藉口說回家和健康中心空間不好玩
What is going on
到底是怎麼回事
Today's my birthday and now they're my parents remember it
今天是我的生日，現在他們是我的父母，記得
Not even a single word of Celebration
連一個慶祝的詞都沒有
Thing is always
事情總是
I'm getting sick of it
我厭倦了
Thinking is that they were angry because my failing grades
想著他們生氣是因為我的成績不及格
That's been on the steady decline I still can pass
那一直在穩步下降我仍然可以通過
I'm just below the average
我只是低於平均水平
All I want is a reason to fight and complain about each other
我想要的只是一個互相爭吵和抱怨的理由
So that really sucked like
所以這真的很糟糕
I would not like you know
我不想讓你知道
Forgetting someone's birthday
忘記某人的生日
And that's something to celebrate
這是值得慶祝的事情
I feel you kid I feel you
我感覺到你的孩子我感覺到你
Never gets tired of fighting
永遠不會厭倦戰鬥
I feel as if I don't have a home
感覺好像沒有家
I start to lock myself up in my room every time one of them comes back
每當他們中的一個人回來時，我就開始把自己鎖在房間裡
I want to hear their voices anymore
我想再聽到他們的聲音
Every night I wish my life was
每晚我都希望我的生活是
Little happier
開心一點
Just a little is fine
一點點就好
Today's fight with something else
今天和別的東西打架
I overheard something I shouldn't have
我無意中聽到了一些我不應該聽到的東西
They said they wouldn't be here together if I weren't born
他們說如果我沒有出生他們就不會在一起
He also said that I was born before they married
他還說我是在他們結婚之前出生的
I'm sure that's what they said
我確定他們是這麼說的
Come they never talked to me about it
來吧，他們從來沒有和我談過這件事
I feel unwanted
我覺得不受歡迎
I should exist
我應該存在
I don't feel right to be in this world
我覺得在這個世界上不合適
I want to hide to keep on a piece of furniture again but
我想躲起來再繼續做一件家具，但是
I didn't set my color this time
這次我沒有設置顏色
Just so I don't forget
只是為了不忘記
Write this down
寫下來
Biscuits
餅乾
Music you said that I should let the dog handle the hiding but
音樂你說我應該讓狗處理隱藏但
Watch the dog
看狗
Why trust a dog
為什麼要相信狗
Watches with dogs are so nice in
帶狗的手錶很好看
3rd gear fluffy in
3檔蓬鬆
Loyal
忠誠
I got the key
我拿到鑰匙了
A child has gone through some s*** bro
一個孩子經歷了一些他媽的兄弟
Now I'm scared about what's going to happen to the dad are you still okay
現在我很害怕爸爸會發生什麼你還好嗎
Okay goodbye
好的，再見
I just don't want to be in the house anymore
我只是不想再呆在家裡
Yeah I really don't want to be there anymore all that. Dude scares me
是的，我真的不想再在那裡了。哥嚇死我了
I like to go
我喜歡去
I want to go to music's because that's where the box was right
我想去聽音樂，因為那是盒子對的地方
Here's the thing I'm
這就是我的東西
Oh my God the police officers scared me I turned around I forgot he was there
Oh my God 警察嚇到我了我轉身我忘了他在那裡
I don't want to wait till you see the way he looks at you too it's just so fun
我不想等到你也看到他看你的樣子這太有趣了
Walking scary like he's just standing there
走路嚇人，就像他只是站在那裡一樣
Is in his face just like how to Shadow to it like he's going to creep up on me
在他的臉上就像是如何對它產生陰影，就像他要爬到我身上一樣
Sorry
對不起
Sorry my bad guys
對不起我的壞人
Papa police officer gun weird it's alright
爸爸警察槍很奇怪沒關係
Arthur spooking Soundview though
雖然亞瑟嚇壞了 Soundview
Can open it without a key I have a key right here
不用鑰匙也能打開 我這裡有鑰匙
I've become the computer password now okay
我已經變成電腦密碼了
Saginaw bring it over to what's-his-face
Saginaw 把它帶到什麼是他的臉
Co-op apply on her computer
在她的電腦上申請合作社
The music is computer
音樂是電腦
Cancel
取消
A big
一個大的
Donation for the gift Subs welcome hope you have a great day and thank you for the all the bitties
捐贈禮物 Subs 歡迎希望你有一個美好的一天，並感謝你的所有點點滴滴
Earlier
早些時候
Thank you for all the resolves everybody and Zoe
謝謝大家和佐伊的所有決心
Summary thank you for the donation
摘要 感謝您的捐贈
You say once more shirt
你再說一遍襯衫
The biddies that yeah bittys like you know you when you are cheer bits twitch bits
當你歡呼時，像你這樣的小傢伙們都知道你
YouTube doesn't have b w which has it
YouTube 沒有 bw 有它
I gained access to the computer what should I do you the email
我可以訪問計算機我該怎麼辦你的電子郵件
The email says musically
電子郵件以音樂的方式說
Are you broke up with your boyfriend are you okay
你和你男朋友分手了嗎 你還好嗎
Remember you would tell me how much you love him
記住你會告訴我你有多愛他
I'm a little worried
我有點擔心
Winky face
眨眼的臉
Wait is that a winky face I can't sell
等等，那是一張我賣不出去的眨眼臉
Talk to me anytime
隨時跟我說話
I would gladly help you out
我很樂意幫助你
The worried face
擔心的臉
I saw soccer
我看過足球
Shrinks chat box says
縮小聊天框說
Musically don't forget to bring it
音樂上別忘了帶上它
I know
我知道
Going to the park right
去公園右邊
Akiko
明子
Don't be late
不要遲到
Play for white
為白色而戰
Skin-walker
皮膚行者
Guys
伙計們
B u
卜
Y'all like I
你們都喜歡我
I don't know what to do with the right though the beer hey let's go back to the police station
我不知道怎麼處理權利雖然啤酒嘿讓我們回警察局
Hey old man
嘿老頭
Auntie son
兒子阿姨
Is your beer
你的啤酒是
How do I give it to you
我怎麼給你
Oh Lord
我的天
Hallelujah
哈利路亞
You are my hero
你是我的英雄
Here please take this
請收下這個
I'm sure this is what you were looking for
我確定這就是你要找的
Thank you so much
太感謝了
What
什麼
Haha
哈哈
Omaha
奧馬哈
Sir
先生
Play why he run like that
玩他為什麼那樣跑
The f*** the f*** shot okay
該死的，該死的，還可以
Well I mean it's kind of weird
我的意思是這有點奇怪
Whatever
任何
All the cat
所有的貓
Why are you running
你為何跑
Mwah mwah mwah
嗚嗚嗚嗚
Okay
好的
That is a really cute cat though
雖然那是一隻非常可愛的貓
Is like a missing cat poster or something
就像一張失踪的貓海報什麼的
Is it is amazing composter or is it like supposed to be ar
它是驚人的堆肥機還是它應該是 ar
Is it supposed to be something just like hey look at my cat
是不是應該像嘿看看我的貓一樣
Now some people do that right they just
現在有些人這樣做是對的，他們只是
Just put posters up in his like
把海報貼在他喜歡的地方
Has pictures of their cats just a show
有他們的貓的照片只是一個節目
The new dogs
新的狗
I go to the park
我去公園
Around a little bit more let me save
多一點讓我省錢
Airygal poggers
艾里加波格
Are you going to park
你要停車嗎
Let's hurry before it's too late okay or am I hurting about
讓我們在為時已晚之前快點好嗎
Spooky time right yacht spooky time I don't know what's at the park and bought anticipate
幽靈般的時間正確的遊艇幽靈般的時間我不知道公園裡有什麼並買了期待
Who are you who is that
你是誰
Who is that
那是誰
Ono Ono
小野小野
I don't want to f*** with her I do whoever-you-are I'm so sorry
我不想和她做愛我不管你是誰我很抱歉
Boys get away from me she's fast
男孩們離我遠點 她很快
She still coming
她還來
Hello
你好
Where she go
她去哪裡
Don't Turn back I I kind of want to look around the area around up there
Don't Turn back II 有點想環顧四周
Play maybe I can go on to the playground now I can't
玩也許我可以去操場現在我不能
There's somebody looking up there, what to do though
有人在上面看，怎麼辦
Hey kid are you okay kid
嘿孩子你還好嗎孩子
The vending machines is raining over here this is weird
這裡的自動售貨機正在下雨，這很奇怪
It is not okay yeah it doesn't look like it
不行，是的，看起來不像
I hope that's the the kid that were looking for
我希望那是正在尋找的孩子
I don't like going to parks at night either
我也不喜歡晚上去公園
Unless you have a friend go go with a friend I've seen plenty
除非你有朋友和我見過很多的朋友一起去
Any of those out doujins all that were whatever it's like out was it called no like
那些出道的同人中的任何一個，無論它是什麼樣的，都被稱為不喜歡
No like those
不像那些
It's like those scenarios right those scenarios are it's like a
就像那些場景一樣，那些場景就像是
You know you walk a doll is like somebody that's like dog your unit yeah I got nights I'm through a park
你知道你走路一個娃娃就像一個像狗你的單位是的我有夜晚我穿過一個公園
And then it's like public embarrassment cyber thing I've seen those before pretty funny
然後就像公共尷尬的網絡事情我以前見過的很有趣
I don't know what the hell I know what it's called though
我不知道到底是什麼我知道它叫什麼
Humiliation like a humiliation King
像屈辱王一樣屈辱
I don't like this
我不喜歡這個
No nobody's coming after me
沒有人追我
Neither
兩者都不
And what happened to another creature that was chasing my ass
另一個追著我屁股的生物發生了什麼事
Gucci cologne
古馳古龍水
What was that about
那是關於什麼的
Damage
損害
Single Time Can't Behave none of you can behave
一次不能表現你們誰都不能表現
I take your rights away
我剝奪你的權利
This is Thursday she's not going to come back right show
這是星期四，她不會回來了
Look behind you know older they are hello children
往後看，你知道他們是你好孩子
Wait oh no I didn't I miss saw it
等等哦不，我沒有錯過看到它
What the f*** no
什麼他媽的沒有
Oh
哦
Why you push me in
為什麼你推我進去
I fainted and fell into the pond
我暈倒在池塘里
Luckily for the hussy rushed over and save me from drowning
幸運的是，笨蛋衝過來救了我免於溺水
I could save talk to me
我可以節省和我說話
Tonight I couldn't save anyone once again
今晚我無法再次拯救任何人
Not even one of them
甚至沒有一個
Termites doing
白蟻在做
For an entire week I locked myself up and send have the will to do anything
整整一個星期，我把自己關起來，並願意做任何事
Why would they do such a thing
他們為什麼會做這樣的事情
Neither reason for the suicide
自殺的原因都沒有
Resentment feel my heart
怨恨我心
I'm talking took his life
我說的是要了他的命
I try my best to look away from reality
我盡量遠離現實
Let's lose someone so close it's just unbearable
讓我們失去一個如此親密的人，這簡直無法忍受
I've never thought that this kind of thing would have
我從沒想過會有這種事情
Happened so near
發生得那麼近
Somewhere inside I wish it was someone's else's affair
在裡面的某個地方，我希望這是別人的事
Matter was not too big to not taking to my own hands
事情不是太大，不能不親自動手
That's why I want to help this time
這就是我這次想幫忙的原因
I can repeat the same thing
我可以重複同樣的事情
I can save them
我可以拯救他們
Oceanside locked up since the death attack me starts a wall up again
歐申賽德被鎖起來，因為死亡襲擊我又開始築牆了
Talk to Me Maybe Hawaiian today
今天跟我聊聊也許是夏威夷語
Facade
正面
But that moves us
但這讓我們感動
I will not be defeated
我不會被打敗
Alright carry the weight of three more
好吧，再背三個的重量
We cannot allow for their ends being vain
我們不能允許他們的目的是徒勞的
Never
絕不
Do not waste their death
不要浪費他們的死亡
Stand up
起來
What is the only option left for me
留給我的唯一選擇是什麼
I got the bad end
我得到了不好的結局
Oh yeah okay I got the achievement a bad ending okay
哦，是的，好吧，我得到了成就一個不好的結局，好吧
We're going to redo that
我們要重做
Biafra going to redo that part I think I might have missed something
Biafra 將重做那部分我想我可能錯過了一些東西
Probably had to do if those are windmills right
如果這些是風車，可能必須這樣做
I think I was supposed to put the windmills somewhere
我想我應該把風車放在某個地方
I'm not sure we're supposed to put it though I think it sucks
我不確定我們是否應該放它，儘管我認為它很爛
There's a shrine
有一個神社
It was Akiko is right
明子是對的
Yes I think it's a doggy goes okay sure
是的，我認為這是一隻小狗，肯定沒問題
Go over there on zod's put the windmills at The Shrine and I think
去那邊佐德把風車放在神社我想
That should help
那應該有幫助
Give it to the cat know I'm not supposed to give it to the kid guys are supposed to put it at
把它給貓知道我不應該把它給孩子們應該把它放在
Trine the kid doesn't have a need for the windmills
三位一體的孩子不需要風車
That the problem is like do I have all the windmills
問題是我有所有的風車嗎
Wish I do how are you it's supposed to be three
希望我做你好嗎它應該是三個
Zion all except for this part I'm going to redo it though
錫安除了這部分我要重做
I'm not I'm not satisfied
我不是我不滿意
Without ending
沒有結局
Only get the good one and see what the other good ones about again
只得到好的，然後再看看其他好的
You don't like tomorrow yes I am I'm going to go live in about 11 hours from now to 2
你不喜歡明天，是的，我要在大約 11 小時內直播到 2 點
Play unsolved on with you guys for a little bit for too long but want to try until dawn
和你們玩了太久沒有解決的問題，但想嘗試到天亮
See how it is
看看情況如何
Is it over no it's not over there's more
是不是結束了沒有它還沒有結束還有更多
We have a lot more incoming do not worry I'll pay you for the other B
我們還有很多來的別擔心我會為其他 B 付錢給你
Thank you thank you
謝謝謝謝
Oh yeah and I also saw you guys Crush
哦，是的，我還看到你們迷戀
China are you guys still thank you for supporting me
中國你們還支持我嗎
Xennials
Xennials
Alright
好的
Now here's what we're going to do sir we're going to go to Oculus
現在這是我們要做的，先生，我們要去 Oculus
What's on my starting tomorrow I'm going to be playing until dawn in 11 hours from now so that's at
明天開始我要玩什麼 我將在 11 小時後玩到黎明 所以那是在
8 snow that's at 9 a.m. my time but that's
我的時間是早上 9 點有 8 場雪，但那是
10 p.m. jst
晚上 10 點
So it's going to be like 10 p.m. for a
所以大概是晚上 10 點
Japan
日本
Fisher
費舍爾
It's night time for a lot of people over there
那邊很多人都是晚上
Hey here we go
嘿，我們走
Kure Joel
吳喬爾
Me to offer something
我提供一些東西
Yeah
是的
Seems to be satisfied
好像很滿意
That's it right
沒錯
31 Mills for the three children
三個孩子的 31 間磨坊
I don't know what that has to do with helping them out but I I mean we did it
我不知道這與幫助他們有什麼關係，但我的意思是我們做到了
I can going
我可以去
Get the good ending right
得到好的結局
I like to go park
我喜歡去公園
Not going to chase me this time right right bro
這次不會追我吧對吧兄弟
Hurry before it's too late
在為時已晚之前快點
Hey these different guys wait there's no the kid isn't on top of the
嘿，這些不同的傢伙等等，沒有孩子不在上面
Nothing anymore that's good right you succeeded
沒有什麼是好的，你成功了
Don't chasing me pug.
不要追我哈巴狗。
During the other game so far to another one very soon not right now but
在到目前為止的另一場比賽中，很快不是現在，而是另一場比賽
After we get the sending
在我們收到發送後
Sound Australian EST it's easy for us now because all remember guys they like say
聽起來澳大利亞 EST 現在對我們來說很容易，因為所有人都記得他們喜歡說的人
Savings America recently decided to keep things in EDT from now on right we're not going to be
Savings America 最近決定從現在開始將東西保留在 EDT 中，我們不會
Changing off like after this recent daylight savings or not moving the clocks anymore for summer
像在最近的夏令時之後改變，或者夏天不再移動時鐘
I think that's pretty cool so I don't have to like deal with what sunsets
我覺得這很酷，所以我不必喜歡處理日落
Like 5 p.m. or 4 p.m. in the 1/3 of kind of cool
就像下午 5 點或 4 點在 1/3 的那種很酷
So I don't know how that's going to work but I'm excited
所以我不知道這將如何運作，但我很興奮
Not to worry about Daylight Saving stuff anymore so do other people not to worry about it either since I know it's kind of
不再擔心夏令時的事情，所以其他人也不必擔心，因為我知道這有點
Confusing for the rest of the world is sometimes that we are now in
有時讓世界其他地方感到困惑的是，我們現在處於
Specially ett
特地
Because that who the f*** is this guy who's that huh
因為那他媽是誰
Why are you
你為什麼
Children
孩子們
It's an Enderman
這是一個末影人
That's an Enderman I want to play Minecraft again so that actually I might start up but my single-player Minecraft adventure
那是末影人，我想再次玩 Minecraft，這樣實際上我可能會開始，但我的單人 Minecraft 冒險
For myself again
再次為自己
I'm so glad I found them
我很高興我找到了他們
Took a breather and left the park
喘了口氣離開了公園
After the incident I decide to keep in touch with the girls Avella Oculus bully situation
事件發生後我決定與 Avella Oculus 欺負女孩的情況保持聯繫
I contacted the parents in the school it seems like they found evidence of bullying
我聯繫了學校的家長，他們似乎發現了欺凌的證據
Nice at the bowling ends entirely from there I also called 189 to report child neglect sunakhi owner
很好的保齡球完全從那裡結束我還打電話給 189 報告兒童忽視 sunakhi 所有者
Temporary custody things happen so suddenly how could go often tells me
臨時監護的事情發生的這麼突然怎麼會經常告訴我
Everything will be alright as long as you're here with me Supple son
只要你在我身邊，一切都會好起來的 柔軟的兒子
Parent seems to have officially divorced
父母似乎已經正式離婚
Cassidy is said to be the mother was worried about his feelings surprisingly clear
據說卡西迪被媽媽擔心了，他的心情出奇的清晰
She says that she still meet up for her dad often
她說她仍然經常為她爸爸見面
I'm happy to hear that that's for musically after the incident she decides
我很高興聽到這是她決定的事件後的音樂
Talk to say to you again strange letter was found to have been sent by her mother and so that's a shadow
再對你說 奇怪的信被發現是她媽媽寄來的 所以那是影子
That music is mother didn't want her to go out with C280 because she felt that he's not a good match with her decide they hang out
那個音樂是媽媽不想讓她和C280出去，因為她覺得他和她不配，決定他們出去玩
I want s'more known that there was a misunderstanding has been resolved now they're in the process of persuading her mother
我想讓更多人知道，有一個誤會已經解決，現在他們正在說服她媽媽
Be long before the mother accepts them I couldn't save my son talk to me then
早在母親接受他們之前，我無法挽救我的兒子然後跟我說話
He's no longer here how many times have I told myself. But the truth is he's
他已經不在了，我告訴自己多少次了。但事實是他
Then there was me all along thanks to talk to me I was able to find these people I'm certain
然後一直有我感謝與我交談我能夠找到這些人我確定
I'm any regrets since he died however
然而，自從他死後，我感到很遺憾
From Shawn Elder that he's living beside me and look up at the sky
來自Shawn Elder，他住在我身邊，仰望天空
Beautiful Starry Sky as a night of the incident mom you did your best
美麗的星空作為事發之夜媽媽你盡力了
Is your sleep voice somewhere
你的睡眠聲音在某個地方嗎
Is that
就是它
She's a bully detective and helped out these three children right she just basically help them
她是一個惡霸偵探，幫助了這三個孩子，她基本上只是幫助他們
I don't know how y'all doing I guess we just found them
我不知道你們過得怎麼樣 我想我們剛剛找到了他們
It's a bit confusing honestly but I found them
老實說，這有點令人困惑，但我找到了它們
They're in a better situation now there's no more bullying and do their own situations okay
他們現在的情況好多了
So alright cool
好酷
The black blob person was talking to me that was Alchemy holyshit really
那個黑點的人在跟我說話，那真是煉金術的天哪
Creepy man butt
令人毛骨悚然的男人屁股
That is it for a missing children we're going to move on to another game now
就是為了一個失踪的孩子，我們現在要進行另一場比賽
I'll closing shift made by the same creators
我將關閉由同一創作者製作的班次
Are we going to update that should say the closing shop now we exit
我們是否要更新應該說現在我們退出的關閉商店
Now where is
現在在哪裡
Cool boy new game I'm excited
酷男孩新遊戲我很興奮
Have you guys except for this one feel
除了這個，大家有沒有感覺
Nice white sauce
不錯的白醬
It was but that's why we're having two games play tonight
但這就是為什麼我們今晚要玩兩場比賽
We're doubling up
我們加倍
Here-we-go sawed-off
在這裡，我們去鋸掉
Let me adjust the volume since it might be a little loud for some of you guys alright
讓我調整一下音量，因為對你們中的一些人來說可能有點大，好吧
So how does that sound better
那怎麼聽起來更好
Salon now maybe I should like it just it so you guys can see Maya
現在沙龍，也許我應該喜歡它，這樣你們就可以看到瑪雅了
Hahaha
哈哈哈
My my hands
我的手
Like this right is IQ
喜歡這個權利就是智商
The coffee cup I'm going to be your Bruce tougher tonight y'all
咖啡杯，今晚我將成為你的布魯斯，你們所有人
It was a little weird but a bare with me
這有點奇怪，但對我來說是赤裸裸的
Alright
好的
KU game
KU遊戲
Earlier I had to adjust the settings so that's why there's a continue game file
早些時候我不得不調整設置，這就是為什麼有一個繼續遊戲文件
I like to adjust the options beforehand
我喜歡事先調整選項
Okay let's see
好的讓我們看看
Billy for work
比利工作
I should be on my car by now
我現在應該在我的車上
I wish we got like the
我希望我們能像
And I like put the toast in our mouths with the butter and jam in just
我喜歡把吐司和黃油和果醬一起放進嘴裡
You know run so it's work
你知道運行所以它的工作
Flowers
花卉
Plus painted nails sometimes I like to paint my nails black like this or like McDonald's in males block
加上塗指甲，有時我喜歡把指甲塗成黑色，或者像男性街區的麥當勞一樣
Nice
好的
How many other colors though
還有多少其他顏色
What is this what is this creature right here
這是什麼這是什么生物就在這裡
A rat
一隻老鼠
Is that alright yeah that's all I'm saying is that alright it looks like a rat
可以嗎，是的
No it's it's like a Pokemon
不，這就像口袋妖怪
Maybe
可能是
Chinchilla
龍貓
All of the chinchilla okay
所有的栗鼠都可以
Oops my bad
哎呀我的壞
Dynamic sense because you know
動態感，因為你知道
The game is chinchilla base
遊戲是龍貓基地
Like how we can see our legs in our arms found out
就像我們如何看到我們的雙腿被發現
Okay well lady we are a
好吧，女士，我們是
Hard-working
任勞任怨
Business lady
商務女士
All this is one of those is this like one of those tiny Apartments
所有這一切都是其中之一，就像那些小公寓之一
Like
喜歡
I've never been in one of these like we have a bed and we can climb up to and is like the bathroom and kitchen
我從來沒有去過其中一個，就像我們有一張床，我們可以爬上去，就像浴室和廚房
Probably and there's like
大概是這樣的
Living room area
客廳區域
Yeah it's a really tiny apartment I don't think I could live in one of these though it looks cozy by the same time like
是的，這是一個非常小的公寓，我不認為我可以住在其中一個，儘管它看起來很舒適，就像
Play Weezer
播放威澤
Oh here's your kitchen this is such a small kitchen though
哦，這是你的廚房，不過這廚房太小了
Are you going to do all your cooking
你會做所有的烹飪嗎
It's kind of cozy looking to be honest yeah like there's a bathroom
老實說，這是一種舒適的感覺，是的，就像有一個浴室
Is there a very tiny boil it works right
是否有一個非常小的煮沸它可以正常工作
I'm guessing this is like common in Japan
我猜這在日本很常見
I need more room though for like a my
我需要更多的空間來像我的
Like my computer and all that stuff so I don't think I could live in a place like this
像我的電腦和所有這些東西，所以我認為我不能住在這樣的地方
Do all
做所有
Leave apartment
離開公寓
Alright
好的
Oh boy I'm excited for this I've been anticipating this game for a while now like honestly when they
哦，男孩，我為此感到興奮我已經期待這場比賽有一段時間了，老實說，當他們
They announced that they were coming out with this and I saw like the concepts for the game I was really excited I couldn't wait for it to come out
他們宣布他們要推出這個，我看到了遊戲的概念，我真的很興奮，我迫不及待地想要它出來
Smiley out flashlight
笑臉手電筒
Is it morning time or is it like nighttime Frost right now it looks like it's off
現在是早上還是像夜間 Frost 現在看起來已經關閉了
Feels like it's some night time sounds so tired I always sound like
感覺就像是某個晚上的時間聽起來很累我總是聽起來像
I'm tired
我累了
Not somebody's phone I don't sound tired do I I mean I don't I'm not
不是某人的電話 我聽起來不累嗎 我的意思是我不 我不是
Tired right now I just I just talk like this
現在很累我只是這樣說話
Someone's phone okay while we picked up somebody's phone I guess all right
某人的電話沒問題，而我們拿起某人的電話我想沒問題
Also let me know if it's too dark maybe I can adjust the brightness a bit
也讓我知道如果它太暗也許我可以調整一下亮度
You guys can see better that's not too harsh on the eyes
你們可以看得更清楚，眼睛不會太刺眼
Oh yeah let me see if I can not let's not have
哦，是的，讓我看看我是否不能讓我們沒有
The VHS filter everything looks a little bit more clear I think that helps you
VHS 過濾器一切看起來都更清晰了，我認為這對你有幫助
Deja Salter does definitely make it look a little bit more
Deja Salter 確實讓它看起來多一點
Granny Centauri
半人馬座奶奶
Akari akari akari akari though
阿卡里阿卡里阿卡里阿卡里雖然
I'm a fan of it hipsy hippies C
我是 hipsy hippies C 的粉絲
What is like off brand Pepsi
百事可樂是什麼品牌
Names that are really funny alright I don't really like Pepsi
真的很有趣的名字好吧我不太喜歡百事可樂
I think if there is off but there's a soda that would drink is Coca-Cola but I don't really
我想如果有關閉但有一種可以喝的蘇打水是可口可樂但我真的不是
Minnesota that often anyways I don't really consider that these days to be honest and saw love sugar
明尼蘇達州，無論如何，我真的不認為這些天老實說，看到愛糖
But there's one asking it's Coca-Cola because I'm
但有人問是可口可樂，因為我是
Those are really nice and sweet and then Pepsi is just kind of like you know medicine medicinal tasting in the way
那些真的很好吃很甜，然後百事可樂就像你知道藥藥味一樣
Some people like that
有些人喜歡這樣
We are we supposed to get to work all right
我們應該好好上班
Is there driving around back here see if there's any secrets I like
有沒有開車回來看看有沒有我喜歡的秘密
I'll look around for secret sometimes
我有時會四處尋找秘密
Price of bass
貝斯的價格
I beg to that I've personally like a Whatsit
我請求我個人喜歡 Whatsit
Coca-Cola more how do I get inside my car hello
可口可樂更多我如何進入我的車你好
Hello what
你好什麼
Inside the car is on on my car guys looking for something what
車內在我的車上，伙計們正在尋找什麼東西
What's the guy looking for something
這傢伙在找什麼東西
Play oh oh hey there I didn't see you
Play oh oh hey there 我沒看到你
It was so dark I couldn't see you sir all my God I'm so sorry okay
天太黑了，我看不見你，先生，我的上帝，我很抱歉，好吧
Adjust my brightness obviously it's too dark
調整我的亮度顯然太暗了
Excuse me but you're kind of creepy excuse me
對不起，但你有點毛骨悚然，對不起
I don't like the looks of him
我不喜歡他的長相
Why is Boise look like that
為什麼博伊西看起來像這樣
Are you looking for something well I found this give me
你在找東西嗎我發現這個給我
Okay
好的
Oh I don't like you I don't like you at all
哦，我不喜歡你，我一點也不喜歡你
Does my car go to work y'all just go to work
我的車去上班嗎你們都去上班
I think we're at work already
我想我們已經開始工作了
Alright I don't talk to them I mean I was
好吧我不和他們說話我的意思是我是
I like giving people their possessions back right it's just
我喜歡把他們的財產歸還給人們，這只是
It's nice on all these are kind of cute I like this it's adorable
很好，所有這些都很可愛，我喜歡這個，很可愛
Who are you you are hot hello would you like to hold hands Wherever You Are
你是誰你很熱你好你想牽手無論你在哪裡
Hey hit me up
嘿打我
Like a bunch of YouTubers I don't know about
就像一群我不知道的YouTuber
A lot of times you look like a bunch of Ichiro's I just don't know about
很多時候你看起來像一群我只是不知道的一郎
Boys and hot girls
男孩和辣妹
Alright well don't who that weirdo was
好吧，不知道那個怪人是誰
Yes we can go into work now it looks like Starbucks, right reminds me of a star
是的，我們現在可以上班了，它看起來像星巴克，讓我想起了明星
Fox coloration everything sale squirrel bucks
狐狸著色一切出售松鼠雄鹿
All I mean Godzilla's coffee-based
我的意思是哥斯拉的咖啡基
Hello
你好
So quiet in here
這裡好安靜
Robin
羅賓
Pastry bags
糕點袋
Put away my stuff and talk to senpai
收起我的東西和前輩談談
Who's some pie
誰有餡餅
Have some pie
吃點餡餅
Yeah we're at for myself away all the private all you're my Senpai hello
是的，我們只為自己而去所有的私人你都是我的前輩你好
Over here
這邊
No trash
沒有垃圾
Are there yellow my phone my keys alright
有沒有黃色我的手機我的鑰匙好嗎
Coolio
庫里奧
Cold drinks it's real hot drinks it's real food tutorial
冷飲這是真正的熱飲這是真正的食物教程
Oh God
天啊
Wait
等待
I actually have to cook s***
我真的要做飯***
Sometime
有時
Sorry I'm late
對不起，我來晚了
Austin hot season 5 careful
奧斯汀炎熱的季節 5 小心
Stun guns tell the manager
電擊槍告訴經理
I am very sorry
我很抱歉
Be careful
當心
Be careful is not enough
小心是不夠的
Tell me you won't be late
告訴我你不會遲到
Do you understand
你明白嗎
Yes sir I will not be late again
是的，先生，我不會再遲到了
Y'all some mess up some orders don't you
你們都搞砸了一些命令，不是嗎？
If you have any troubles to order there's some tutorials videos for you so look through it
如果您在訂購時遇到任何麻煩，這裡有一些教程視頻供您參考，請仔細閱讀
Okay I'll take a look
好的 我去看看
On one more thing
還有一件事
Make sure leave your phone in locker
確保將手機放在儲物櫃中
You better not be texting anyone during work
你最好不要在工作期間給任何人發短信
Yes sir
是的先生
Wall
牆
Senpai Senpai senpai
前輩前輩前輩
Custom pie
定製餡餅
Oh my God I thought that car was about to run over some pie
哦，我的上帝，我以為那輛車要碾過一些餡餅
Okay buy some pie I guess
好吧，我想買一些餡餅
No we all have customers what's s***
不，我們都有客戶什麼是***
Okay well I have to look through these
好吧，我得看看這些
Yeah these are tapes because I don't know how to cook any of this stuff
是的，這些是磁帶，因為我不知道怎麼做這些東西
Cold a chocolate-chip Sheila
冷巧克力片希拉
Shelob Pacino
希洛布·帕西諾
Caramel chellappa Chino vanilla Frappuccino
焦糖切拉帕奇諾香草星冰樂
Mashallah Pacino alright
瑪莎拉·帕西諾
Let's watch the video
讓我們看視頻
What the f*** is happening all they putting ice inside
他媽的發生了什麼他們把冰放進去
The blunder
大錯
And then
然後
There's milk okay they put milk inside the 12 hold on slowed down
有牛奶，他們把牛奶放在裡面 12 慢點
I don't know what's happening
我不知道發生了什麼
There's nothing in that glass
那個玻璃杯裡什麼都沒有
You're lying to me
你在騙我
You are a liar
你是個騙子
You are a f****** liar what
你是個騙子什麼的
Bro
兄弟
That's really hard to see right
這真的很難看對
Okay I guess I'll watch the the hot drink
好吧，我想我會看熱飲
On sale
發售中
Ono Bros
小野兄弟
What
什麼
I I can't believe I actually have to learn how to cook s***
我不敢相信我真的要學會做飯
And Bruin
還有布魯因
I'll have to steam the milk
我得把牛奶蒸一下
Okay
好的
Steam the milk
蒸牛奶
I don't know what I did there I put some kind of
我不知道我在那裡做了什麼我放了一些
I don't get it bro
沒看懂兄弟
Haha
哈哈
Work hard for that bank I guess so
為那家銀行努力工作，我猜是這樣
I'll food tutorial okay sure
我會食物教程好的
Yeah I guess actually is like Starbucks
是的，我想實際上就像星巴克
I liking the sandwiches at Starbucks sometimes like when I'm in a hurry and I need to get a drink from there I've some I like to get the
我喜歡 Starbucks 的三明治
The mozzarella
馬蘇里拉奶酪
And the tomato
還有番茄
Like yours like a chicken caprese sandwich or something like that
像你的像雞肉捲心菜三明治或類似的東西
Every now and then
時不時
Alright well
好吧好吧
Ha
哈
I'll try my best
我會盡力的
Cool do the recipes old man
酷做食譜老人
Hello sir
你好先生
How are you today like I talked to you about. She said
你今天怎麼樣，就像我跟你說的一樣。她說
You said she was coffee I've never been to one of these fancy places before
你說她是咖啡 我以前從未去過這些高檔地方之一
I feel uneasy there's something strange about this place there's something strange
我感到不安 這個地方有什麼奇怪的地方有什麼奇怪的地方
My daughter seems to have found this place and now I'm here however I'll leave the drinks to you
我的女兒似乎找到了這個地方，現在我在這裡，但是我會把飲料留給你
I want Alex get two of them
我想讓亞歷克斯得到其中兩個
Would you want a latte in a coffee I'll be just fine it's really uncomfortable here okay
你想要一杯拿鐵咖啡嗎 我會很好 這裡真的很不舒服 好嗎
You don't have to rub it in
你不必摩擦它
Oliver how can you charge such a price or something like this
奧利弗你怎麼能收取這樣的價格或類似的東西
You know that sounds just like a customer service because right
你知道這聽起來就像客戶服務，因為對
Coffee and a latte
咖啡和拿鐵
I don't know how to make a coffee in a latte
我不知道如何用拿鐵咖啡沖泡
Latte is coffee and steamed milk okay so I have milk
拿鐵是咖啡和蒸牛奶還可以，所以我有牛奶
And then I put the milk inside
然後我把牛奶放進去
I make him uncomfortable excuse you
我讓他不舒服 原諒你
Hot shops coffee dispenser
熱店咖啡機
I think I'm doing it right I'm I doing it right
我認為我做對了 我做對了
Let's just say I'm doing it right sure and then nah this one can go inside.
假設我做對了，然後這個可以進去。
Play
玩
Play hot cup of steamed milk inside
在裡面玩熱騰騰的熱牛奶
I think I did that's a lot say okay okay okay then I grab him
我想我做了很多，好吧好吧好吧，然後我抓住他
And you're also good weight
而且你的體重也不錯
Buttercup go
毛茛去
Oh here it is
哦，在這裡
Oh and then okay
哦，然後好吧
I think I did it right
我認為我做對了
I hope
我希望
Hey sir sir sir
嘿 先生 先生 先生
You have to tell me how the coffee was
你得告訴我咖啡怎麼樣
Wait is this the coffee place the order item I didn't even get the place to order item that you just leave
等一下，這是咖啡點的訂單項目我什至沒有得到你剛剛離開的訂單項目的地方
I don't know if I did it right
我不知道我是否做得對
Can even tell me where's my status where's my gratification right
甚至可以告訴我我的狀態在哪裡我的滿足權在哪裡
Was I too slow
我是不是太慢了
I really hope I wasn't too slow I feel bad
我真的希望我不是太慢我感覺不好
I'm by myself
我一個人
I have to do all this s*** down
我必須做這一切
Oh you're very pretty wait wait what happened to your neck
哦，你很漂亮，等等，你的脖子怎麼了
Did you guys see that
你們看到了嗎
We will have internet yeah looks kind of weird
我們將有互聯網是的，看起來有點奇怪
I don't think that's okay lady you might want to get that checked out
我不認為那沒關係女士你可能想檢查一下
I missed scarf is it the scarf I don't know guys
我錯過了圍巾是不是我不認識的圍巾
Oh now she looks fine I'm not doesn't like okay whatever
哦，現在她看起來很好 我不是不喜歡 好吧
Sarin Saran did you hear on the news that your stalker cases are on the rise
Sarin Saran 你有沒有聽說你的纏擾者案件正在上升的消息
I don't want to be stocked please scary woman like me see
我不想被放養 請像我這樣可怕的女人看看
Be careful
當心
The guys are we staring at me so
伙計們是我們盯著我看
Be careful to
小心
Well you don't have to worry as much as I do but you should watch out either way she's a b****
好吧，您不必像我一樣擔心，但是無論哪種方式，您都應該注意她的ab****
She just called us all ugly what you're calling ugly
她只是說我們都很醜你說的醜
Film dark mocha chip Sheila Pacino please
電影黑摩卡芯片希拉帕西諾請
And you're expecting me to give you good service okay
你期待我給你提供良好的服務好嗎
You're right I have to
你是對的 我必須
I think it saw me go check the recipe for it again Messer orderup
我想它看到我又去檢查它的食譜了 Messer orderup
No I don't want to do that that's Daddy
不，我不想那樣做，那是爸爸
Chocolate chip Sheila Pacino okay Blended iced oops
巧克力片希拉·帕西諾（Sheila Pacino）還可以混合冰凍哎呀
When did I sorry rh10c the students Eli she didn't see that its okay its okay its okay
我什麼時候對不起 rh10c 學生 Eli 她沒看到沒關係 沒關係 沒關係
Ice inside of wonder
奇蹟中的冰
I forgot a cappuccino cappuccino
我忘記了卡布奇諾卡布奇諾
Is it supposed to be a cappuccino or Frappuccino I'm not sure
我不確定是卡布奇諾還是星冰樂
Chocolate sauce in cocoa powder where is the cocoa powder
可可粉中的巧克力醬在哪裡可可粉
A chocolate sauce is
巧克力醬是
Okay where's the old cocoa powder
好的，舊的可可粉在哪裡
Cocoa powder Dairy Joe
可可粉乳業喬
Frank Ocean ocean you didn't see that shooting see that lady to get the
弗蘭克海洋海洋你沒有看到那次射擊看到那位女士得到
Cold drink dispenser
冷飲分配器
And my jual chocolate sauce and then I do Coco
還有我的朱爾巧克力醬，然後我做可可
Gold powder
金粉
Enough enough enough milk milk
足夠足夠的牛奶牛奶
And ice
還有冰
That's it right
沒錯
Wow pog
哇波格
Yeah coffee chocolate sauce cocoa powder milk in 12 dice that's that's right
是的 12粒咖啡巧克力醬可可粉牛奶 沒錯
Hey goodbye
嘿再見
She just going to sit there okay
她只是想坐在那裡好嗎
The guys are amazing Parker that's crazy that you see that
伙計們太棒了帕克，你看到那真是太瘋狂了
Kicker out I want to kick her out
踢出去我想把她踢出去
What the f***
什麼鬼***
Why do they look like they're going to beat me up
為什麼他們看起來像是要揍我
Squad rolled-up holyshit The Boys the boys rolled up at the at the Starbucks
小隊捲起的狗屎男孩們在星巴克捲起
What is a cleaning supplies didn't realize I cleaning supplies
什麼是清潔用品沒意識到我清潔用品
A matcha cake please stop
抹茶蛋糕請停下
Pushing me a salted caramel mocha then I'll have a matcha latte
給我一杯咸焦糖摩卡，然後我要一杯抹茶拿鐵
Pacino you always campaign should drink so let's share man
帕西諾你總是競選應該喝所以讓我們分享男人
Sure let's do that
當然讓我們這樣做
One pumpkin cake I think I'll have something you see what you can order first I'll have
一個南瓜蛋糕 我想我會吃點東西 你看看你能先點什麼 我會吃的
Hot cocoa
熱可可
A Coke or are you serious I don't have any money right now
一杯可樂還是你是認真的我現在沒有錢
Joe said that come on I'll buy you 10 you want to drink yes but
喬說來吧，我給你買 10 你想喝是的，但是
Just said he's got money
只是說他有錢
No it's not like that but really anything is fine
不，不是那樣，但真的什麼都好
Really I want a white mocha
真的我想要一杯白摩卡
Okay any food
好的任何食物
No I just a drink
不，我只是喝一杯
Come on what's the recent food but okay
來吧，最近的食物是什麼，但還好
American waffles
美國華夫餅
Waffles thanks both of you
華夫餅謝謝你們倆
Hey where you looking at
嘿，你在哪裡看
You sure that noise noise what noise does a noise
你確定那噪音噪音什麼噪音噪音
Enter either it's probably nothing
輸入要么它可能什麼都沒有
Must be your imagination that happens from time to time
一定是你不時發生的想像
Sis I've made up my mind and apple pie
姐姐，我已經下定決心和蘋果派
What's happening
發生了什麼
Will that be all your call me sis
這就是你叫我姐姐的全部嗎
The f*** are you calling sis
你他媽的叫姐姐
That's all sister I don't know
這就是我不知道的妹妹
Colossians sake I don't know what the
歌羅西人的緣故，我不知道是什麼
I didn't keep track of any of that can you guys help me what the f***
我沒有記錄任何這些，你們能幫我嗎？
Talk today just say I'll move over here
今天說話就說我搬過來
Yeah can you guys help me
是的，你們能幫幫我嗎
Mashallah Pacino a salted caramel mocha
Mashallah Pacino 咸焦糖摩卡
The second one
第二個
The middle one
中間一個
The longest one really
最長的真的
Okay you know these they all kind of reminded me I don't know it's like
好吧，你知道這些，它們都讓我想起了我不知道這就像
Like if the luxium boys just rolled up like I'm working I'm working night shift and they rolled
就像如果 luxium 男孩像我在工作一樣捲起我正在上夜班並且他們捲起
About that my my Cafe
關於我我的咖啡館
And they're all giving me a hard time in my mind
他們都讓我很難過
So glad to be here. Hang out with you hope you've been doing well virtual hug
很高興來到這裡。和你出去玩，希望你一直做得很好虛擬擁抱
Okay I think we will go after the third one right there second one
好的，我想我們會在第三個之後進行第二個
Hold on while Some Things Remembered all that
等一些事情記住了這一切
Will be waiting
會等著
Alright
好的
How to do their order
如何做他們的訂單
Lysol
來蘇爾
American apple pie American waffle in pumpkin cake
美式蘋果派 南瓜餅中的美式華夫餅
Talk to the pastry shop till
與糕點店交談直到
Yeah let's do the pastry first I think those are easier I
是的，讓我們先做糕點吧，我認為那些更容易我
Okay there's a monster cake and then there's a
好的，有一個怪物蛋糕，然後有一個
I'll put this one here
我會把這個放在這裡
Okay that's one that's one
好的，這就是一個
Now I need so I put the pumpkin cake where's the pumpkin cake pumpkin cake
現在我需要所以我把南瓜蛋糕放在哪里南瓜蛋糕南瓜蛋糕
Pumpkin cake pumpkin cake
南瓜餅南瓜餅
Okay there's a regular pumpkin cake sir and you can have some of my cake later
好的，先生，有一個普通的南瓜蛋糕，你可以稍後再吃我的蛋糕
I want to see
我想看看
American waffle
美國華夫餅
Where's the waffle
華夫餅在哪裡
Primo baked cheese tart strawberry churro Americans
Primo 烤奶酪餡餅草莓油條美國人
Bacon and spinach quiche
培根菠菜乳蛋餅
Okay I found the waffle is your waffle and
好的，我發現華夫餅是你的華夫餅
The apple pie have an apple pie down here. Well here's your apple pie
蘋果派這裡有一個蘋果派。這是你的蘋果派
And you're so big a wheel of big portion sizes right
你是如此之大，一個大份量的輪子，對
Bro it's imagine where you doing this all by yourself with no hair
兄弟，想像一下你自己在沒有頭髮的情況下做這一切
Write like you're actually doing this in real life making overwhelmed of orders that sounds like pain
寫得好像你在現實生活中確實在做這件事，讓聽起來像痛苦的命令不堪重負
I'll know which one do I do first salted caramel mocha
我會知道我先做哪個咸焦糖摩卡咖啡
Hello
你好
But I heard somebody alright
但我聽到有人說好的
A white mocha
一杯白摩卡
What's a white mocha coffee and steamed milk and white chocolate sauce
什麼是白摩卡咖啡和蒸牛奶和白巧克力醬
Oh that's it okay that's easy ways a hot drink yeah it is a hot drink
哦，沒關係，這很容易喝一杯熱飲是的，它是一種熱飲
Alice to always have steamed milk from earlier to
愛麗絲從早到晚總是有蒸牛奶
I'm just grab.
我只是搶。
Put another picture skim milk doing great day thank you
再放一張脫脂牛奶做的很棒的一天謝謝
You so much for believing in me
你非常相信我
Okay f****** wait
好吧，f******等等
Oh f*** wait chocolate what's the white chocolate sauce first right and then we
哦，f ***等等巧克力什麼是白巧克力醬先對然後我們
We can do the steamed milk and then that's all
我們可以做蒸牛奶然後就是這樣
The white mocha right isn't that the white mocha
白摩卡不是那個白摩卡
As I do that right
正如我做的那樣
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I did it right I did it right they would tell me if I did wrong so right
是啊是啊是啊是啊我做對了我做對了他們會告訴我如果我做錯了那麼對
Okay poggers now I have to do the salted caramel mocha
好的，現在我必須做咸焦糖摩卡咖啡
Not saw
沒看到
16 mil Coffee caramel syrup hazelnut syrup and chocolate sauce that's a lotta
16 mil 咖啡焦糖糖漿榛子糖漿和巧克力醬，真是太棒了
A lot of sauces in syrups
糖漿裡有很多醬汁
F*** I forgot
F***我忘了
Caramel
焦糖
Hazelnut and chocolate caramel
榛子和巧克力焦糖
Hazelnut
榛子
And chocolate
還有巧克力
Now
現在
Add to do the Moksha jalapa Chino
添加做 Moksha jalapa Chino
Alarm
警報
I press
我按
Unimpressed caramel
不為所動的焦糖
Best caramel
最好的焦糖
It's supposed to have caramel caramel
它應該有焦糖焦糖
What do you mean wrong sauce is says I'm supposed to have caramel
你是什麼意思錯誤的醬汁是說我應該有焦糖
I did it twice
我做了兩次
Coffee single caramel syrup hazelnut
咖啡單焦糖糖漿榛子
Akshay oops my bad my bad my bad my bad iic
Akshay 哎呀我的壞我的壞我的壞我的壞 iic
Vegetable with caramel syrup by accident don't look at me
不小心加了焦糖糖漿的蔬菜別看我
Okay caramel
好的焦糖
Chocolate and what else
巧克力什麼的
Wait hazelnut
等榛子
Wait wait wait wrong again f***
等等等等又錯了f***
Chocolate caramel sauce
巧克力焦糖醬
All I put caramel sauce caramel sauce by accident
所有我不小心放了焦糖醬焦糖醬
Don't look at me don't give you guys don't see anything between me and you
不要看我不要給你們看不到我和你之間的任何東西
I'll f****** kill you
我會他媽的殺了你
Okay caramel syrup hazelnut caramel syrup
好的焦糖糖漿榛子焦糖糖漿
Chocolate sauce and there's a steamed milk
巧克力醬和蒸牛奶
But you're right
但你是對的
Alright
好的
Guys
伙計們
I almost press this one
我差點按這個
Yeah they seem happy is some free pretty happy about that right okay
是的，他們看起來很開心
Good good good good
不錯不錯不錯不錯
Now we have to do a macho chellappa Chino
現在我們要做一個男子氣概的 chellappa Chino
When did Ice milk matcha powder and whipped cream weight we have whipped cream to
冰奶抹茶粉和鮮奶油什麼時候重我們有鮮奶油
Okay
好的
And then we got Blended ice get ice put in the
然後我們得到了混合冰，把冰放進去
Wonder cup hog in their weight
神奇的杯子豬在他們的體重
Oh I have to put the ice
哦，我得放冰塊
And then okay now it's born in the ice you guys must think I'm f****** stupid but trust
然後好吧，現在它誕生在冰上，你們一定認為我他媽的愚蠢但相信
When I say I'm very f****** stupid I'm trying to understand
當我說我非常愚蠢時，我試圖理解
Okay matcha Blended iced milk
好的抹茶混合冰牛奶
Matcha powder
抹茶粉
Why doesn't coffee or no coffee it says there's no coffee for this one
為什麼沒有咖啡或沒有咖啡，它說這個沒有咖啡
Rongkop
榮科普
Wait
等待
Neha Kapur
內哈·卡普爾
Haha
哈哈
Oh my God it was Blended ice melt okay there's no coffee for this one I started this supposed to have coffee
哦，我的上帝，它是混合冰融化好的，這個沒有咖啡我開始這個應該喝咖啡
Why is this one have coffee to have coffee but then these two don't have coffee
為什麼這個有咖啡喝咖啡，而這兩個沒有咖啡
Okay milk matcha powder whipped cream in ice milk
好的牛奶抹茶粉打發奶油冰牛奶
Knock
敲
Iced matcha powder and where's the whipped cream huh where the f*** is the
冰抹茶粉和鮮奶油在哪裡？
What's cream what's cream
什麼是奶油什麼是奶油
All right away that's the wrong lid on
好吧，這是錯誤的蓋子
Ugly I don't
醜我不
I'm wasting so many couplets
我浪費了這麼多對聯
Thought you lot were you okay see you goodbye
以為你們還好嗎 再見
My God how stressful
我的天哪有壓力
Famous say thank you you're still getting Loft
著名的說謝謝你仍然得到閣樓
Ungrateful I get back in the car looking clowns
忘恩負義的我回到車裡看小丑
Why do they drive like that
他們為什麼那樣開車
Wow
哇
Duda Speedy's guys are like on Initial D shape
Duda Speedy 的人就像在 Initial D 形狀
Good job babe. Thank you I'm trying to invest right now
幹得好寶貝。謝謝，我現在正在嘗試投資
What is the store it's like dotted
星羅棋布的店舖是什麼樣的
For some reason
因為某些原因
Hey I wait aren't you the same dude from earlier
嘿，我等一下，你不是以前的那個傢伙嗎
Here's my order o
這是我的訂單
Latte latte wow I love you
拿鐵拿鐵哇我愛你
Thank you I was just coughing steam milk ezpz
謝謝我只是在咳嗽蒸汽牛奶ezpz
I know how to do a latte
我知道怎麼做拿鐵
Just coffee
只是咖啡
Milk
牛奶
An hour.
一小時。
Wait
等待
Shut the fuk up you didn't see the s*** you did not see
閉嘴你沒看到 s*** 你沒看到
Anything exciting. Prasad twice
任何令人興奮的事情。普拉薩德兩次
Okay we're good I forgot
好吧，我們很好，我忘了
Is because the jalapa Chino confuse me
是因為jalapa Chino把我弄糊塗了
From earlier
從早些時候
Play the original
播放原版
You going to talk to me hey I'm going to
你要跟我說話嘿我要
Private investigator
私家偵探
All are you are you here to talk to me about your you know your daily worries
All are you you are you are you here to talk about you 你知道你每天的煩惱
Give me a little insight about what's your investigation you spot
讓我了解一下您發現的調查內容
Suspicious around the area there been numerous reports of people getting harassed
該地區可疑，有許多關於人們受到騷擾的報導
I was wondering if you see anything in the store
我想知道你是否在商店裡看到了什麼
Mute
靜音
Call me if something ever happens try closing the store early if you don't want to get in trouble
如果發生什麼事情就打電話給我如果你不想惹麻煩，試著提前關店
I think that's a that's a
我認為那是一個
The flag
國旗
Almond the music's off
杏仁音樂響了
With the music turned off
隨著音樂關閉
Oh man well I'm scared now hello
哦，伙計，我現在很害怕你好
Cars are
汽車是
Thinking reports of harassment Psy
對騷擾 Psy 的思考報告
Should look around
應該環顧四周
Yeah we should close the store early
是的，我們應該早點關店
Can I flip the closed sign
我可以翻轉關閉的標誌嗎
I can't put the closed sign doesn't let me
我不能把關閉的標誌不讓我
That's closing time did you scared me
那是關門時間你嚇到我了嗎
Alright well
好吧好吧
Older CC TV
較舊的央視
We have a we have a security camera I didn't know we had a security camera
我們有一個我們有一個安全攝像頭我不知道我們有一個安全攝像頭
This entire time
這整個時間
Don't trust this this either all of this all of the drive-thru window people are going to come
不要相信這個或者所有這一切所有的開車窗口的人都會來
Do the drive-thru in the future that's kind of bug
將來做得來速這是一種錯誤
Anybody back here
任何人回到這裡
Oh there's a power any right here till that's creepy
哦，這裡有一種力量，直到那令人毛骨悚然
The power's going to turn off later
稍後電源將關閉
Okay I'll still sweet before
好吧，我還是會甜蜜的
Don't know where we're supposed to sweep
不知道我們應該掃到哪裡
Oh that's how we sweep your Galaxy 3 right that's why I'm saying how do they make such a mess in such a short
哦，這就是我們如何掃蕩你的 Galaxy 3 這就是為什麼我要說他們怎麼會在這麼短的時間內搞得這麼一團糟
There's only a few customers
只有幾個顧客
Did they decide to spill their drinks on the floor
他們是否決定將飲料灑在地板上
Assholes
混蛋
The lady was sitting here she spilled her drink on the floor she called me ugly
那位女士坐在這裡，她把飲料灑在地板上，她說我醜陋
Y'all f*** you lady
你們都他媽的你的女士
Oh no
不好了
Guys
伙計們
WYD
世界青年節
What happened
發生了什麼
Hello
你好
I have a broom
我有一把掃帚
I'm a f****** broom I'll check not free to Bunk you
I'm af****** broom 我會檢查沒有空給你下舖
Where where the hell are you where's the
你到底在哪裡
I'm again side
我又在身邊
Wait
等待
Spilt milk
覆水難收
Somebody was back here
有人回來了
It was a fall the spilt milk
灑出來的牛奶是秋天
God don't like that
上帝不喜歡那樣
Yeah we have all the spilled milk for I don't understand
是的，我們有所有溢出的牛奶，因為我不明白
Is everything okay
一切都好嗎
Yeah how'd that happen dude like where the f***
是的，這是怎麼發生的，伙計，就像他媽的在哪裡一樣
Invite out there all CCTV
邀請所有中央電視台
Do you spell Tamela call right all right
你拼寫 Tamela call 好嗎
Am I in the bathroom
我在浴室裡嗎
Nope nobody's inside the bathroom
沒有人在浴室裡
Maybe somebody's hiding inside the closet
也許有人躲在壁櫥裡
So am I supposed to do with the spilt milk
所以我應該處理灑出來的牛奶嗎
Take It Outside
把它帶到外面
Backdoor
後門
Maybe I put it in the trash now
也許我現在把它扔進垃圾桶了
Hello summer
夏天你好
Play out here and leave a store like that unattended right
在這裡玩，離開這樣無人看管的商店吧
Like a bad idea
就像一個壞主意
Ojai things got so much more creepy I don't like it
Ojai 的事情變得更加令人毛骨悚然，我不喜歡它
My phone
我的手機
I don't know what to do with spilled milk
我不知道怎麼處理打翻的牛奶
Oh
哦
Put in the fridge
放入冰箱
New day
新的一天
What the f***
什麼鬼***
Where are we
我們在哪
Okay 11:15 that's November 15th right
好的 11:15 那是 11 月 15 日，對
I suddenly feel a lot more uncomfortable like I feel like something's going to go wrong in someone's going to
我突然感到更不舒服，好像我覺得有人要出問題了
We're going to find somebody in our house that's the kind of level of all freekesha I'm expecting right now
我們會在我們的房子裡找到一個我現在期待的所有freekesha級別的人
Yeah I guess it's the next day after everything that just happened
是的，我想這是剛剛發生的一切之後的第二天
Hope we don't see that creepy guy again remember that one that had the we give his phone back
希望我們不再看到那個令人毛骨悚然的傢伙記得那個我們把手機還給他的人
Maybe she was actually a nice guy I don't know maybe I'm driving too fast but
也許她實際上是一個好人我不知道也許我開得太快但
He was all pretty creepy while I could tell she don't want to go to Starbucks
他非常令人毛骨悚然，而我可以看出她不想去星巴克 1834年
See this is why I hate closing shift I really like working in the middle of the day
看到這就是為什麼我討厭下班我真的很喜歡在中午工作 1835年
So when I used to working now what's it a food service place when I was
所以當我以前工作的時候，現在是什麼食品服務場所？ 1836年
Like super super young I would hate closing shift because it's just a lot of work at the end
就像超級超級年輕人一樣，我討厭結束輪班，因為最後需要做很多工作
Feel like morning and midday is a lot better
感覺早上和中午好多了 1838年
Magic tissues inside because maybe we were two shoes and not just want you
裡面有神奇的紙巾，因為也許我們是兩隻鞋子，而不僅僅是想要你
Like I have How many pairs of shoes I like 123456 Lexus
Like I have 我喜歡多少雙鞋 123456 雷克薩斯
But that's it really.
但事實就是如此。
Is just dress shoes like one of them shoes and like the other five or like
只是正裝鞋像其中一隻鞋和其他五隻鞋一樣
You know like two of them are for running and for going to the gym or like running and then the other three are like for work
你知道其中兩個是為了跑步和去健身房或喜歡跑步，然後另外三個是為了工作 1843年
Stuff like that stylish sometimes you want to be stylish guys right
像這樣時髦的東西，有時你想成為時髦的人，對吧 1844年
Yeah
是的 1845年
A bad feeling about this ever really bad feeling about this
對這種感覺非常不好的感覺 1846年
I hope all weirdos not around
我希望所有怪人都不在身邊 1847年
Anymore yeah The Vibes are suddenly so much more scary because of
再說了，是的，Vibes 突然變得如此可怕，因為 1848年
Private investigator telling us about the harassment cases and just seeing that one guy from earlier
私家偵探告訴我們關於騷擾案件的事，只是看到了之前的那個人
Really f***** up my head I hope he doesn't show up again
真的他媽的我的頭，我希望他不會再出現
Right here anymore
就在這裡
I'm seeing anymore I think we're fine. OK Google work
我不再看到我認為我們很好。好的谷歌工作
Older Zara some fly some pie
舊 Zara 一些飛一些餡餅 1853年
I sometimes I
我有時我 1854年
Hello senpai
你好前輩 1855年
Stuff away first
先收拾東西 1856年
Vinesauce
醋汁 1857年
Like
喜歡 1858年
My dogs are not getting fire by the way how did the spilled milk and up outside there from the fridge smells weird
順便說一句，我的狗沒有著火，從冰箱裡溢出的牛奶和外面怎麼聞起來很奇怪
So mighty. Thank you for the 10,000 B hope you having a great morning or evening bro welcome
如此強大。謝謝你的 10,000 B 希望你有一個美好的早晨或晚上兄弟歡迎
10000 B again you guys are insane
10000 B 又是你們瘋了
Appreciate it though
雖然欣賞 1862年
A seriously
一個認真 1863年
Really can you oversleep
真的可以睡過頭嗎 1864年
I'm so sorry no not I'm so sorry
我很抱歉 不 我很抱歉 1865年
I want you to not be late
我要你不要遲到 1866年
This is the second time I'm sorry
這是第二次對不起 1867年
Lemoore doozy Azimuth help flush you think why don't you ask your mama to wake you up
Lemoore doozy Azimuth 幫助沖洗你想為什麼不叫你媽媽叫醒你 1868年
You're a dick
你是個屌絲
Your f****** dick don't get back here don't know no f*** you f*** you
你的f ****** 迪克不要回到這裡不知道不 f *** 你 f *** 你
The customers bulshit I'ma beat your ass in the parking lot
顧客胡說八道我在停車場打你的屁股
Sometime you see the weird guy sometime sometime
有時你會在某個時候看到那個奇怪的傢伙 1872年
Who's this dude he looks like me to do from nights of livery
誰是這個傢伙，他看起來像我從制服的夜晚做的 1873年
You guys remember the dude from night delivery in the in the in the apartment she was like gang scam by the priest
你們還記得公寓裡那個晚上送貨的傢伙，她就像牧師的幫派騙局 1874年
Gonna remind you that guy a little bit
會稍微提醒你那個人 1875年
Weird Al
奇怪的鋁 1876年
Weird Al looking out there
奇怪的艾爾向外看 1877年
Well hello there
你好 1878年
Where's my order coffee
我點的咖啡在哪裡 1879年
Coffee okay
咖啡還行
Impossible for me to f*** of coffee right
對我來說不可能喝咖啡吧
Yes sir there you go
是的，先生，你去吧 1882年
Jerry coffee
傑瑞咖啡 1883年
Want to talk
想談談 1884年
Aussie have more oh you have more you a******
澳大利亞人有更多哦你有更多你a****** 1885年
American scone caramel Soffe American Alpine American waffle is it because he looks like an American
美式scone caramel Soffe American Alpine American waffle 是因為他長得像美國人 1886年
Is our gang all the American food I don't know waffle pie and sauce
我們這幫人都是我不知道的美國菜嗎 華夫餅和醬汁 1887年
Coffee
咖啡 1888年
I don't know what the developers were thinking
不知道開發者是怎麼想的
Falafel
沙拉三明治
Is there a waffle
有華夫餅嗎 1891年
Dude me too though I would order like maybe 5 things to sample like Silas big cheese
伙計我也是，雖然我可能會點 5 樣東西來品嚐，比如 Silas 大奶酪 1892年
Start I want a big cheese start now or like an egg tart that sounds so delicious
開始我現在想要一個大奶酪開始，或者像一個聽起來很美味的蛋撻 1893年
Jay and the scone
杰和烤餅 1894年
That's right and now we have the apple pie apple pie
沒錯，現在我們有了蘋果派蘋果派 1895年
Apply
申請 1896年
Miguel
米格爾 1897年
On our way he's walking away is going to try to get inside from the back door guys
在我們離開的路上，他會試圖從後門進去 1898年
Hey girl thank you very much
嘿女孩非常感謝你
Haha
哈哈
You'll compressed no need so nihongo jouzu me
你會壓縮沒有必要所以 nihongo jouzu 我
What what
什麼什麼
I've been living here for more than 15 years
我在這裡住了超過 15 年 1903年
Okay
好的 1904年
Hey girl
嘿姑娘 1905年
Something's not right about this place
這個地方有點不對勁 1906年
Didn't expect that I really didn't expect him to say that by the way
沒想到真的沒想到他會這麼說 1907年
I didn't think that because I'm not around some something about the store
我不這麼認為，因為我不在商店的某些地方 1908年
Maybe because of that guy over there
可能是因為那邊那個人 1909年
Yeah he's gone you songs you write
是的，他走了，你寫的歌
I guess it was just my imagination no it was not just your imagination bro
我想這只是我的想像，不，這不僅僅是你的想像，兄弟
We definitely saw weirdo looking at us through the window
我們肯定看到怪人透過窗戶看著我們 1912年
Are you haunted by any chance know maybe I am
你是否被任何機會困擾知道也許我是 1913年
By the way I'm running late so I'm going to have to go okay guys guys guys guys I talk to
順便說一句，我要遲到了，所以我得走了 1914年
Earlier but the music down for a little bit the scariest thing to me
早些時候，但音樂下降了一點對我來說最可怕的事情 1915年
Is not monsters monsters are hot okay
是不是怪物怪物很熱好嗎 1916年
I feel like the scariest thing to me is real people
我覺得對我來說最可怕的是真實的人 1917年
Like actual Killers murderers and like kidnappers
就像真正的殺手兇手和綁架者一樣 1918年
Real people are
真實的人是 1919年
A thousand times more scary than like an alien or like I don't know
比像外星人或像我不知道一樣可怕一千倍
I'll f****** Pyramid Head
我會f******金字塔頭 1921年
Or Slenderman or whatever could ever be
或 Slenderman 或任何可能的東西 1922年
You know or scp's those guys they're pretty scary right
你知道或者 scp 的那些傢伙他們很可怕吧 1923年
B
乙 1924年
You know
你懂的 1925年
People that are literal stalkers
字面上的跟踪狂的人 1926年
And thought
並想 1927年
You know tractors all that type of stuff that's really what gets Maya
你知道拖拉機所有那種類型的東西，這才是瑪雅真正的動力 1928年
You know
你懂的 1929年
It's me and not for your spot self I think this game is trying to appeal more to that rather than like ghosts
是我，而不是你的現場自我我認為這個遊戲試圖吸引更多人而不是像鬼一樣
And like spirits
和精神一樣 1931年
So I think that's kind of cool you know
所以我覺得你知道這很酷 1932年
So far I feel like the theme right now is that we're exploring
到目前為止，我覺得現在的主題是我們正在探索 1933年
Jewel
寶石 1934年
People
人們 1935年
Being like a threat
像威脅一樣 1936年
To us rather than like spirits and demons of chemical
對我們來說，而不是像化學的精神和惡魔 1937年
Alright so long
好久不見 1938年
Secure old man
保護老人 1939年
I think there's somebody in the back
我覺得後面有人
I know what's back there that door doesn't open
我知道後面有什麼那扇門打不開 1941年
All all
全部全部 1942年
She going to come in the store
她要去商店 1943年
He is going to come in the store
他要進店 1944年
Damn bro
該死的兄弟 1945年
Why were you looking around from being a creep from outside huh
你為什麼從外面的蠕動中四處張望呢？ 1946年
He's inside the store what do I do guys
他在商店裡我該怎麼辦伙計們 1947年
Oh wait you ordered already how'd you order I didn't talk to you
哦，等一下，你已經下單了，你是怎麼下單的，我沒和你說話 1948年
Milk
牛奶 1949年
Plus milk weight vanilla chellappa Chino plus milk plus milk so he just want a cup of milk
加牛奶重香草 chellappa 奇諾加牛奶加牛奶所以他只想要一杯牛奶
Plus milk
加牛奶 1951年
Plus milk that's weird how do I make this ice milk
加上奇怪的牛奶我怎麼做這個冰牛奶 1952年
Vanilla syrup and vanilla powder would you like you would you like extra would you like extra
香草糖漿和香草粉 你想要嗎 你想要額外的 你想要額外的嗎 1953年
Breastmilk with that sir
和那個先生一起吃母乳 1954年
Turn my case boy milk I don't know
把我的案子男孩牛奶我不知道 1955年
You like a latte with extra boy milk
你喜歡加牛奶的拿鐵 1956年
All right now and look at the other
現在好了，看看另一個 1957年
So it's just milk milk vanilla syrup and vanilla powder okay
所以它只是牛奶牛奶香草糖漿和香草粉好嗎 1958年
Subway over here
地鐵這邊 1959年
The ice inside
裡面的冰
Milk vanilla powder
牛奶香草粉 1961年
And vanilla syrup
還有香草糖漿 1962年
Yeah
是的 1963年
Now he just wants milk right
現在他只想喝牛奶 1964年
But what is what is a
但是什麼是什麼 1965年
In what just a cold cup of milk
在什麼只是一杯冷牛奶 1966年
Okay
好的 1967年
Here's your milk I guess
我猜這是你的牛奶 1968年
Likewise you just want regular milk if he really likes milk
同樣，如果他真的喜歡牛奶，您只需要普通牛奶
You really wants his milk is he's a growing dude
你真的想要他的牛奶是他是個正在成長的傢伙
Right
正確的 1971年
Weirdo
怪人 1972年
The bottom milk shut off no bottom milk why are you talking about oh my God
底奶關掉沒底奶你在說什麼天啊 1973年
You guys got a like slow down
你們都慢了下來 1974年
You know what he looks like to come you know who he looks like he reminds me
你知道他來的樣子你知道他的樣子他提醒我 1975年
Light Yagami
輕八神 1976年
A little bit Light Yagami right he see it
有點輕八神，他看到了 1977年
Shoya
莊屋 1978年
You're just going to leave already what you do with your milk
你只是要離開你用牛奶做的事情
Your cute can I have your number
你可愛我可以要你的號碼嗎
F*** you
你他媽的 1981年
Would you like to order anything sir
你想點什麼嗎先生 1982年
Your heart this is you guys really dislike you guys
你的心這是你們真的不喜歡你們 1983年
Tarantula
狼蛛 1984年
Trying to do my job right now but you order something b****
現在正試圖做我的工作，但你點了一些 b**** 1985年
Engulf your recommendation
吞噬你的推薦 1986年
Your name tell me your name
你的名字告訴我你的名字 1987年
Our recommendation be the limited-time-only double chocolate chip Frappuccino I see what's your phone number
我們的推薦是限時雙巧克力片星冰樂我知道你的電話號碼是什麼 1988年
Stop it oh my God you wants my what's my number
停止它哦我的上帝你想要我什麼是我的號碼
You know why she wants my name what's my name so we can write in the f****** death no I know your tricks Light Yagami f*** you
你知道她為什麼要我的名字我叫什麼名字這樣我們就可以在 f****** 死亡中寫下我知道你的把戲 Light Yagami f*** you
My phone number
我的電話號碼
I'm not good-looking aren't I I booze myself I'm quite popular around here maybe this is
我不好看不是我自己喝酒我在這附近很受歡迎也許這是
Is the ferociter the investigator was talking about the investigator
調查員所說的兇猛者是調查員嗎
I think we found the harasser
我想我們找到了騷擾者
Get them out
讓他們出去
Get out of here Beat It
離開這裡打敗它
Now's your chance now's my chance for what
現在是你的機會 現在是我的機會
Did he give like he gives me the fuckboi energy right now so
他是不是就像他現在給了我他媽的能量一樣給了
I really want to grab the broom and just like you don't shove him out get the f*** out of here
我真的很想抓住掃帚，就像你不把他推開一樣把他媽滾出去
I'm trying to run a professional Cafe
我正在嘗試經營一家專業的咖啡館
Establishment cease give him
建立停止給他 2001年
A fake phone number or order the double chocolate chip Frappuccino
一個假電話號碼或訂購雙巧克力片星冰樂 2002年
Do you guys see that hold on
你們看到堅持住了嗎 2003年
Right there which we give up pixels number
就在那裡，我們放棄了像素數 2004年
Now we should just do the order right
現在我們應該正確地做訂單 2005年
I don't want to play with D I feel like we should just do it or not play with his
我不想和 DI 一起玩，感覺我們應該這樣做還是不和他一起玩 2006年
Emotions or whatever
情緒什麼的 2007年
Okay
好的 2008年
Even though I'm so tempted to bite my ass later though
儘管我很想稍後再咬我的屁股
I'm just answering I'm down I'm not interested
我只是回答 我很沮喪 我不感興趣
The attitude
態度
Don't regret this I'm going home
不要後悔 我要回家了
You mean you're going home
你的意思是你要回家
You're going home what are you doing
你要回家你在做什麼
Weirdo
怪人
Dumb
啞的 2016 年
Is that it
是這樣嗎
Closet doors
壁櫥門
There's a lot of cars going by till
有很多車經過
They look at all this
他們看著這一切
Wait what is this
等等這是什麼
Huh
呵呵
GIC the s***
GIC ***
The dude is taking pictures of it's the f***** that ordered the milk he's obsessed
哥們在拍照 是他媽點了他迷戀的牛奶
No
不
Oh my God is that is a dude from outside I was looking at us and ordered extra boy milk
哦，我的上帝，那是外面的傢伙，我看著我們，點了額外的男孩牛奶
You get out of here
你離開這裡
How do you take a picture I didn't even see him have a camera
你怎麼拍照我什至沒看到他有相機
How do you print out a picture so fast to what
怎麼把圖片打印出來這麼快到什麼程度
Oh no that's weird all know he's back he's back what's
哦，不，這很奇怪，所有人都知道他回來了，他回來了
It's him
是他
Please don't come up to it please stop
請不要碰它請停止
Foreclosed sir
止贖先生
Try hide
嘗試隱藏
I feel scared now
我現在感到害怕
Did I honestly feel like I should hide
我真的覺得我應該隱藏嗎
Okay
好的
I'm just going to take my trash out
我只是要把我的垃圾拿出來
What's the tables how do I Busby Stables
什麼是桌子 我如何使用 Busby 馬厩
Bossy bossy
專橫專橫
He still there
他還在
Acer get the f*** out
宏基滾蛋
Please
請
Is he like scoping the place or something
他喜歡劃定這個地方的範圍還是什麼
Always at the drive-thru
總是在得來速
Begin by the drive-thru what
從得來速開始什麼
He stole their bro
他偷了他們的兄弟
Get out
出去
Yeah
是的
Okay maybe that wasn't the guy
好吧，也許那不是那個人
Maybe that was like somebody else and they are like all are you guys open though it's probably closed
也許這就像其他人一樣，他們就像你們所有人都是開放的，儘管它可能已經關閉了
Oh my God
我的天啊
Worth trash come from
值得垃圾來自哪裡
Do you know
你知道嗎
This is like that episode from SpongeBob
這就像海綿寶寶的那一集
You guys remember that when he was trying to take out the trash at night time
你們還記得當他試圖在晚上倒垃圾的時候
It's actually pretty scary
其實很嚇人
Fctv there's nothing in the cctv-4 fine
Fctv cctv-4 裡面什麼都沒有
Yeah it's the one of The Hash Slinging Slasher
是的，它是 The Hash Slinging Slasher 之一
But we're not bring about The Hash Slinging Slasher ring and Valdosta
但我們不會帶來 The Hash Slinging Slasher 戒指和 Valdosta
Walking creep
行走蠕動
Cleaning writing an offer busing the tables right
清潔寫一個報價busing the table right
Can I call the guy
我可以打電話給那個人嗎
Volume India investigator he gave me his number right
卷印度調查員他給了我他的電話號碼
Don't know we're not allowed to take her phone out during your work shift
不知道在你輪班期間我們不能把她的手機拿出來
Because Senpai is going to give us a hard time do that
因為前輩會讓我們很難做到這一點
Is he still around
他還在嗎
Anybody out there don't think so fine
外面的人都覺得不太好
We want to switch the closed sign so like show that were closed instead of like having somebody walk in
我們想切換關閉的標誌，就像關閉的節目一樣，而不是讓有人走進來
While we're working
在我們工作的時候
Nice
好的
November 27th now
現在11月27日
You guys hear that all this is another thing about living in the apartment I could never live in one because
你們聽說這一切都是住在公寓裡的另一回事，我永遠不能住在一個公寓裡，因為
You guys know how much ice cream right I feel like I'd be up and noise disturbance
你們知道有多少冰淇淋，我覺得我會起床和噪音干擾
Very obvious Sun noise disturbance and Zaman neighbors would be very angry at me
非常明顯的太陽噪音干擾和扎曼鄰居會對我很生氣
So I don't care whatever you want to do that right
所以我不在乎你想做的事
After somebody in the other room
在另一個房間裡有人之後
Alto
中音
I'll come check it out
我過來看看
Knock on the door I think you're just being loud neighbors as usual you have those sometimes right
敲門我想你只是像往常一樣大聲鄰居你有時是對的
Yeah I don't know if I should even look around like
是的，我不知道我是否應該環顧四周
The other Flores like what reason do I have to look at the other apartment florist
其他弗洛雷斯喜歡我有什麼理由去看看其他公寓花店
Oh my God lady
哦，我的上帝女士
Holyshit
媽的
You f******
你他媽的
Emotional damage
情感傷害
That one that one really got me
那個那個真的讓我
Watch where you're going watch where you're going Jesus young ones these days
看你要去哪裡看你要去哪里耶穌這些天年輕人
I'm really being I'm really being scolded by a boomer I'm being scolded
我真的是我真的被一個嬰兒潮一代罵我被罵
My f****** Boomer right now about watching where I'm going
我的f****** Boomer現在關於看我要去哪裡
Hey are you a baby or a baby look weird are you look at me like that
嘿，你是嬰兒還是看起來很奇怪的嬰兒，你是那樣看著我嗎？
You look at me like that why you just standing there till
你那樣看我為什麼你就站在那裡直到
God I can't
天啊我不行
Condescending look you know I'm talking about like a old Asia older age
居高臨下的樣子，你知道我說的就像一個老亞洲老年人
Asian ladies like that haughty attitude arms crossed
亞洲女士喜歡那種傲慢的態度雙臂交叉
Judgmental stare like they're better than you and that you know
判斷性的凝視，好像他們比你更好，你知道
Isn't this the car that we saw yesterday is that the car we saw yesterday
這不是我們昨天看到的車就是我們昨天看到的車嗎
Dykes I'm not sure
堤壩我不確定
Is that the car we saw I don't know it looks kind of similar I'm not sure
是不是我們看到的那輛車我不知道它看起來有點像我不確定
CDs
光盤
Oh my God wake whoever is my was hiding behind the
哦，我的上帝喚醒了躲在我背後的人
The car they're looking at us
他們看著我們的車
My car I'm not late this time am I
我的車這次我不遲到是嗎
Where's some pie some pie somebody you in today
你今天在哪裡？
Senpai
前輩
Really my stuff and talk to some pie yeah
真的是我的東西，和一些餡餅說話是的
ISM by
ISM 由
Today's our first closing shift
今天是我們的第一個結業班次
Oh
哦
Did I not have closing shifts before
我以前沒有輪班嗎
I thought we were closing before
我以為我們之前要關門了
Have a questions you get strange customers around at night
有一個問題，你晚上會遇到奇怪的顧客
Well sometimes video just brush it off if they come focus on your work that's plenty to do
好吧，有時視頻只是把它刷掉，如果他們專注於你有很多事情要做的工作
Actually I'm afraid I might be being stalked
其實我怕我被跟踪
You want me to believe someone is interested in the likes of you he's a dick
你想讓我相信有人對你這樣的人感興趣 他是個混蛋
He is such a dick
他真是個雞巴
Dude what is stopping me
伙計是什麼阻止了我
From
從
Punching him across the face right now
現在打他的臉
God some pie you're a b****
上帝啊，你真是個餡餅
I guess I'll come find a help you if anything ever happens haha
我想如果有什麼事我會來找你的哈哈
No Lie
沒有謊言
Senpai by Ono
小野前輩
Customers already geez okay
客戶已經很好了
I was going to break his leg
我要打斷他的腿
No
不
It's okay
沒關係
I guess
我猜
Just another day
只是另一天
And you guys have
你們有
Oh
哦
Wait until really late for school students to be out right now
等到真的很晚，學生們現在才出去
Hold on
堅持，稍等
Mari
馬里
Sorry I'm going to the bathroom can you order a macchiato for me
抱歉，我要去洗手間，你能幫我點一杯瑪奇朵嗎
Remy okay
雷米還好
Mayumi I'll have a cinnamon roll churros and a cup of coffee please and add whipped cream to it
Mayumi 我要一份肉桂卷油條和一杯咖啡，然後加生奶油
You going to eat that much
你要吃那麼多
Wonder you got so fat don't be mean
想知道你這麼胖別刻薄
What are e
什麼是電子
Think separately
分開思考
Together is fine and I'll have them mashallah Pacino
在一起很好，我會讓他們 mashallah Pacino
What's jalapa Sheena can't be serious
什麼是jalapa Sheena不能是認真的
How cold it is right now
現在有多冷
I'll be fine
我會沒事兒的
Helen what did Maria want again
海倫 瑪麗亞又想要什麼
She said you wanted a macchiato
她說你想要一杯瑪奇朵
You mean shelah Pacino
你是說希拉·帕西諾
She's going to catch a cold
她會感冒
No she wants
不，她想要
No I would be fine but Maria won't be
不，我會很好，但瑪麗亞不會
I said earlier right
我之前說的對
For what
為了什麼
Caramel macchiato
焦糖瑪奇朵
Stop please
請停一下
Hot Journal macchiato got it
Hot Journal 瑪奇朵得到了它
What these pieces are toxic
這些碎片有毒
Oh my God works tutor dealing with toxic schoolmates wow or gain the whole
哦，我的上帝工作導師與有毒的同學打交道哇或獲得整個
I'll menu of customers tonight that's that's incredible
今晚我將提供客戶菜單，這太不可思議了
Yeah I was a really confusing order I'm not too sure what the f*** I'm supposed to deal
是的，我是一個非常混亂的訂單，我不太確定我應該處理什麼
I still have the photo
我還有照片
Mashallah Pacino strawberry and cream roll strawberry churro
Mashallah Pacino 草莓奶油卷草莓油條
Let's get the strawberry cream roll and strawberry Trail for stripe
讓我們來買草莓奶油捲和草莓小徑吧
Strawberry
草莓
Play cream roll on a cream roll
在奶油卷上玩奶油卷
Hands off
放手
Rissa
里薩
The strawberry one
草莓一號
No no. No I don't want that
不，不。不，我不想那樣
Only got trash this
只有這個垃圾
Where's the Cheraw
Cheraw在哪裡
Dichro there is the churro
Dichro 那裡是油條
Miss the boys right now
現在想念男生
Boys are funny yeah
男孩子很有趣耶
It is the cream roll and saw
這是奶油捲和鋸
Is your
是你的
Is there turo
有圖羅嗎
Would you like to see a photo of me
你想看我的照片嗎
No no
不，不
Okay
好的
Guys do see anything outside hunting ice anything else right
伙計們確實看到了狩獵冰之外的任何東西
I think weird
我覺得奇怪
Just
只是
Making sure we have an extra set of eyes
確保我們有一雙額外的眼睛
Shema crazy
舍瑪瘋了
Coffee and whipped cream
咖啡和生奶油
Just coffee and whipped cream
只是咖啡和生奶油
That's it
而已
Okay
好的
What's cream where's the whipped cream
什麼是奶油 生奶油在哪裡
You guys like to scream a lot I feel like I'm more of a fan of a Cool Whip
你們喜歡尖叫很多我覺得我更像是酷鞭子的粉絲
I think about that when I mean like something strawberries
當我的意思是草莓之類的東西時，我會想到這一點
Alright thank you for that
好的，謝謝你
Bowser corrects that's what you want to write
Bowser 糾正了這就是你想要寫的
I want some cream like Cool Whip
我想要一些奶油，比如 Cool Whip
Extreme sometimes is nice it's fluffy
極端有時很好，它很蓬鬆
Gentle
溫和的
Alright
好的
I like the caramel macchiato now
我現在喜歡焦糖瑪奇朵
Is a caramel macchiato
是焦糖瑪奇朵
It's coffee steamed milk caramel syrup and caramel sauce
是咖啡蒸牛奶焦糖糖漿和焦糖醬
What's the difference between
有什麼區別
What's the what's the difference between caramel syrup and caramel sauce
焦糖漿和焦糖醬有什麼區別
Is there supposed to I thought the same thing
我應該有同樣的想法嗎
Viscosity all syrup is thicker alright
粘度所有的糖漿濃一點就好了
Okay
好的
Coffee coffee coffee
咖啡 咖啡 咖啡
And that's make a mugshot shelah Pacino
這就是一張面部照片 shelah Pacino
Which is Blended ice all poggies alright
哪個是混合冰所有的poggies好嗎
What has more sugar steel is it a syrup
含有更多醣鋼的是糖漿
Gotomypc rap
Gotomypc 說唱
And now we need steamed milk
現在我們需要蒸牛奶
Milk and then internal sauce and then
牛奶，然後是內部醬汁，然後
Caramel syrup
焦糖糖漿
And
和
I said
我說
Nice
好的
Yeah nice
不錯不錯
I didn't f*** it up this time
這次我沒搞砸
Macchiato
瑪奇朵
Channel macchiato
渠道瑪奇朵
Hey are you are you proud of me I'm doing a good job right
嘿，你為我感到驕傲嗎？我做得很好嗎？
Okay
好的
Noah
諾亞
Need to get a
需要得到一個
Mashallah Pacino
瑪莎拉·帕西諾
Can I put the sauce inside the blender cup at school
我可以把醬汁放在學校的攪拌杯裡嗎
Haha
哈哈
Alright
好的
Come to this
來到這個
And then
然後
And then we put milk
然後我們放牛奶
And
和
And then we'd seal
然後我們會密封
What's the
是什麼
Matcha powder and whipped cream
抹茶粉和鮮奶油
Matcha powder there's no much syrup
抹茶粉沒有太多醣漿
No coffee
沒有咖啡
Huh
呵呵
Play me no coffee
玩我不喝咖啡
Type of coffee boxing
咖啡拳擊類型
All type of coffee boxing
所有類型的咖啡拳擊
When Chuck is that supposed to have coffee
Chuck 什麼時候應該喝咖啡
It's not supposed to have coffee
它不應該喝咖啡
Coffee in that you're right
咖啡因為你是對的
Dammit teriyaki
該死的照燒
Redo it will redo it
重做它會重做它
I keep thinking I had to put the coffee inside the chellappa Chino for some reason
我一直在想出於某種原因我不得不把咖啡放在 chellappa Chino 裡面
God god dammit man
上帝該死的男人
And matcha powder and then
然後抹茶粉
When did Ice
冰什麼時候
And then cream
然後奶油
Gossiping that
八卦那
Is every time I hear the scream noise it's so funny
是不是每次我聽到尖叫聲都那麼好笑
All right and that's it
好吧，就是這樣
Nothing that's it right
沒有什麼是對的
And sticker
和貼紙
What happened to your friend
你朋友怎麼了
Wait
等待
Oh Mari thanks I'll pay you back now what's
哦，瑪麗，謝謝，我現在就還給你什麼
I mean okay thanks
我的意思是好的謝謝
Who's this guy
這個人是誰
Hey
嘿
Wasn't that guy on the bus with us today creepy looking
今天和我們一起在公共汽車上的那個人不是看起來很毛骨悚然嗎
Yeah good thing we got off at a different place
是的，還好我們在不同的地方下車
On the bus
在公交車上
You know she might have done something to harm us
你知道她可能做了一些傷害我們的事
Yeah but you know what
是的，但你知道嗎
Since you seem like a dangerous person so you know the guy outside
既然你看起來像個危險的人，所以你認識外面的那個人
I could hear him breathing from miles away
我能聽到他在數英里外的呼吸聲
The way he looks give me the shivers
他的樣子讓我不寒而栗
You still here
你還在這裡
What's what he abducts me scary
什麼是他綁架我可怕
Don't worry no one's to kidnap you
不用擔心沒人綁架你
Is that like a in so I don't know what's that supposed to mean by outside right now
是不是像一個 in 所以我現在不知道外面是什麼意思
Seriously though
不過說真的
Tell the police or something yes tell the police
告訴警察或某事是的，告訴警察
Technically he didn't do anything
從技術上講，他什麼都沒做
Besides I don't want to get involved in anything creepy
此外，我不想參與任何令人毛骨悚然的事情
Right
正確的
Maybe he's just another weirdo
也許他只是另一個怪人
There's nothing on the TV though
不過電視上什麼都沒有
Goodbye guys Sia
再見，Sia
Always always travel in groups be careful
總是成群結隊旅行要小心
Okay
好的
Secure and also who's this dude he's just looking at the coffee
安全，還有誰是這個傢伙，他只是在看咖啡
His hair looks like
他的頭髮看起來像
Was it like grass
是不是像草一樣
Axor what's your order
雅生您的訂單是什麼
Latte please
請拿鐵
A latte
拿鐵
I'll be 371
我會是371
371 let's see 4567
第371章 4567
And 100-yen
還有100日元
1 seal
1個印章
Huion 1470n can't afford it
惠翁1470n買不起
I guess I better luck next time
我想我下次運氣會更好
I'll pay the rest okay that's sweet
剩下的我會付錢的
I'm sorry I thought you were an a******
對不起，我以為你是一個**
He kind of looks like a creeper s
他有點像爬行者
But
但
Be a Good Samaritan that's what my father always told me
做一個好撒瑪利亞人這是我父親一直告訴我的
School today so drink something warm yeah
今天上學，喝點熱的吧
For someone like me
對於像我這樣的人
Mention it
提到它
Thank the Lord
感謝主
Oh by the way have you seen any ghosts lately What where did that come from
哦，對了，你最近有沒有看到任何鬼魂？那是從哪裡來的？
Oh by the way have you seen a gross lately I'm just trying to do your orders sir
哦，順便說一句，你最近有沒有看到一個噁心的東西，我只是想听你的命令，先生
Please
請
No
不
IC
我知道了
Define then
然後定義
Why did that give me sudden chills
為什麼這讓我突然發冷
Was that about how what was that about
那是關於如何 那是關於
I don't know
我不知道
Must be the stress of poverty
一定是貧窮的壓力
Poor guy
可憐的傢伙
Haha
哈哈
Got it
知道了
I'm sorry no
我很抱歉沒有
Dude what what was that joke
哥們開什麼玩笑
I'll have a vanilla latte
我要一杯香草拿鐵
Alright well
好吧好吧
I guess he's a bit of a dark dark humor, a guy or something I don't know
我猜他是個有點黑色幽默的人，一個我不認識的人
The guys are also phased into each other oh my God you have a bulge
伙計們也逐漸進入彼此哦，我的上帝，你有一個凸起
Yeah I see that
是的，我看到了
Ideas are overlapping I can see the dude's bulge better
想法重疊，我可以更好地看到這傢伙的凸起
That's incredible
這是令人難以置信的
Okay well yeah that's an make a latte right
好吧好吧，那是拿鐵咖啡吧
I'll make a latte
我會做一杯拿鐵
Things on the camera
相機上的東西
Cool
涼爽的
I have a job to you you're very right you know you're very correct have a job to do
我有一份工作給你
Semi pulled up beside milk
半拉到牛奶旁邊
When will I ever use the swim off by the way I feel like I haven't use that all this entire time
我什麼時候才能使用游泳，因為我覺得我一直沒有使用它
Lead-ins
導入
And the lot say
很多人說
You do sir enjoy your latte
先生，你喜歡你的拿鐵咖啡嗎
Have a good day
祝你有美好的一天
You your kind of funny
你很有趣
You look like a gamer
你看起來像個遊戲玩家
You kind of like he is like he's like he's a he's a streamer he's probably a
你有點像他就像他就像他是一個流光他可能是一個
Like Ninja
喜歡忍者
Or some s***
或者一些s***
It's not just because of the the green hair
這不僅僅是因為綠頭髮
Promise
承諾
Okay vanilla latte
好的香草拿鐵
I was just the same thing but with vanilla syrup okay obviously
我只是一樣的東西，但香草糖漿顯然沒問題
Twitter f******. Okay
推特他媽的。好的
Now where is the vanilla syrup
現在香草糖漿在哪裡
Hog deer
豬鹿
I'm getting I'm in better at this
我越來越擅長這個
Are y'all talking
你們都在說話嗎
On my way to home the other guy
在我回家的路上另一個人
Love to
喜歡
What I want to see what they're all about
我想看看他們的全部內容
It said
它說
The f****** coffee just implode in front of me see I see that
他媽的咖啡就在我面前爆炸，我看到了
Did you guys see that
你們看到了嗎
It just exploded
剛剛爆發了
In front of my face what
在我面前什麼
Can the closet door
衣櫃門可以嗎
I wasn't going to close the door guys
我不打算關門伙計們
I wish I could lock it to
我希望我能把它鎖定到
Bus the tables
巴士桌子
A+ the tables there's anybody back here
A+ 桌子有人回來了
Also wait the bathroom right
也等浴室吧
If use the bathroom I might have to clean that in a bit
如果使用浴室，我可能需要稍微清潔一下
All snowing to hey
都下雪了嘿
Do you guys like the snow it's really beautiful
你們喜歡雪嗎 真的很美
That's a little bit more Ambience to the outside
外面的氛圍有點多
I like to snow a lot I don't like shoveling snow but I do like snow
我喜歡下很多雪我不喜歡鏟雪但我喜歡雪
Is there another photo
有沒有另一張照片
Is the Saints able to cuetopia
聖徒是否能夠 cuetopia
The photo was sitting at the other time
這張照片是在其他時間坐著的
Think anybody's going to come around
認為有人會過來
Give me a snowblower
給我一個吹雪機
You know maybe it's about time I guess nobler or gallon for my parents
你知道也許是時候為我的父母買高貴或加侖了
Who the f*** are you
你他媽是誰
Hello
你好
I don't know what to do about that
我不知道該怎麼辦
Guys I don't know what to do about that
伙計們，我不知道該怎麼辦
Should I call somebody I think I might
我應該打電話給我認為可能的人嗎
How come it's so nice I really don't want to check on
怎麼這麼好看我都不想看了
Mannitol
甘露醇
Why can't I just call the police if somebody weird here
如果這裡有人奇怪，我為什麼不能報警
The same stalker from last time no waiting who is this guy
上次的那個跟踪狂不等這人是誰
She doesn't have a hold on this time or maybe that's not the right guy call the guy
這次她沒有把握，或者也許這不是合適的人打電話給那個人
Guy who on man I don't know
我不認識的人
I want to do y'all take a broom with me
我想做你們都帶著我的掃帚
The broom of me as a weapon sure f*** you up your ass
我的掃帚作為武器肯定會f***你的屁股
Wait
等待
Play White
打白
The day we first met yes at Sheila's she smiled at me
我們第一次見面的那天是在希拉家，她對我微笑
Flower just thinking about her makes my heart pound I've never
花一想到她就讓我心跳加速 我從來沒有
I felt this way before I wonder if she's putting on a smile
在我懷疑她是否在微笑之前我有這種感覺
I want space like she does mine
我想要空間，就像她做我的一樣
I don't like that
我不喜歡那樣
All know that dude is creepy as hell
都知道這哥們太可怕了
What is this
這是什麼
Play what are we looking at
播放我們在看什麼
Ice photos
冰照片
Whose photos are these
這些是誰的照片
Oh my God wait I think we're the milk
哦，我的上帝等等，我想我們是牛奶
Wait
等待
The guy's a weirdo
這傢伙是個怪人
He's taking pictures of us and drinking the milk from our place
他在給我們拍照，喝我們家的牛奶
Low
低的
What the f*** is this
這是什麼鬼
I know her best
我最了解她
Maybe after your mother and father
也許在你的父母之後
I'll really be number one in time
我真的會及時成為第一
She talks to me
她跟我說話
She picked up my phone and went out of her way to give it to me
她拿起我的手機，特意把它給了我
I knew she felt the same way I did
我知道她的感覺和我一樣
We are in love
我們相愛了
Today's our anniversary
今天是我們的周年紀念日
God almighty.
全能的上帝。
Guys
伙計們
What do I do
我該怎麼辦
Call in sick
請病假
Awesome fly I can't make it in today someone's trying to
令人敬畏的蒼蠅，我無法在今天有人試圖
Someone's trying to kill me
有人想殺我
Or
要么
And or getting my pants and I don't want that
或者得到我的褲子，我不想要那個
Leave the apartment supposed to leave the apartment like this
離開公寓應該這樣離開公寓
I mean of course she knows like
我的意思是她當然知道
And where we live he's been stalking us the entire time
在我們住的地方，他一直在跟踪我們
Hide in the bathroom
躲在浴室裡
I guess presenza
我猜presenza
Alexandra not at home
亞歷山德拉不在家
But now he knows every time we're about to go to work
但現在他知道每次我們要上班
Hello
你好
Guys I'm scared
伙計們我害怕
I'm like this and like that guy unlike him help me
我喜歡這個，也喜歡那個不像他的人幫助我
Somebody help me
來人幫幫我
I don't want to be alone the f***
我不想一個人呆著他媽的
Oh my God
我的天啊
What's over here the train
火車在這兒怎麼了
Call the police are called Detective
報警叫偵探
Is my car a second hold on
我的車是第二次等嗎
Can I take the train instead is that an option is as the trains over here
我可以坐火車嗎？
Today is that possible
今天是可能的
Help help
幫助幫助
Someone with this is the bus stop
有這個的人是公共汽車站
We can take the train holyshit that's so cool
我們可以坐火車，太酷了
Wow I like that a lot maybe because we changed
哇，我很喜歡，也許是因為我們改變了
Star pattern
星紋
I like where we go
我喜歡我們去的地方
You won't show up
你不會出現
Right
正確的
I think I just outplayed him
我想我只是超過了他
At the bus not a train or bus I meant to say about my bad
在公共汽車上不是火車或公共汽車我想說我的壞事
What's going off my heart rate
我的心率怎麼了
Why you looking at me
你為什麼看著我
Why is he looking at me like that why is everybody looking at me so weird stop
為什麼他這樣看著我 為什麼每個人都看著我那麼奇怪 停下
Stop it you guys are weirdos don't look at me
停下來你們是怪人別看我
Is this the right place
這是正確的地方嗎
Oh yeah it is the right place yeah the sound only got my ears feel
哦，是的，這是正確的地方，是的，聲音只讓我的耳朵感覺到
Well we didn't take the the car today we took
好吧，我們今天沒有坐車
Guitar the boss hopefully
吉他老闆希望
Home some pies not upset at all right
回家一些餡餅一點也不生氣
Is that our car no that's us some toys car
那是我們的車嗎不那是我們一些玩具車
Right
正確的
Only myself and talk to some pie
只有我自己和一些餡餅說話
Sometime
有時
I'm late for work I'm sorry it waits imply
我上班遲到了我很抱歉它等待意味著
Or some kygo
或者一些 kygo
Did some Tyga
做了一些泰加
He's sitting in the back
他坐在後面
Maybe he's in the bathroom Sunfire are you taking a poo
也許他在浴室 Sunfire 你在拉屎嗎
Oh
哦
Our
我們的
Hey
嘿
Hahaha
哈哈哈
1 mi
1 英里
God
上帝
You scare the s*** out of me leave me alone while I'm in the restroom goddamnit
你嚇到我了
Get to work what will
開始工作
Why why did you just dip out so fast he literally booked you like Sonic
為什麼你這麼快就跳出來了，他真的像索尼克一樣預訂了你
Omar
奧馬爾
Paul Alicia Keys
保羅·艾麗西亞·凱斯
What is it isn't that the guy
什麼不是那個人
What does the same guy no that's the same dude
the same guy no that's the same dude 是什麼意思
That we give the phone to back then no we have a weirdo
我們把電話還給我們，然後不，我們有一個怪人
American scum okay
美國渣還行
I don't like this I really don't like this
我不喜歡這個 我真的不喜歡這個
Somebody save me somebody coming to the game and kill him
有人救我有人來比賽然後殺了他
Or like just tell him to the cease-and-desist like a
或者就像告訴他停止和停止一樣
Not s macchiato iced coffee and steamed milk
不是瑪奇朵冰咖啡和蒸牛奶
I sold your truck
我賣了你的卡車
Is there any monster I hope you know that
有沒有什麼怪物希望你知道
Minnesota
明尼蘇達
He was devoted to stalking me I don't like it
他一直在跟踪我，我不喜歡
Talking like it bro don't think anybody would like that right
像這樣說話，兄弟認為沒有人會喜歡這樣
Queso need caramel sauce
Queso需要焦糖醬
Sounds good
聽起來不錯
Hard caramel sauce caramel syrup
硬焦糖醬焦糖糖漿
Hog goodbye
豬再見
Zuri like I don't know if it's just a game or
Zuri 就像我不知道這只是一個遊戲還是
Is it like zoodoo other Japan drive that fast
是不是像其他日本的zoodoo一樣開得那麼快
I'm pretty sure the game is just like exaggerating it right
我很確定遊戲就像誇大其詞一樣正確
Don't think anybody drives that fast
不要以為有人開車那麼快
Not usually speed-wise welcome
通常不歡迎速度
So she's a very stylish lady I like your outfit
所以她是一個非常時尚的女士我喜歡你的衣服
Can you can you help me with that gentleman over there like maybe crab
你能不能幫我和那邊的那個紳士像螃蟹一樣
I'll hand you a knife right
我會遞給你一把刀
You pretend like you're going to murder me right and we'll bring the police here
你假裝要殺了我，我們會把警察帶到這裡
And then and I can deal with him or something I don't know saniplus scenario help me
然後我可以處理他或我不知道的事情 saniplus 場景幫助我
I'd like a green tea latte while those waffles still
我想要一杯綠茶拿鐵，趁著那些華夫餅還在
Green tea latte in a waffle that's the green zealots and Waffles are delicious I always go for those two
華夫餅中的綠茶拿鐵是綠色狂熱者和華夫餅很好吃我總是去這兩個
Glad you like them know thank you for serving them my son likes them too
很高興你喜歡他們知道謝謝你為他們服務我兒子也喜歡他們
Are you alone I'll give you this if you'd like
你一個人嗎？如果你願意，我會給你這個
This rosary bracelet sets ward off evil you should keep it
這個念珠手鍊可以驅邪，你應該保留它
Aux kind of sweet ass like a protection charm
Aux 那種像保護咒一樣的甜美的屁股
Bought it from an infomercial on TV they said some amazing things about it I'll know you got scammed lady
從電視廣告上買的，他們說了一些令人驚奇的話，我就知道你被騙了女士
He believed it for only 9999
他只相信了9999
It's fine I owe them a lot anyways
沒關係，反正我欠他們很多
In this day and age it's so convenient to buy things to cellphone there are only a few
在這個時代，用手機買東西非常方便，只有少數
Prices of a button away
一個按鈕的價格
I'll lady got scammed lady got scammed but thank you for your rosary
我會女士被騙了女士被騙了但謝謝你的念珠
I guess
我猜
The bracelet now and green tea latte
現在的手鐲和綠茶拿鐵
American waffle you know all this talk about waffles is making me really crave
美國華夫餅你知道所有關於華夫餅的討論讓我非常渴望
Good waffle now not like the Legos one you know like Echoes are pretty pods
好的華夫餅現在不像你知道的樂高積木，比如 Echoes 是漂亮的豆莢
B I I want like a a Belgian waffle you know
BII 想要你知道的比利時華夫餅
Nice
好的
Green tea latte
綠茶拿鐵
Where's the green tea latte again
綠茶拿鐵又在哪裡
It's vanilla syrup
這是香草糖漿
Steam the milk in matcha powder
用抹茶粉蒸牛奶
Oh there's no coffee in it
哦，裡面沒有咖啡
Okay
好的
Steamed milk
熱牛奶
Sometimes I realize that Sons realize not all Lots
有時我意識到兒子們並沒有意識到所有的事情
Highest have coffee in it
最高的有咖啡在裡面
Just saw surprising I thought most are like it's called a latte have coffee in it
剛看到很驚訝我以為大多數都像拿鐵咖啡裡面有咖啡
Syrup and matcha powder
糖漿和抹茶粉
I do believe I'm getting a lot better at this oh I think I know why it's not being served
我確實相信我在這方面會變得更好哦我想我知道為什麼它沒有被送達
Like rats for this window so then why server they're automatically goes over there okay that makes more sense
就像這個窗口的老鼠，那麼為什麼他們會自動去那裡的服務器好吧，這更有意義
Is young lady
是少婦
Lattes is about the milk so not the coffee
拿鐵是關於牛奶而不是咖啡
Pancakes or waffles yeah I mean I like pancakes a lot so you pancakes are definitely my favorite over waffles but
煎餅或華夫餅是的，我的意思是我非常喜歡煎餅，所以你的煎餅絕對是我最喜歡的華夫餅，但是
I just
我只是
Sometimes you craving waffle right sometimes you just want to eat a waffle instead of Allah
有時你渴望華夫餅，有時你只想吃華夫餅而不是安拉
Salva pancake right now I want a pancake in a waffle
薩爾瓦煎餅現在我想要華夫餅裡的煎餅
Oh hello
哦你好
Wait is it isn't it like kind of cold outside
等等是不是外面有點冷
Ayc dress like that if it's like so it's like real it's snowing you know
Ayc 穿成那樣，如果它是這樣的，它就像真的一樣，你知道下雪了
So I mean okay I mean I guess if you're not cold right
所以我的意思是好吧我的意思是我猜如果你不冷對吧
Idol sister aren't you a cute one are you by any chance
偶像姐姐你不是可愛嗎
Model or something
型號什麼的
She flirting with me
她和我調情
Oh she's an idol okay that's why
哦，她是偶像，好吧，這就是為什麼
No nothing in particular
沒有什麼特別的
What a waste I'm sorry but you should definitely make you some style you got
真是浪費我很抱歉，但你絕對應該讓你有一些你得到的風格
I mean do you want me to introduce you to my office give me your number sorry I'm not sure about that kind of thing
我的意思是你想讓我把你介紹給我的辦公室嗎 給我你的電話號碼 抱歉我不確定那種事情
See
看
Don't care if you regret it
不要在意你是否後悔
I'll have a salted caramel mocha please
請給我一杯咸焦糖摩卡
I know please I would love to do I mean
我知道，我很樂意這樣做 我的意思是
Better than being stocks here I guess
我想比在這裡做股票要好
I don't know
我不知道
She seems pretty nice though I can trust her probably
她看起來很漂亮，雖然我可能可以相信她
Okay I saw any salted caramel mocha salted caramel mocha that's a lot of s***
好吧，我看到任何咸焦糖摩卡咸焦糖摩卡，這是很多s***
Play coffee steamed milk caramel syrup and hazelnut syrup
玩咖啡蒸牛奶焦糖糖漿和榛子糖漿
Let's go lesbians all right
讓我們去女同性戀吧
It's just that she's doubting but we can we can pull you
只是她在懷疑，但我們可以拉你
Just believe
只要相信
Hazelnut syrup and caramel syrup right
榛子糖漿和焦糖糖漿對
And we also need
而且我們還需要
Chocolate sauce okay that's why I f***** up online
巧克力醬好吧，這就是我在網上玩的原因
Forgot about that
忘了那個
Are you lady
你是女士嗎
That's it
而已
Okay I thought you was going to stick around for a little bit longer and have a conversation with us B
好吧，我以為你會多待一會兒，然後和我們談談 B
I guess not there's no weirdos around either
我想周圍也沒有怪人
Right
正確的
I wonder if me taking the train or the bus today was like affected anything
我想知道我今天乘坐火車或公共汽車是否會受到任何影響
What
什麼
Okay
好的
What the f*** dude
什麼他媽的老兄
I
一世
I o i kind of
我有點
I want to keep washing him
我想繼續給他洗
Do his thing
做他的事
What the f*** is happening why
他媽的發生了什麼為什麼
Judas comes into a Starbucks I mean I guess I'm getting like the full experience as a as a food service
猶大進了星巴克
Circular bite
圓形咬合
Damn he's got moves though
該死的，雖然他有動作
You throw it back or back more
你把它扔回去或更多
Is like a male stripper
就像一個脫衣舞男
God damn good for you raw okay what's your order
該死的對你有好處，好吧，你的訂單是什麼
Momotaro
桃太郎
Hey hey it's so hot today I'll have a caramel chellappa Chino
嘿嘿今天太熱了，我要一份焦糖切拉帕奇諾
That's hot today
今天好熱
Is it hot today
今天熱嗎
Talking like yourself
像自己一樣說話
Excuse me sir could you please put on some clothes and not make a scene
對不起，先生，請你穿上一些衣服，不要鬧劇嗎？
Come on I won't be here for long
來吧，我不會在這裡很久
No it would not
不，它不會
So legally that saw the question when it be a disaster of a customer catches a cold
所以從法律上講，當它是客戶感冒的災難時，它就看到了這個問題
Y'all still approach it that way
你們還是那樣做
What's
什麼是
What
什麼
Are you worried about me
你擔心我嗎
Thanks but it's all today
謝謝，今天就這樣了
I feel like I'm being grilled on these questions
我覺得我被這些問題盤問了
I hope it doesn't affect my ending on the mooer here so you guys can see what the options are
我希望它不會影響我在這裡的 mooer 的結局，所以你們可以看到選項是什麼
I don't know what to do for here still be nice if you would consider other customers it's cold outside
如果您考慮其他客戶外面很冷，我不知道在這裡做什麼仍然很好
And what to say
以及要說什麼
Guys hold nipples are out
男生抱乳頭都出來了
I think it's cold outside
我覺得外面很冷
What's
什麼是
Send a single-digit
發送個位數
I'm surprised you could notice no because it'll get colder and colder
我很驚訝你會注意到不，因為它會越來越冷
Now
現在
I only have clothes at home
我家只有衣服
Come back some water when you're dressed
穿好衣服回來喝水
Then you'll just have to go home
然後你只需要回家
Oh no I likes him why dude he was kind of
哦，不，我喜歡他，為什麼伙計他有點
Cool I want to see more of Monmouth Auto
酷我想看更多蒙茅斯汽車
F*** I'll never forget you that you're cool
F***我永遠不會忘記你，你很酷
I was an experienced man
我是一個有經驗的人
Close the door first
先關門
Senpai still here know somebody's gone
前輩還在這裡 知道有人走了
Dirty toilet
骯髒的廁所
He's probably like a Tik-Tok ER you know
他可能就像你知道的 Tik-Tok ER
Remind me to take talkers
提醒我帶談話者
Like walk up the wall and McDonald's in like
就像走上牆和麥當勞一樣
Do some wacky s***
做一些古怪的事情***
Coliseum
體育館
Trash out again
再次扔垃圾
Pray for me I don't die I wonder what happens if you
為我祈禱我不會死我想知道如果你會發生什麼
Other dude
其他哥們
Open closet haven't post on Tik-Tok in a while now
打開衣櫃好久沒在抖音上發帖了
Part of the reason for that is because I'm trying to focus a little bit more on my YouTube right now but
部分原因是因為我現在正試圖更多地關注我的 YouTube，但是
I'm still trying to figure stuff out for a Tik-Tok it's like
我仍在嘗試為 Tik-Tok 找出一些東西，就像
Juggling juggling a lot of different you know things are difficult but
雜耍雜耍很多不同的東西你知道事情很困難但是
You know we're trying
你知道我們正在努力
130 toilet
130廁所
Nice
好的
And now
現在
Toilet paper ran out we were the all the
衛生紙用完了，我們是所有人
Where's all the toilet paper
哪裡來的衛生紙
You saw it
你看到了
So what
所以呢
Huh
呵呵
You saw what
你看到了什麼
You're the door
你是門
You seem resigned see anyting
你似乎辭職了
Where's the toilet paper at Dalton's homemade solar paper
道爾頓自製太陽能紙的衛生紙在哪裡
Toilet paper
衛生紙
If it's in the storage area
如果它在存儲區
I don't
我不
I don't see the toilet paper guys
我看不到衛生紙的傢伙
Does somebody took a s*** there EOS invited to cash it in the toilet the floor yet to clean it it's his fault
有人把 EOS 當作 *** 被邀請在廁所兌現 地板還沒有清理它是他的錯
You look delicious way to Second what
你看起來美味的方式來第二個什麼
What kind of spread is this
這是什麼傳播方式
I'm enjoying it though on what's that say
我很享受它，但那是怎麼說的
Basil chicken and tomato mozzarella
羅勒雞肉和番茄芝士
Yeah that's probably one of them I like ham and the cheese
是的，這可能是其中之一，我喜歡火腿和奶酪
Vienna sausage
維也納香腸
Chicken Inn
小雞旅館
Green sandwich 29 green sandwich
綠色三明治 29 綠色三明治
I would get the
我會得到
Basil chicken and tomato mozzarella one I like that a lot
羅勒雞肉和番茄馬蘇里拉奶酪，我非常喜歡
I'm hungry now
我現在餓了
It's like 12:30 a.m. and I'm already hungry
現在是凌晨 12:30，我已經餓了
F***
F***
I replace the toilet paper where's the toilet paper at huh
我更換衛生紙 衛生紙在哪裡
What if you lived in the vents of the
如果你住在通風口怎麼辦
Avion
亞航
Stylish rananda be creepy
時尚的蘭達令人毛骨悚然
Is nobaday
是nobaday
It would have a public today that sounds gross
今天會有一個聽起來很噁心的公眾
I'm about to think public bidets in self
我要考慮自己的公共坐浴盆
Guys you know where the toilet paper is
伙計們，你知道衛生紙在哪裡
Are the counters counters
計數器是計數器嗎
Look we just give them whipped cream so wipe their ass with
看我們只是給他們生奶油所以擦他們的屁股
Oh here's the toilet paper
哦，這是衛生紙
Nice
好的
Airygal
艾里加
Yeah I see that
是的，我看到了
Somebody there
有人在那裡
Why is that
這是為什麼
Why is there countdown countdown
為什麼會有倒計時倒計時
Wait why is there a countdown for what why is there countdown for
等等 為什麼會有倒計時 為什麼會有倒計時
Lotte or
樂天或
Did you order weight why am I being X on in order to f*** her since
你有沒有訂購體重，為什麼我要上 X 以他媽的她，因為
When you're an a****** I don't know who you are but
當你是一個**時，我不知道你是誰，但
Sting's milk in Hewitt
休伊特的 Sting 牛奶
Okay okay
好吧好吧
A latte another latte
一個拿鐵另一個拿鐵
F****** all f****** in the ass dude I'm so stoned I'm so boned just
F****** all f****** in the ass dude I'm so stoned I'm so boned just
Show me lattes why they wants only lattes for huh hahaha
告訴我拿鐵咖啡為什麼他們只想要拿鐵咖啡哈哈哈
Oh God I'm screwed I'm screwed I'm so screwed
哦，上帝，我被搞砸了，我被搞砸了，我被搞砸了
Hahaha
哈哈哈
Did I fail something I don't know why was I supposed to make lattes for
我是不是失敗了一些我不知道為什麼我應該做拿鐵咖啡
Can I at least service last one
我至少可以為最後一個服務嗎
Okay
好的
Really dark
真的很黑
Guys
伙計們
I'm stuck
我被困住了
I do
我願意
What do I do
我該怎麼辦
What
什麼
Oh
哦
Oh I was just having a nightmare
哦，我只是在做噩夢
Oh s***
哦該死
Weird as hell
詭異到極點
Why was I having a nightmare for
為什麼我會做噩夢
Yahoo's that mystery door about God damn it dude
雅虎關於該死的傢伙的神秘之門
Who's watching us
誰在看我們
Is the same dude last time
上次是同一個人嗎
Creepiest motherfukers washing a suit with drive-thru window
最令人毛骨悚然的混蛋用得來速窗口洗西裝
There's no delivery right
沒有送貨權
You think it's like multiple people I don't think it's multiple people
你認為這就像多人 我不認為這是多人
We need help the guys we definitely need help where's why don't we
我們需要幫助我們絕對需要幫助的人我們為什麼不
Call the chief investigator private investigator guy
打電話給首席調查員私人調查員
I thought I was somebody else's
我以為我是別人的
Phones
電話
Coming I took a train today
來了 我今天坐火車
I can't take the train
我不能坐火車
I hate this
我討厭這個
Oh wait where's my car wait my car or the f***** my cargo
哦等等我的車在哪裡等我的車或者我的貨物
Some pie are you sure I had a nightmare
一些餡餅你確定我做了一個噩夢
Sometimes I
有時候我
Some fire
有些火
The f*** are you some pie
該死的，你是餡餅嗎
Has my stuff there already
我的東西已經在那裡了
What's the investigator guy
什麼是調查員
So my suspicions were true
所以我的懷疑是真的
I'm glad you contacted me
很高興你聯繫我
We contacted him
我們聯繫了他
I'm the police won't help
我是警察不會幫忙的
All they do is brush things off to lessen their workload
他們所做的只是刷掉事情以減輕他們的工作量
Which is why people like me
這就是為什麼人們喜歡我
Take a look around and see if I can find anything
環顧四周，看看我能不能找到什麼
Do you thank God I got received I think
你感謝上帝我收到了我想
For now
目前
You going to take a look around the building I think right
你要去看看我認為正確的建築物
Hope he doesn't die he's a good guy
希望他不要死，他是個好人
Please don't die
請不要死
Somebody got salted caramel mocha here so delicious looking to love some pie
有人在這裡買了咸焦糖摩卡咖啡，好吃到想吃餡餅
Okay I guess I'll try that then one salted caramel mocha
好吧，我想我會試試，然後再來一杯咸焦糖摩卡咖啡
I'll have a dark mocha chip jalapa Gina
我要一杯黑摩卡薯片墨西哥捲餅吉娜
You're not getting salted caramel yeah I want to try something different today
你沒有得到咸焦糖是的，我今天想嘗試一些不同的東西
I had one today
我今天有一個
Seba chellappa Chino on a day like this you're so young
Seba chellappa Chino 在這樣的一天 你還這麼年輕
Cuz it's delicious
因為很好吃
Hustle the music is like going off you guys hear that
喧囂的音樂就像走開你們聽到了
Alicia
艾麗西亞
I'd like to pay your bill
我想付你的賬單
Today the day of the photo shoot or something the store going to be featured in a newspaper
今天是拍攝照片的日子或商店將在報紙上刊登的東西
I know I don't think so why
我知道我不這麼認為為什麼
I saw someone outside taking pictures
我看到有人在外面拍照
Oh
哦
Was he taking pictures of the store yeah the store in Yuma
他是在給商店拍照嗎 是的 尤馬的商店
Likely
可能的
My makeup
我的妝
Are you talkin about
你在談論
I'm sorry we'll be together the drinks are on me
對不起，我們會在一起，酒在我身上
What are you sure
你確定什麼
Thank you so much son by
非常感謝你的兒子
I'm in a good mood today
我今天心情很好
My son used to being a shut-in
我兒子曾經是一個封閉的人
Is in a better mood now that he's going to school
現在他要上學了，心情好多了
Your son's middle school right yeah I just hope he wasn't bullied at school
你兒子的中學是對的，我只是希望他在學校沒有被欺負
I don't have any good memory when I was his age
我在他這個年紀的時候記性不好
So
所以
Where what's up with the investigators he okay
調查員怎麼了 他沒事
LPS fine
LPS 很好
Like I really don't want him to
就像我真的不希望他那樣
And I'll give her a call so this door back here what's behind the mystery door right am I the only one that's like wondering
我會給她打個電話，所以這扇門回來了，神秘門後面是什麼，我是唯一一個想知道的人
What the f*** is happening back there
那裡發生了什麼事
Gina okay
吉娜還好
Did like
喜歡
I'm so happy he's around here making sure that were safe
我很高興他在附近確保安全
But
但
If he doesn't show up for like another like another few minutes I'm going
如果他沒有像另一個人一樣出現幾分鐘，我就走了
Sports likes he got taken out by the stalker right
體育喜歡他被纏擾者帶走
I want that to happen
我希望那發生
The lady isn't always safe zactly that's why that's why it's like
這位女士並不總是安全的，這就是為什麼這就是為什麼它就像
Safer I feel a lot safer if I had my co-worker around
更安全 如果我有同事在身邊，我會感覺更安全
Like at least one other person but no
至少喜歡另一個人，但不喜歡
I'm by myself
我一個人
Have any friends
有沒有朋友
No friends
沒朋友
No maidens
沒有少女
Just coffee
只是咖啡
And I need
我需要
Channel syrup hazelnut syrup and chocolate sauce
通道糖漿榛子糖漿和巧克力醬
What sauce
什麼醬
All maidens
所有少女
That's correct
這是正確的
I don't really want to f*** it out
我真的不想搞砸
Zombie Walk softball many of them
殭屍步行壘球其中許多
Have we f***** up a single one
我們有沒有搞砸一個
I don't think so right I mean there were a few that we've gotten kind of close to f****** lot but we ended up costing that out anyway
我認為不太對，我的意思是有一些我們已經接近了 f****** 很多，但我們最終還是把它花掉了
And you know
而且你知道
We came back from it
我們從那裡回來了
And cocoa powder
還有可可粉
And that's it
就是這樣
Where's my bracelet Yahweh where's my bracelet
我的手鐲在哪裡 耶和華我的手鐲在哪裡
I wore it last time but it's gone now isn't it
上次穿了，現在沒了
Maybe it got like used up when we got haunted by whatever the f*** happened that one night
也許當我們被那天晚上發生的任何事情所困擾時，它就像用完了一樣
Someone stole it it's who did he steal it he snuck into our apartment star bracelet probably
有人偷了 是誰偷的 他偷偷溜進了我們公寓的明星手鍊
What if he sneaks in our apartment while we're out of work
如果他在我們下班的時候偷偷溜進我們的公寓怎麼辦
Oh my God it's the b**** lady with the baby
哦，我的上帝，這是那個帶著嬰兒的混蛋女士
It's a b**** you guys remember her
你們一定記得她
Ilona how you did that but we were there baby huh
伊洛娜你是怎麼做到的，但我們在那裡，寶貝哈
What
什麼
Why'd you walk in here
你為什麼走進這裡
With a baby carriage
帶著嬰兒車
Is crying
哭了
Was she crying
她哭了嗎
Salted caramel mocha while she crying
她哭的時候咸焦糖摩卡
Did her baby die
她的孩子死了嗎
Wheeler she lost her baby on I feel like a dick
惠勒，她失去了她的孩子，我覺得自己像個雞巴
Play you can't do this to me
玩你不能這樣對我
Can baby feel bad for you
寶寶會不會為你難過
No you want to talk
不，你想說話
Baby Gone Gone
寶貝走了
So why she still walking around with the carriage all
所以為什麼她還帶著馬車到處走
That sucks
太糟糕了
That's kind of creepy though maybe we're hallucinating I'm not sure
這有點令人毛骨悚然，雖然也許我們是幻覺我不確定
Yeah that's all
是的，僅此而已
We'll see what happens I feel like there might be some things were missing
我們會看看會發生什麼我覺得可能有些東西丟失了
Like contact conceptually we're missing some stuff right
就像概念上的聯繫一樣，我們缺少一些正確的東西
Well that's strange ma'am
嗯，這很奇怪，女士
Oh I'm sorry give me the usual
哦，對不起，給我平常的
What's the usual
什麼是常態
Woodforest
伍德森林
Sweet red beans and butter bread alright
甜紅豆和黃油麵包好嗎
Red beans and butter bread
紅豆黃油麵包
I'll do the store real fast and then I'll do the other drinks
我會很快做商店，然後我會做其他飲料
Honestly though whoever said it is right this is a lot like slower than usual
老實說，儘管無論誰說是對的，這都比平時慢
Bariachi Lazard game I'm not too sure why but I mean I do like the pace it's
Bariachi Lazard 遊戲我不太清楚為什麼，但我的意思是我喜歡它的節奏
Going nuts
快瘋了
And there's different ends it's like slowly building up the
有不同的結局就像慢慢建立起來
Four aspect of it all but
這一切的四個方面，但
I mean I feel safe now I think since we all have our friend around right
我的意思是我現在感覺很安全 我想因為我們都有朋友在身邊
We cannot put the Skins milk in
我們不能把 Skins 牛奶放進去
Michigan
密歇根州
Books-A-Million
百萬書籍
Oops
哎呀
Now I think I did it right
現在我覺得我做對了
Want to talk
想談談
I saw one more order to do
我又看到了一個訂單
Caramel macchiato
焦糖瑪奇朵
I do that again
我再做一次
Coffee skim milk and caramel stuff
咖啡脫脂牛奶和焦糖的東西
Alright
好的
Tell Alex she's here
告訴亞歷克斯她來了
But the camera
但是相機
She wasn't sure earlier right
她不確定之前是對的
Is a different lady
是個不一樣的女人
Made me seem like a
讓我看起來像一個
It was a what's it the same customer came back or something
這是一個什麼是同一個客戶回來或什麼的
Our second but investor is gone she's gone he's okay
我們的第二個，但投資者走了，她走了，他還好
I still believe he's out there a
我仍然相信他在外面
Are you repairing the stores at the end senatu sour
你在修senatu sour結尾的商店嗎
Antenna
天線
No ma'am
沒有女士
Why
為什麼
I saw someone on the roof
我看到有人在屋頂上
It should be anyone on the roof
應該是屋頂上的任何人
Could be the investigator maybe I should check it out
可能是調查員 也許我應該檢查一下
Could have been my imagination
可能是我的想像
Anyway to drink please
無論如何請喝
Should I go check that out guys
我應該去看看那些傢伙
I still deserve the customers what
我仍然值得客戶什麼
Use the lighter to check the roof
用打火機檢查屋頂
Use the lighter to check the roof that's bad
用打火機檢查壞的屋頂
That doesn't seem good to me
這對我來說似乎不太好
Where's the ladder at then
那時梯子在哪裡
Back here
回到這裡
Where is a lottery
哪裡有彩票
Why is this door open was open the entire time
為什麼這扇門一直開著
Whose car is that is that the investigators you still here right sir
那是誰的車 調查員 你還在這裡 對 先生
Let me look at the other cute vtubers that are around all your
讓我看看你身邊的其他可愛 vtuber
Cute I love you are you're all so cute
可愛我愛你你都那麼可愛嗎
You also look cute you're so cute
你看起來也很可愛 你很可愛
Hold on it's kind of cool no it doesn't let me see all of them it's so cool
堅持一下，這很酷，不，它不會讓我看到所有這些，這太酷了
But all the air off patreon supporters on there though I like it okay
但是所有的 patreon 支持者都在那裡，雖然我喜歡它，好吧
Focusrite right we have to get on the roof that's check the roof and see if
Focusrite 是的，我們必須上屋頂檢查屋頂，看看是否
What is up I like that
怎麼了 我喜歡
Try to window like that who's out there though we see anyting my crazy
試著像那樣打開窗戶，儘管我們看到了我的瘋狂
How did weight how did the investigator even get up there in the first place right
權重 調查員一開始是怎麼爬上去的
I don't think he should have been able to get up there
我不認為他應該能夠爬上去
There's no way there's no way
沒有辦法 沒有辦法
Climb guess we have to
爬猜我們必須
Oh no
不好了
Way he's been living inside the guys guys guys even live
他一直生活在男人體內的方式男人們甚至生活著
No we don't want my God
不，我們不想要我的上帝
Can I leave we know he's inside the room
我可以離開嗎？我們知道他在房間裡
He's been inside the room the entire time inside the fence
他一直在房間裡，在柵欄裡
Oh my God the f****** been living inside the vent still
哦，我的上帝，f****** 還住在通風口裡
Dolor de I want me out
Dolor de 我要我出去
What is this
這是什麼
What is that
那是什麼
What's the closest store
最近的商店在哪
Tricor
卓佳
Who's the store how do I get out of here close the store how do I close the store wide
誰是商店我怎麼離開這里關閉商店我如何關閉商店
I don't even know how to close the store unlock the door
我什至不知道如何關閉商店解鎖門
What is this
這是什麼
What is happening what do I need to do product scanner
發生了什麼我需要做什麼產品掃描儀
Okay I guess I'm taking off
好吧，我想我要起飛了
All the pastries out for some reason counter products
出於某種原因，所有糕點都出櫃了
I'm I'm scared yeah I do
我很害怕 是的 我很害怕
I don't know the music changed and everything self in the private investigator is not here anymore
我不知道音樂變了，私家偵探裡的一切都不在了
Where's the detective yeah where's the detective can we take the ladder
偵探在哪裡 是的 偵探在哪裡 我們可以帶梯子嗎
Tell where we can open the door the entire time
告訴我們在哪裡可以一直打開門
Old pastries you just toss it out
舊糕點你扔掉
Almost is just trashing the pastries
幾乎只是在浪費糕點
Before I draw the last pastries or anything else that missing
在我畫出最後的糕點或其他任何缺失的東西之前
What the signs are closed
什麼標誌是關閉的
Cool
涼爽的
What is it
它是什麼
I do I do I do
我做我做我做
Stay at the door
留在門口
So I have to run from him
所以我必須逃離他
Guys I don't know what to do here
伙計們，我不知道在這裡做什麼
I go get my phone
我去拿手機
Stop my phone took my phone
停止我的手機拿走了我的手機
I don't have my phone
我沒有手機
Screwdriver what do I have a screwdriver for events
螺絲刀 我有什麼活動用螺絲刀
The ladder
梯子
Maybe we hide in the vents
也許我們躲在通風口
Help help
幫助幫助
Help
幫助
Guys
伙計們
Thank God
感謝上帝
We have to take the car I should take the car
我們必須坐車 我應該坐車
Yeah I should take the car I should take the f****** car before he comes after me
是的，我應該坐車，我應該在他來找我之前坐那輛他媽的車
Go go get in the car and clean the car in the car
去 去 上車 把車裡的車擦乾淨
Why can't I get inside my car huh guys
為什麼我進不了我的車啊伙計們
Mikey's all he took my keys
Mikey 是他的全部，他拿走了我的鑰匙
On the roof maybe oh my God
也許在屋頂上 哦，我的上帝
No
不
These photographs of me the keys where are my keys
這些照片我的鑰匙我的鑰匙在哪裡
Guys where's my key
伙計們，我的鑰匙在哪裡
I'm so dead I'm so f****** dead I don't know how to get inside my car
我死了我死了我不知道如何進入我的車
Or I don't have my keys I can't take the bus if she keeps saying I should take the car
或者我沒有鑰匙，如果她一直說我應該坐車，我就不能坐公共汽車
The Walker gun
沃克槍
The roof
屋頂
It won't let me put the ladder down to get back on the roof you guys
它不會讓我放下梯子回到屋頂你們
It won't let me put it from the storage area
它不會讓我把它從存儲區
You're right you're right you're right you're right
你是對的 你是對的 你是對的 你是對的
Can we just kill em with the screwdriver
我們可以用螺絲刀殺死他們嗎
We're just going to get a break to break open the door all my God
我們只是要休息一下打開門我的上帝
I think we ought to break open the window
我想我們應該打破窗戶
The Brick
磚頭
I'm now
我現在
No
不
Why can't I break my
為什麼我不能打破我的
My car windows The Brick guys
我的車窗磚傢伙
Omaha
奧馬哈
Are we just going to murder him
我們是不是要殺了他
What the f*** bro
什麼他媽的兄弟
Arena kill him with a brick
競技場用磚頭殺了他
Think we have to kill him with the brick holyshit I don't have my
認為我們必須用磚頭乾掉他，我沒有我的
It's not giving me many options
它沒有給我很多選擇
Where she goes he's inside the bathroom why can't we just run like
她去哪裡他在浴室里為什麼我們不能像這樣跑
Can we just run I should take the car f*** the car why don't we just run
我們可以跑嗎我應該開車去他媽的車為什麼我們不跑
My car key
我的車鑰匙
Corky right here hold on hold on
Corky 就在這裡 等一下
Have the brick for what's the brick for
有什麼磚是為了什麼
Oh my God the purchaser to I mean I have the brick now I don't know what have the brick for a but I have to bring
哦，我的上帝，購買者對我的意思是我現在有磚我不知道磚有什麼用，但我必須帶上
Work now I guess I have to get out of here soon as possible
現在工作 我想我必須盡快離開這裡
Inside the car
車內
Dude what if he's already inside the car
伙計，如果他已經在車裡怎麼辦
You ever think about that and you like hiding in the backseat
你有沒有想過，你喜歡躲在後座
Oh my God I don't know what to do I don't know what to do
Oh my God 我不知道該怎麼做 我不知道該怎麼做
I get the brick ready I want to check the black one
我準備好磚我想檢查黑色的
What do I do here do I check the bathroom or die
我在這裡做什麼是檢查浴室還是死
Doors locked
門鎖著
I think I should just go on the car like there's no way I'm going to win against him with just a f******
我想我應該直接上車，就好像我不可能只用 af****** 贏他一樣
Brick guys right I'm going to drive
磚頭們，對，我要開車
I'm just going to drive
我只是要開車
You idiots
你們這些白痴
2 why are we so dumb why are we so dumb
2 為什麼我們這麼笨 為什麼我們這麼笨
I know it I f****** knew it
我知道我他媽的知道
F****** knew it I called that s***
F******知道我叫那個s***
Retry
重試
Oh my God
我的天啊
Lisa W me retry
Lisa W 我重試
You are creepy your creepy motherfuker you know that right
你是令人毛骨悚然 你的毛骨悚然的混蛋 你知道的對
I hate him I hate him
我恨他我恨他
Am I suppose
我想是不是
Grab the bull
抓住公牛
Brick so we don't take the car
磚，所以我們不開車
I have a brick now we're watch out
我現在有一塊磚，我們要小心
I can show you
我可以給你看
Now I can I hate that noise so much
現在我可以討厭那種噪音了
What's my do differently this time
這次我有什麼不同
The him from the rooftop was that what
屋頂上的他是什麼
I was supposed to do I was supposed to drop the brick on top of him from
我應該做的 我應該把磚頭從他身上掉下來
The roof and not all my god I think I'm boned I think I'm gon still guys all know it's Gigi
屋頂而不是我的上帝
Do the poor private investigator
做可憐的私家偵探
That's why you took so long
這就是為什麼你花了這麼長時間
Well I'm going to check this area again
好吧，我要再次檢查這個區域
No he's not here anymore
不，他不在這裡了
Okay bullshitz I have to do this again then
好吧，胡說八道，那我必須再做一次
Just have to go through the the same ending
只需要經歷同樣的結局
No I don't have to I can still go on the roof I can still go on the roof really oh my God
不，我不必，我仍然可以在屋頂上，我仍然可以在屋頂上，真的，我的上帝
Okay alright alright yeah
好吧好吧好吧
Where is he though
雖然他在哪裡
Is he all right if you're in the car he's already in the
如果你在車裡，他還好嗎？他已經在車裡了
Car yeah he's not here anymore I think he's already inside my car guys
車是的，他不在這裡了，我想他已經在我的車裡了伙計們
No he's already inside my car
不，他已經在我的車裡了
Oh s*** alright I'm just go back inside
哦，天哪，好吧，我只是回到裡面
Okay restart one more time
好的 再重啟一次
So f***** up
所以他媽的
I thought the event was a good idea like
我認為這個活動是個好主意
It's always seems like it's a good idea but whatever
這似乎總是一個好主意，但無論如何
Man
人
Alright one more time one more time
好吧 再來一次 再來一次
One more time
再一次
Your cross your gross your stinky your stinky you are disgusting you now
你的十字架 你的噁心 你的臭 你的臭 你現在讓你噁心
Not shave your ass
不剃你的屁股
I'm get the f*** out imma get the f*** out
I'm get the f*** out imma get the f*** out
Where is he
他在哪裡
I'll drop it on my car how do I drop
我會把它丟在我的車上 我怎麼丟
Put on my car drop it on my car
放在我的車上 把它放在我的車上
I can't even get their stop running around so fast and you'll see him
我什至無法阻止他們跑得這麼快，你會看到他
Okay
好的
Oh there he is
哦，他來了
What's goal
目標是什麼
Wow
哇
I killed a man as I picked up a brick the man looked right at me if I didn't drop I thought you would somehow
當我撿起一塊磚頭時，我殺了一個人，如果我沒有摔倒，那個人正看著我，我以為你會以某種方式
Noggin sign kill me that man looks terrifying that even know him why did he
Noggin 標誌殺了我那個男人看起來很可怕，甚至知道他為什麼他
I have no choice I didn't mean to kill him I was scared her into the police
我別無選擇 我不是故意要殺他 我被她嚇到報警了
I told the police everything that happened in the police took me back to the scene that man was no longer there
我告訴警察警察發生的一切把我帶回現場那個人已經不在了
There's no one there please tell me back home and told me to leave the rest of us and went back to investigate
那裡沒有人請告訴我回家告訴我離開我們其餘的人回去調查
It's all over it's hard after all that happened
一切都結束了，這一切都很難發生
Rest peacefully at home I'll know guys
在家里安靜地休息，我會知道伙計們
He he's inside our house isn't he
他他在我們家，不是嗎？
He's inside our house
他在我們家
Hello
你好
Cables acting weird again
電纜再次表現怪異
Call the owner
打電話給店主
Where's my phone
我的手機呢
God really
上帝真的
He has it
他有
Oh no bro it's outside I don't want to go outside
哦，不，兄弟，在外面，我不想出去
I have to though
我不得不
New phone just got a new phone it's okay
新手機剛拿到新手機沒關係
God we're gang baited rigging beat it's so hard
上帝，我們是幫派誘餌索具打敗它太難了
Why are we letting this happen
我們為什麼要讓這種情況發生
Yikes snowman please no
哎呀雪人請不要
Next to the car to
旁邊的車到
I think he's inside our apartment now
我想他現在在我們的公寓裡
Eyes we got our phone but
眼睛，我們得到了我們的手機，但是
I don't want to walk back up to the apartment he's inside
我不想走回他在裡面的公寓
Oh my God
我的天啊
Oh no
不好了
We really just still losing
我們真的只是還在輸
In the end
到底
I can't believe this I feel cheated man
我不敢相信這我覺得被騙了
We work so hard to see live with a brick like throw into his head
我們拼命看活用磚頭一樣扔進他的腦袋
I got your back I just built different
我得到了你的支持我只是建立了不同的
I don't know how you lived I was a heavy Bricks Young Man
我不知道你是怎麼過的我是一個沉重的磚頭年輕人
Would you live how did he live
你會活嗎 他是怎麼活的
Well I thought guys
好吧，我以為伙計們
I mean that was a really good game
我的意思是那是一場非常棒的比賽
I like a lot a lot of envelopes you much. Coffee making about the same time
我很喜歡你很多很多的信封。大約在同一時間製作咖啡
Is really terrifying staff to deal with the
真的是可怕的工作人員來處理
Weird Al showing up every now and then and creeping around knowing you lived in the stuff
奇怪的艾爾時不時地出現並四處走動，知道你住在這些東西里
Around the other area where the coffee was stored that's so weird
在存放咖啡的另一個區域周圍，這太奇怪了
I had a feeling sooner because that door was locked the entire time and it didn't even let us know
我有一種感覺，因為那扇門一直鎖著，甚至沒有讓我們知道
No like what was behind her the movie Think Like there has to be something secretive back there involving that
不像她的電影 Think Like 背後一定有一些秘密的東西
Your stalker
你的跟踪狂
That was a good game
那是一場好比賽
I like that a lot you found washable thank you
我很喜歡你發現可以洗的謝謝
Oh my God is that mean I'm I'm like certified to be a barista now
哦，我的上帝，這意味著我現在已經獲得了咖啡師資格
I can I can work out a Starbucks going for an hour right
我可以我可以算出星巴克一個小時的權利
Why does my training training montage
為什麼我的訓練訓練蒙太奇
But it's no I hadn't
但我沒有
Nice times in that little I don't know it was kind of like a cafe simulator
在那小小的我不知道它有點像咖啡館模擬器的美好時光
Type of thing
事物類型
Mixed in with all the horror elements all Android it
混合了所有Android它的所有恐怖元素
Had a fun time
度過了愉快的時光
Allow
允許
House creepy
令人毛骨悚然的房子
I think the biggest jump-scare though
我認為最大的跳躍恐慌
The biggest jump scare the entire time was the f****** lady with the baby carriage and she just showed up
整個過程中最大的跳躍恐慌是那個帶嬰兒車的f******女士，她剛剛出現
Just tell me to watch where I was going. I don't think anything else scared me more than that
只是告訴我看我要去哪裡。我認為沒有什麼比這更讓我害怕了
Is everything else was kind of like I expected it to happen then the f****** on C baby carriage
是不是一切都像我預期的那樣發生在C嬰兒車上的f******
It was known that really got me out of everything
眾所周知，這真的讓我擺脫了一切
Sad
傷心
But it is getting late guys and I have another stream
但是時間不早了，伙計們，我還有另一個流
With y'all in about saw 8 hours from now so I have to send it off here so I can get some proper
你們都在大約 8 小時後，所以我必須把它送到這裡，這樣我才能得到一些合適的
Sleep and get ready for tomorrow
睡覺，為明天做準備
Salon give me a second European
沙龍給我第二個歐洲人
Quit the game first
先退出遊戲
I move over to the all
我移到所有
The bedroom
臥室
Where's the bedroom
臥室在哪裡
Are there it is
有沒有
Give me a second almost looking to turn on some music for y'all tell
給我一秒鐘幾乎想打開一些音樂給你們說
Cuz I want to be
因為我想成為
Bathroom overlay
浴室覆蓋物
Wonky
搖搖晃晃
And saw
並且看到了
I'm not there
我不在
Cuz I'm right here now
因為我現在就在這裡
Oh wait hold on
哦等等等等
Give me a second
你稍等一會兒
11-second
11 秒
Are you gone now looks better
你走了嗎現在看起來好多了
Those are really fun time I've generally like talking a lot you kind of like reminded me of
那些真的很有趣
Even when it's a horror game you still coming
就算是恐怖遊戲你還是會來
You're amazing and I hope you have tons of fun tomorrow as well
你太棒了，我希望你明天也有很多樂趣
Thank you all
謝謝你們
I'm side Supply until dawn for a little bit if you guys tomorrow I'll so yeah it was really nice to get to just
如果你們明天我會的，我會一直供應到黎明
Even though
雖然
We struggled a bit the horror was definitely a presence and I'm glad that the Explorer the theme
我們有點掙扎，恐怖絕對是存在的，我很高興探索者的主題
I wasn't really explored before where it is not just ghost and creepy like you know possession and demons
我之前並沒有真正探索過它不僅僅是幽靈和令人毛骨悚然的地方，就像你知道的附身和惡魔一樣
Urban legends this time around the looks that you know actual stalkers which is pretty cool I like that
這次的都市傳說圍繞著你知道真正的跟踪狂的樣子，這很酷，我喜歡
Applejack thank you again for doing the saw you know except for me
蘋果傑克再次感謝你做了除了我之外你知道的鋸子
Aquila lockup
天鷹座鎖定
You know how nice it so I can actually be a proper barista
你知道這有多好，所以我實際上可以成為一個合適的咖啡師
Tonight
今晚
Julie sweet
朱莉甜
Black nails are pretty thank you
黑指甲很漂亮 謝謝
Also hold on I see I feel like I am a bit late on all the donations and stuff like that but like give me a s i z e
還堅持一下
Thank you for the $5.20 sodaman thank you for that tenancy longest subs off
感謝您提供 5.20 美元的蘇打水，感謝您提供最長的租期
B-boy Bowser thank you for the $15
B-boy Bowser 謝謝你的 15 美元
Ends off some of our thank you for the bits
結束我們的一些感謝您的位
Memorial Day
紀念日
Get that SOB
得到那個 SOB
But you guys are all the gifted subs and all the results and all the new Subs is a lot of news people that join the guild today till so
但是你們都是有天賦的潛艇，所有的結果，所有的新潛艇都是今天加入公會的很多新聞人，直到現在
Hope you having a good one and Zoe
希望你和佐伊過得愉快
Exactly the stream in a little while from now till
正是從現在到現在
Also traveler thing for the $10 and saw anything for the gifted Subs
還有 10 美元的旅行用品，並為有天賦的 Subs 看到了任何東西
It's
它是
It's really late in the night already I'm going to go to bed in a little bit because it's sorry 1 a.m. so
已經很晚了，我要稍微睡覺了，因為對不起，凌晨 1 點
Thank you guys for coming by tonight and
謝謝你們今晚光臨
Like I said before I always have a nice time just chilling out and doing horror indie horror games like this in and I'll games
就像我之前說的，我總是很開心，只是放鬆一下，做這樣的恐怖獨立恐怖遊戲，我會玩
Relaxed even though isn't that so relaxing and it was overall like
放鬆，即使不是那麼放鬆，總體來說就像
I feel comfortable letting these kinds of games and stuff how we get to do this again in the future looks like from work she looking
我覺得讓這些遊戲和東西讓我們在未來再次做到這一點看起來很舒服，就像她看起來的工作一樣
Games are like other Indie Games I find out Illinois are
遊戲就像我發現伊利諾伊州的其他獨立遊戲一樣
Goodnight Chouteau
晚安喬托
I'm not supposed to announcement after I and stream that we're going to be coming live in
我不應該在我和流媒體之後宣布我們將要直播
Different nozzle a little later
稍後不同的噴嘴
More streams
更多信息流
What's Gomer streams Prague okay
什麼是 Gomer 流布拉格的好
Okay take care and Zaza remember to join the Discord if you have it
好的，保重，如果你有的話，Zaza 記得加入 Discord
Already it's discord.gg / football we like to hang out there and soft play video
已經是 discord.gg / football 我們喜歡在那裡閒逛和軟播放視頻
Shell out Sands all over everyone there is just really nice and friendly so
把金沙扔到每個人身上，真的很好很友好，所以
I'll come by in the plug-ins for sometime or just get announcements on now when I go live
我會在插件中出現一段時間，或者在我上線時立即獲得公告
Refrigerant Discord okay
製冷劑不和諧
Appreciate on
欣賞
Alright
好的
What's enough
什麼夠了
Don't look for somebody to write tonight Phoenix thank you for the $13.37
今晚不要找人寫 Phoenix 謝謝你的 13.37 美元
The $5 in
5 美元
I think they're $6.90 that's okay hope you're having a good night
我認為它們是 6.90 美元，沒關係希望你過得愉快
Rushmore
拉什莫爾
Sleep more you're obviously tired right so also thank you for the $5
多睡一點，你顯然很累，所以也謝謝你的 5 美元
Appreciate song
欣賞歌曲
And I are going to be streaming in the little bit suicidal that's why I want to get my sleep
而且我會流著一點點自殺這就是為什麼我想睡覺
That's exactly why I want to get my sleep song
這就是為什麼我想要我的睡眠歌曲
And again one more time thank you guys for 200k
再一次感謝你們 200k
It means a lot wrong with that 300 downloader
這意味著 300 下載器有很多問題
Another mile summer we found so fast it's hard to keep up but again
又一英里的夏天，我們發現速度如此之快，很難跟上，但又一次
It means a lot that you guys are still around then want to support me
這意味著很多你們還在身邊然後想支持我
I'm not only platforms and I'll try not to disappoint
我不僅是平台而且我會盡量不讓你失望
Imma keep
伊瑪保留
Keep giving it my all and zoc keep doing my best for you guys all right
繼續全力以赴，zoc 繼續為你們盡我所能
Alright let me go and look for somebody that's life tonight and then we can hop on off and sleep
好吧，讓我去尋找今晚有生命的人，然後我們就可以上車睡覺了
Who's live
誰在直播
Who is life who is live
誰是生活誰是生活
I want to go inside I bother
我想進去我打擾了
Very tricky
非常棘手
Tricky sounds like a good person to write tonight right
Tricky 聽起來是個今晚寫作的好人吧
I think there's anybody else
我覺得還有人
Tricky
棘手
All right take care guys have a good one I'll see you all
好吧，保重，伙計們有一個很好的，我會見到你們的
Jason
傑森
Love you bye bye
愛你再見
Play some good music now
現在播放一些好音樂
Something that's a little bit more hype Albia upon over
阿爾比亞的炒作有點過頭了
Are you going to listen to this again because why not
你會再聽一遍嗎，因為為什麼不
They care guys before I disown
在我否認之前，他們關心男人
Camaro
卡馬羅